     
    <rows>
         
            <value column="0">Qraspine</value>
            <value column="1">of Grasp</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qua</value>
            <value column="1">In so far as; in the capacity or character of; as.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qua-bird</value>
            <value column="1">The American night heron. See under Night.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quab</value>
            <value column="1">An unfledged bird; hence, something immature or unfinished.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quab</value>
            <value column="1">See Quob, v. i.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quacha</value>
            <value column="1">The quagga.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quack</value>
            <value column="1">To utter a sound like the cry of a duck.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quack</value>
            <value column="1">To make vain and loud pretensions; to boast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quack</value>
            <value column="1">To act the part of a quack, or pretender.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quack</value>
            <value column="1">The cry of the duck, or a sound in imitation of it; a hoarse, quacking noise.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quack</value>
            <value column="1">A boastful pretender to medical skill; an empiric; an ignorant practitioner.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quack</value>
            <value column="1">Hence, one who boastfully pretends to skill or knowledge of any kind not possessed; a charlatan.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quack</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to or characterized by, boasting and pretension; used by quacks; pretending to cure diseases; as, a quack medicine; a quack doctor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quack grass</value>
            <value column="1">See Quitch grass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quackeries</value>
            <value column="1">of Quackery</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quackery</value>
            <value column="1">The acts, arts, or boastful pretensions of a quack; false pretensions to any art; empiricism.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quacking</value>
            <value column="1">of Quack</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quackish</value>
            <value column="1">Like a quack; boasting; characterized by quackery.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quackism</value>
            <value column="1">Quackery.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quackle</value>
            <value column="1">To suffocate; to choke.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quackled</value>
            <value column="1">of Quackle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quackling</value>
            <value column="1">of Quackle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quacksalver</value>
            <value column="1">One who boasts of his skill in medicines and salves, or of the efficacy of his prescriptions; a charlatan; a quack; a mountebank.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quad</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quade</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quad</value>
            <value column="1">A quadrat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quad</value>
            <value column="1">A quadrangle; hence, a prison.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quade</value>
            <value column="1">Evil; bad; baffling; as, a quade wind.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadra</value>
            <value column="1">The plinth, or lowest member, of any pedestal, podium, water table, or the like.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadra</value>
            <value column="1">A fillet, or listel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrable</value>
            <value column="1">That may be sqyared, or reduced to an equivalent square; -- said of a surface when the area limited by a curve can be exactly found, and expressed in a finite number of algebraic terms.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrae</value>
            <value column="1">of Quadra</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadragenarious</value>
            <value column="1">Consisting of forty; forty years old.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadragene</value>
            <value column="1">An indulgence of forty days, corresponding to the forty days of ancient canonical penance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadragesima</value>
            <value column="1">The forty days of fast preceding Easter; Lent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadragesimal</value>
            <value column="1">Belonging to Lent; used in Lent; Lenten.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadragesimals</value>
            <value column="1">Offerings formerly made to the mother church of a diocese on Mid-Lent Sunday.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrangle</value>
            <value column="1">A plane figure having four angles, and consequently four sides; any figure having four angles.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrangle</value>
            <value column="1">A square or quadrangular space or inclosure, such a space or court surrounded by buildings, esp. such a court in a college or public school in England.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrangular</value>
            <value column="1">Having four angles, and consequently four sides; tetragonal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrans</value>
            <value column="1">A fourth part of the coin called an as. See 3d As, 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrans</value>
            <value column="1">The fourth of a penny; a farthing. See Cur.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrant</value>
            <value column="1">The fourth part; the quarter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrant</value>
            <value column="1">The quarter of a circle, or of the circumference of a circle, an arc of 90ยก, or one subtending a right angle at the center.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrant</value>
            <value column="1">One of the four parts into which a plane is divided by the coordinate axes. The upper right-hand part is the first quadrant; the upper left-hand part the second; the lower left-hand part the third; and the lower right-hand part the fourth quadrant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrant</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument for measuring altitudes, variously constructed and mounted for different specific uses in astronomy, surveying, gunnery, etc., consisting commonly of a graduated arc of 90ยก, with an index or vernier, and either plain or telescopic sights, and usually having a plumb line or spirit level for fixing the vertical or horizontal direction.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrantal</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to a quadrant; also, included in the fourth part of a circle; as, quadrantal space.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrantal</value>
            <value column="1">A cubical vessel containing a Roman cubic foot, each side being a Roman square foot; -- used as a measure.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrantal</value>
            <value column="1">A cube.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrantes</value>
            <value column="1">of Quadrans</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrat</value>
            <value column="1">A block of type metal lower than the letters, -- used in spacing and in blank lines.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrat</value>
            <value column="1">An old instrument used for taking altitudes; -- called also geometrical square, and line of shadows.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrate</value>
            <value column="1">Having four equal sides, the opposite sides parallel, and four right angles; square.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrate</value>
            <value column="1">Produced by multiplying a number by itself; square.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrate</value>
            <value column="1">Square; even; balanced; equal; exact.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrate</value>
            <value column="1">Squared; suited; correspondent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrate</value>
            <value column="1">A plane surface with four equal sides and four right angles; a square; hence, figuratively, anything having the outline of a square.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrate</value>
            <value column="1">An aspect of the heavenly bodies in which they are distant from each other 90ยก, or the quarter of a circle; quartile. See the Note under Aspect, 6.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrate</value>
            <value column="1">The quadrate bone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrate</value>
            <value column="1">To square; to agree; to suit; to correspond; -- followed by with.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrate</value>
            <value column="1">To adjust (a gun) on its carriage; also, to train (a gun) for horizontal firing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrated</value>
            <value column="1">of Quadrate</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadratic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to a square, or to squares; resembling a quadrate, or square; square.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadratic</value>
            <value column="1">Tetragonal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadratic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to terms of the second degree; as, a quadratic equation, in which the highest power of the unknown quantity is a square.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadratics</value>
            <value column="1">That branch of algebra which treats of quadratic equations.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrating</value>
            <value column="1">of Quadrate</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadratojugal</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the quadrate and jugal bones.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadratojugal</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the quadratojugal bone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadratojugal</value>
            <value column="1">The quadratojugal bone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadratrix</value>
            <value column="1">A curve made use of in the quadrature of other curves; as the quadratrix, of Dinostratus, or of Tschirnhausen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrature</value>
            <value column="1">The act of squaring; the finding of a square having the same area as some given curvilinear figure; as, the quadrature of a circle; the operation of finding an expression for the area of a figure bounded wholly or in part by a curved line, as by a curve, two ordinates, and the axis of abscissas.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrature</value>
            <value column="1">A quadrate; a square.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrature</value>
            <value column="1">The integral used in obtaining the area bounded by a curve; hence, the definite integral of the product of any function of one variable into the differential of that variable.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrature</value>
            <value column="1">The position of one heavenly body in respect to another when distant from it 90ยก, or a quarter of a circle, as the moon when at an equal distance from the points of conjunction and opposition.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrel</value>
            <value column="1">A square piece of turf or peat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrel</value>
            <value column="1">A square brick, tile, or the like.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrennial</value>
            <value column="1">Comprising four years; as, a quadrennial period.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrennial</value>
            <value column="1">Occurring once in four years, or at the end of every four years; as, quadrennial games.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrennially</value>
            <value column="1">Once in four years.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrennium</value>
            <value column="1">A space or period of four years.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadri-</value>
            <value column="1">A combining form meaning four, four times, fourfold; as, quadricapsular, having four capsules.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadri-syllabical</value>
            <value column="1">Having four syllables; of or pertaining to quadrisyllables; as, a quadrisyllabic word.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadribasic</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Tetrabasic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrible</value>
            <value column="1">Quadrable.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadric</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the second degree.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadric</value>
            <value column="1">A quantic of the second degree. See Quantic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadric</value>
            <value column="1">A surface whose equation in three variables is of the second degree. Spheres, spheroids, ellipsoids, paraboloids, hyperboloids, also cones and cylinders with circular bases, are quadrics.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadricapsular</value>
            <value column="1">Having four capsules.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadriceps</value>
            <value column="1">The great extensor muscle of the knee, divided above into four parts which unite in a single tendon at the knee.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadricipital</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the quadriceps.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadricorn</value>
            <value column="1">Any quadricornous animal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadricornous</value>
            <value column="1">Having four horns, or hornlike organs; as, a quadricornous beetle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadricostate</value>
            <value column="1">Having four ribs.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadridentate</value>
            <value column="1">Having four teeth; as, a quadridentate leaf.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadriennial</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Quadrennial.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrifarious</value>
            <value column="1">Arranged in four rows or ranks; as, quadrifarious leaves.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrifid</value>
            <value column="1">Divided, or deeply cleft, into four parts; as, a quadrifid perianth; a quadrifid leaf.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrifoil</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quadrifoliate</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrifoliate</value>
            <value column="1">Four-leaved; having the leaves in whorls of four.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrifurcated</value>
            <value column="1">Having four forks, or branches.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadriga</value>
            <value column="1">A car or chariot drawn by four horses abreast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrigae</value>
            <value column="1">of Quadriga</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrigeminal</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quadrigeminous</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrigeminous</value>
            <value column="1">Fourfold; having four similar parts, or two pairs of similar parts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrigenarious</value>
            <value column="1">Consisting of four hundred.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrijugate</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Quadrijugous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrijugous</value>
            <value column="1">Pinnate, with four pairs of leaflets; as, a quadrijugous leaf.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrilateral</value>
            <value column="1">Having four sides, and consequently four angles; quadrangular.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrilateral</value>
            <value column="1">A plane figure having four sides, and consequently four angles; a quadrangular figure; any figure formed by four lines.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrilateral</value>
            <value column="1">An area defended by four fortresses supporting each other; as, the Venetian quadrilateral, comprising Mantua, Peschiera, Verona, and Legnano.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrilateralness</value>
            <value column="1">The property of being quadrilateral.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadriliteral</value>
            <value column="1">Consisting of four letters.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrille</value>
            <value column="1">A dance having five figures, in common time, four couples of dancers being in each set.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrille</value>
            <value column="1">The appropriate music for a quadrille.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrille</value>
            <value column="1">A game played by four persons with forty cards, being the remainder of an ordinary pack after the tens, nines, and eights are discarded.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrillion</value>
            <value column="1">According to the French notation, which is followed also upon the Continent and in the United States, a unit with fifteen ciphers annexed; according to the English notation, the number produced by involving a million to the fourth power, or the number represented by a unit with twenty-four ciphers annexed. See the Note under Numeration.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrilobate</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quadrilobed</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrilobed</value>
            <value column="1">Having four lobes; as, a quadrilobate leaf.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrilocular</value>
            <value column="1">Having four cells, or cavities; as, a quadrilocular heart.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrin</value>
            <value column="1">A small piece of money, in value about a farthing, or a half cent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrinodal</value>
            <value column="1">Possessing four nodes; as, quadrinodal curves.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrinomial</value>
            <value column="1">A polynomial of four terms connected by the signs plus or minus.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrinomical</value>
            <value column="1">Quadrinomial.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrinominal</value>
            <value column="1">Quadrinomial.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadripartite</value>
            <value column="1">Divided into four parts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadripartitely</value>
            <value column="1">In four parts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadripartition</value>
            <value column="1">A division or distribution by four, or into four parts; also, a taking the fourth part of any quantity or number.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadripennate</value>
            <value column="1">Having four wings; -- said of insects.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadriphyllous</value>
            <value column="1">Having four leaves; quadrifoliate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrireme</value>
            <value column="1">A galley with four banks of oars or rowers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrisection</value>
            <value column="1">A subdivision into four parts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrisulcate</value>
            <value column="1">Having four hoofs; as, a quadrisulcate foot; a quadrisulcate animal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrisyllabic</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quadri-syllabical</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrisyllable</value>
            <value column="1">A word consisting of four syllables.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrivalence</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being quadrivalent; tetravalence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrivalent</value>
            <value column="1">Having a valence of four; capable of combining with, being replaced by, or compared with, four monad atoms; tetravalent; -- said of certain atoms and radicals; thus, carbon and silicon are quadrivalent elements.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrivalve</value>
            <value column="1">Dehiscent into four similar parts; four-valved; as, a quadrivalve pericarp.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrivalve</value>
            <value column="1">A door, shutter, or the like, having four folds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrivalvular</value>
            <value column="1">Having four valves; quadrivalve.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrivial</value>
            <value column="1">Having four ways meeting in a point.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrivial</value>
            <value column="1">One of the four &quot;liberal arts&quot; making up the quadrivium.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrivium</value>
            <value column="1"><![CDATA[The four "liberal arts," arithmetic, music, geometry, and astronomy; -- so called by the schoolmen. See Trivium.]]></value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadroon</value>
            <value column="1">The offspring of a mulatto and a white person; a person quarter-blooded.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadroxide</value>
            <value column="1">A tetroxide.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrumana</value>
            <value column="1">A division of the Primates comprising the apes and monkeys; -- so called because the hind foot is usually prehensile, and the great toe opposable somewhat like a thumb. Formerly the Quadrumana were considered an order distinct from the Bimana, which last included man alone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrumane</value>
            <value column="1">One of the Quadrumana.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrumanous</value>
            <value column="1">Having four hands; of or pertaining to the Quadrumana.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruped</value>
            <value column="1">Having four feet.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruped</value>
            <value column="1">An animal having four feet, as most mammals and reptiles; -- often restricted to the mammals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrupedal</value>
            <value column="1">Having four feet; of or pertaining to a quadruped.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruple</value>
            <value column="1">Fourfold; as, to make quadruple restitution; a quadruple alliance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruple</value>
            <value column="1">four times the sum or number; a fourfold amount; as, to receive to quadruple of the amount in damages.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruple</value>
            <value column="1">To multiply by four; to increase fourfold; to double; to double twice.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruple</value>
            <value column="1">To be multiplied by four; to increase fourfold; to become four times as much.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrupled</value>
            <value column="1">of Quadruple</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruplex</value>
            <value column="1">Fourfold; folded or doubled twice.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruplicate</value>
            <value column="1">To make fourfold; to double twice; to quadruple.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruplicate</value>
            <value column="1">Fourfold; doubled twice; four times repeated; as, a quadruplicate ratio, or a quadruplicate proportion.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruplicate</value>
            <value column="1">Raised to the fourth power.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruplicated</value>
            <value column="1">of Quadruplicate</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruplicating</value>
            <value column="1">of Quadruplicate</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruplication</value>
            <value column="1">The act of making fourfold; a taking four times the simple sum or amount.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadrupling</value>
            <value column="1">of Quadruple</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quadruply</value>
            <value column="1">To a fourfold quantity; so as to be, or cause to be, quadruple; as, to be quadruply recompensed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaere</value>
            <value column="1">Inquire; question; see; -- used to signify doubt or to suggest investigation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaestor</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Questor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaff</value>
            <value column="1">To drink with relish; to drink copiously of; to swallow in large draughts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaff</value>
            <value column="1">To drink largely or luxuriously.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaffed</value>
            <value column="1">of Quaff</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaffer</value>
            <value column="1">One who quaffs, or drinks largely.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaffing</value>
            <value column="1">of Quaff</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quag</value>
            <value column="1">A quagmire.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quagga</value>
            <value column="1">A South African wild ass (Equus, / Hippotigris, quagga). The upper parts are reddish brown, becoming paler behind and behind and beneath, with dark stripes on the face, neck, and fore part of the body.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaggy</value>
            <value column="1">Of the nature of a quagmire; yielding or trembling under the foot, as soft, wet earth; spongy; boggy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quagmire</value>
            <value column="1">Soft, wet, miry land, which shakes or yields under the feet.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quahaug</value>
            <value column="1">An American market clam (Venus mercenaria). It is sold in large quantities, and is highly valued as food. Called also round clam, and hard clam.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quahog</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quahaug</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaich</value>
            <value column="1">A small shallow cup or drinking vessel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaigh</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quaich</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quail</value>
            <value column="1">To die; to perish; hence, to wither; to fade.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quail</value>
            <value column="1">To become quelled; to become cast down; to sink under trial or apprehension of danger; to lose the spirit and power of resistance; to lose heart; to give way; to shrink; to cower.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quail</value>
            <value column="1">To cause to fail in spirit or power; to quell; to crush; to subdue.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quail</value>
            <value column="1">To curdle; to coagulate, as milk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quail</value>
            <value column="1">Any gallinaceous bird belonging to Coturnix and several allied genera of the Old World, especially the common European quail (C. communis), the rain quail (C. Coromandelica) of India, the stubble quail (C. pectoralis), and the Australian swamp quail (Synoicus australis).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quail</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several American partridges belonging to Colinus, Callipepla, and allied genera, especially the bobwhite (called Virginia quail, and Maryland quail), and the California quail (Calipepla Californica).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quail</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of numerous species of Turnix and allied genera, native of the Old World, as the Australian painted quail (Turnix varius). See Turnix.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quail</value>
            <value column="1">A prostitute; -- so called because the quail was thought to be a very amorous bird.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaily</value>
            <value column="1">The upland plover.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaint</value>
            <value column="1">Prudent; wise; hence, crafty; artful; wily.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaint</value>
            <value column="1">Characterized by ingenuity or art; finely fashioned; skillfully wrought; elegant; graceful; nice; neat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaint</value>
            <value column="1">Curious and fanciful; affected; odd; whimsical; antique; archaic; singular; unusual; as, quaint architecture; a quaint expression.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaintise</value>
            <value column="1">Craft; subtlety; cunning.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaintise</value>
            <value column="1">Elegance; beauty.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaintly</value>
            <value column="1">In a quaint manner.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaintness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality of being quaint.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quair</value>
            <value column="1">A quire; a book.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quake</value>
            <value column="1">To be agitated with quick, short motions continually repeated; to shake with fear, cold, etc.; to shudder; to tremble.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quake</value>
            <value column="1">To shake, vibrate, or quiver, either from not being solid, as soft, wet land, or from violent convulsion of any kind; as, the earth quakes; the mountains quake.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quake</value>
            <value column="1">To cause to quake.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quake</value>
            <value column="1">A tremulous agitation; a quick vibratory movement; a shudder; a quivering.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaked</value>
            <value column="1">of Quake</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaker</value>
            <value column="1">One who quakes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaker</value>
            <value column="1">One of a religious sect founded by George Fox, of Leicestershire, England, about 1650, -- the members of which call themselves Friends. They were called Quakers, originally, in derision. See Friend, n., 4.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaker</value>
            <value column="1">The nankeen bird.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaker</value>
            <value column="1">The sooty albatross.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaker</value>
            <value column="1">Any grasshopper or locust of the genus (Edipoda; -- so called from the quaking noise made during flight.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quakeress</value>
            <value column="1">A woman who is a member of the Society of Friends.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quakerish</value>
            <value column="1">Like or pertaining to a Quaker; Quakerlike.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quakerism</value>
            <value column="1">The peculiar character, manners, tenets, etc., of the Quakers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quakerlike</value>
            <value column="1">Like a Quaker.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quakerly</value>
            <value column="1">Resembling Quakers; Quakerlike; Quakerish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quakery</value>
            <value column="1">Quakerism.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaketail</value>
            <value column="1">A wagtail.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaking</value>
            <value column="1">of Quake</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaking</value>
            <value column="1">a. &amp; n. from Quake, v.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quakingly</value>
            <value column="1">In a quaking manner; fearfully.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quakness</value>
            <value column="1">The state of being quaky; liability to quake.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaky</value>
            <value column="1">Shaky, or tremulous; quaking.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualifiable</value>
            <value column="1">Capable of being qualified; abatable; modifiable.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualification</value>
            <value column="1">The act of qualifying, or the condition of being qualified.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualification</value>
            <value column="1">That which qualifies; any natural endowment, or any acquirement, which fits a person for a place, office, or employment, or which enables him to sustian any character with success; an enabling quality or circumstance; requisite capacity or possession.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualification</value>
            <value column="1">The act of limiting, or the state of being limited; that which qualifies by limiting; modification; restriction; hence, abatement; diminution; as, to use words without any qualification.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualificative</value>
            <value column="1">That which qualifies, modifies, or restricts; a qualifying term or statement.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualificator</value>
            <value column="1">An officer whose business it is to examine and prepare causes for trial in the ecclesiastical courts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualified</value>
            <value column="1">Fitted by accomplishments or endowments.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualified</value>
            <value column="1">Modified; limited; as, a qualified statement.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualified</value>
            <value column="1">of Qualify</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualifiedly</value>
            <value column="1">In the way of qualification; with modification or qualification.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualifiedness</value>
            <value column="1">The state of being qualified.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualifier</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, qualifies; that which modifies, reduces, tempers or restrains.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualify</value>
            <value column="1">To make such as is required; to give added or requisite qualities to; to fit, as for a place, office, occupation, or character; to furnish with the knowledge, skill, or other accomplishment necessary for a purpose; to make capable, as of an employment or privilege; to supply with legal power or capacity.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualify</value>
            <value column="1">To give individual quality to; to modulate; to vary; to regulate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualify</value>
            <value column="1">To reduce from a general, undefined, or comprehensive form, to particular or restricted form; to modify; to limit; to restrict; to restrain; as, to qualify a statement, claim, or proposition.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualify</value>
            <value column="1">Hence, to soften; to abate; to diminish; to assuage; to reduce the strength of, as liquors.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualify</value>
            <value column="1">To soothe; to cure; -- said of persons.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualify</value>
            <value column="1">To be or become qualified; to be fit, as for an office or employment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualify</value>
            <value column="1">To obtain legal power or capacity by taking the oath, or complying with the forms required, on assuming an office.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualifying</value>
            <value column="1">of Qualify</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualitative</value>
            <value column="1">Relating to quality; having the character of quality.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualitied</value>
            <value column="1">Furnished with qualities; endowed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualities</value>
            <value column="1">of Quality</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quality</value>
            <value column="1">The condition of being of such and such a sort as distinguished from others; nature or character relatively considered, as of goods; character; sort; rank.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quality</value>
            <value column="1">Special or temporary character; profession; occupation; assumed or asserted rank, part, or position.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quality</value>
            <value column="1">That which makes, or helps to make, anything such as it is; anything belonging to a subject, or predicable of it; distinguishing property, characteristic, or attribute; peculiar power, capacity, or virtue; distinctive trait; as, the tones of a flute differ from those of a violin in quality; the great quality of a statesman.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quality</value>
            <value column="1">An acquired trait; accomplishment; acquisition.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quality</value>
            <value column="1">Superior birth or station; high rank; elevated character.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualled</value>
            <value column="1">of Quail</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualling</value>
            <value column="1">of Quail</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualm</value>
            <value column="1">Sickness; disease; pestilence; death.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualm</value>
            <value column="1">A sudden attack of illness, faintness, or pain; an agony.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualm</value>
            <value column="1">Especially, a sudden sensation of nausea.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualm</value>
            <value column="1">A prick or scruple of conscience; uneasiness of conscience; compunction.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qualmish</value>
            <value column="1">Sick at the stomach; affected with nausea or sickly languor; inclined to vomit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quamash</value>
            <value column="1">See Camass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quamoclit</value>
            <value column="1">Formerly, a genus of plants including the cypress vine (Quamoclit vulgaris, now called Ipomoea Quamoclit). The genus is now merged in Ipomoea.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quandaries</value>
            <value column="1">of Quandary</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quandary</value>
            <value column="1">A state of difficulty or perplexity; doubt; uncertainty.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quandary</value>
            <value column="1">To bring into a state of uncertainty, perplexity, or difficulty.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quandong</value>
            <value column="1">The edible drupaceous fruit of an Australian tree (Fusanus acuminatus) of the Sandalwood family; -- called also quandang.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quandy</value>
            <value column="1">The old squaw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quannet</value>
            <value column="1">A flat file having the handle at one side, so as to be used like a plane.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quant</value>
            <value column="1">A punting pole with a broad flange near the end to prevent it from sinking into the mud; a setting pole.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quanta</value>
            <value column="1">of Quantum</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantic</value>
            <value column="1">A homogeneous algebraic function of two or more variables, in general containing only positive integral powers of the variables, and called quadric, cubic, quartic, etc., according as it is of the second, third, fourth, fifth, or a higher degree. These are further called binary, ternary, quaternary, etc., according as they contain two, three, four, or more variables; thus, the quantic / is a binary cubic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantification</value>
            <value column="1">Modification by a reference to quantity; the introduction of the element of quantity.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantitative</value>
            <value column="1">Relating to quantity.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantities</value>
            <value column="1">of Quantity</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantitive</value>
            <value column="1">Estimable according to quantity; quantitative.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantitively</value>
            <value column="1">So as to be measurable by quantity; quantitatively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantity</value>
            <value column="1">To modify or qualify with respect to quantity; to fix or express the quantity of; to rate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantity</value>
            <value column="1"><![CDATA[The attribute of being so much, and not more or less; the property of being measurable, or capable of increase and decrease, multiplication and division; greatness; and more concretely, that which answers the question "How much?"; measure in regard to bulk or amount; determinate or comparative dimensions; measure; amount; bulk; extent; size.]]></value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantity</value>
            <value column="1">The extent or extension of a general conception, that is, the number of species or individuals to which it may be applied; also, its content or comprehension, that is, the number of its constituent qualities, attributes, or relations.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantity</value>
            <value column="1">The measure of a syllable; that which determines the time in which it is pronounced; as, the long or short quantity of a vowel or syllable.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantity</value>
            <value column="1">The relative duration of a tone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantity</value>
            <value column="1">That which can be increased, diminished, or measured; especially (Math.), anything to which mathematical processes are applicable.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantity</value>
            <value column="1">A determinate or estimated amount; a sum or bulk; a certain portion or part; sometimes, a considerable amount; a large portion, bulk, or sum; as, a medicine taken in quantities, that is, in large quantities.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantivalence</value>
            <value column="1">Valence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantivalent</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to quantivalence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantum</value>
            <value column="1">Quantity; amount.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quantum</value>
            <value column="1">A definite portion of a manifoldness, limited by a mark or by a boundary.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quap</value>
            <value column="1">To quaver.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaquaversal</value>
            <value column="1">Turning or dipping in any or every direction.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaquaversal</value>
            <value column="1">Dipping toward all points of the compass round a center, as beds of lava round a crater.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quar</value>
            <value column="1">A quarry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarantine</value>
            <value column="1">A space of forty days; -- used of Lent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarantine</value>
            <value column="1">Specifically, the term, originally of forty days, during which a ship arriving in port, and suspected of being infected a malignant contagious disease, is obliged to forbear all intercourse with the shore; hence, such restraint or inhibition of intercourse; also, the place where infected or prohibited vessels are stationed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarantine</value>
            <value column="1">The period of forty days during which the widow had the privilege of remaining in the mansion house of which her husband died seized.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarantine</value>
            <value column="1">To compel to remain at a distance, or in a given place, without intercourse, when suspected of having contagious disease; to put under, or in, quarantine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarantined</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarantine</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarantining</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarantine</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarl</value>
            <value column="1">A medusa, or jellyfish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">An arrow for a crossbow; -- so named because it commonly had a square head.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">Any small square or quadrangular member</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">A square of glass, esp. when set diagonally.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">A small opening in window tracery, of which the cusps, etc., make the form nearly square.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">A square or lozenge-shaped paving tile.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">A glazier's diamond.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">A four-sided cutting tool or chisel having a diamond-shaped end.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">A breach of concord, amity, or obligation; a falling out; a difference; a disagreement; an antagonism in opinion, feeling, or conduct; esp., an angry dispute, contest, or strife; a brawl; an altercation; as, he had a quarrel with his father about expenses.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">Ground of objection, dislike, difference, or hostility; cause of dispute or contest; occasion of altercation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">Earnest desire or longing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">To violate concord or agreement; to have a difference; to fall out; to be or become antagonistic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">To dispute angrily, or violently; to wrangle; to scold; to altercate; to contend; to fight.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">To find fault; to cavil; as, to quarrel with one's lot.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">To quarrel with.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">To compel by a quarrel; as, to quarrel a man out of his estate or rights.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrel</value>
            <value column="1">One who quarrels or wrangles; one who is quarrelsome.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarreled</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarrel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrelet</value>
            <value column="1">A little quarrel. See 1st Quarrel, 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarreling</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarrel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarreling</value>
            <value column="1">Engaged in a quarrel; apt or disposed to quarrel; as, quarreling factions; a quarreling mood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrelled</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarrel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrelling</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarrel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrellous</value>
            <value column="1">Quarrelsome.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrelsome</value>
            <value column="1">Apt or disposed to quarrel; given to brawls and contention; easily irritated or provoked to contest; irascible; choleric.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarried</value>
            <value column="1">Provided with prey.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarried</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarry</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrier</value>
            <value column="1">A worker in a stone quarry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarries</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarry</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarry</value>
            <value column="1">Same as 1st Quarrel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarry</value>
            <value column="1">Quadrate; square.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarry</value>
            <value column="1">A part of the entrails of the beast taken, given to the hounds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarry</value>
            <value column="1">A heap of game killed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarry</value>
            <value column="1">The object of the chase; the animal hunted for; game; especially, the game hunted with hawks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarry</value>
            <value column="1">To secure prey; to prey, as a vulture or harpy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarry</value>
            <value column="1">A place, cavern, or pit where stone is taken from the rock or ledge, or dug from the earth, for building or other purposes; a stone pit. See 5th Mine (a).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarry</value>
            <value column="1">To dig or take from a quarry; as, to quarry marble.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarry-faced</value>
            <value column="1">Having a face left as it comes from the quarry and not smoothed with the chisel or point; -- said of stones.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarry-man</value>
            <value column="1">A man who is engaged in quarrying stones; a quarrier.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrying</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarry</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarrymen</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarry-man</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quart</value>
            <value column="1">The fourth part; a quarter; hence, a region of the earth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quart</value>
            <value column="1">A measure of capacity, both in dry and in liquid measure; the fourth part of a gallon; the eighth part of a peck; two pints.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quart</value>
            <value column="1">A vessel or measure containing a quart.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quart</value>
            <value column="1">In cards, four successive cards of the same suit. Cf. Tierce, 4.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartan</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the fourth; occurring every fourth day, reckoning inclusively; as, a quartan ague, or fever.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartan</value>
            <value column="1">An intermittent fever which returns every fourth day, reckoning inclusively, that is, one in which the interval between paroxysms is two days.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartan</value>
            <value column="1">A measure, the fourth part of some other measure.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartane</value>
            <value column="1">Butane, each molecule of which has four carbon atoms.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartation</value>
            <value column="1">The act, process, or result (in the process of parting) of alloying a button of nearly pure gold with enough silver to reduce the fineness so as to allow acids to attack and remove all metals except the gold; -- called also inquartation. Compare Parting.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarte</value>
            <value column="1">A position in thrusting or parrying, with the inside of the hand turned upward and the point of the weapon toward the adversary's right breast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarte</value>
            <value column="1">Same as 2d Carte.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartene</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Butylene.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartenylic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or designating, an acid of the acrylic acid series, metameric with crotonic acid, and obtained as a colorless liquid; -- so called from having four carbon atoms in the molecule. Called also isocrotonic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">One of four equal parts into which anything is divided, or is regarded as divided; a fourth part or portion; as, a quarter of a dollar, of a pound, of a yard, of an hour, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">The fourth of a hundred-weight, being 25 or 28 pounds, according as the hundredweight is reckoned at 100 or 112 pounds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">The fourth of a ton in weight, or eight bushels of grain; as, a quarter of wheat; also, the fourth part of a chaldron of coal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">The fourth part of the moon's period, or monthly revolution; as, the first quarter after the change or full.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">One limb of a quadruped with the adjacent parts; one fourth part of the carcass of a slaughtered animal, including a leg; as, the fore quarters; the hind quarters.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">That part of a boot or shoe which forms the side, from the heel to the vamp.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">That part on either side of a horse's hoof between the toe and heel, being the side of the coffin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">A term of study in a seminary, college, etc, etc.; properly, a fourth part of the year, but often longer or shorter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">The encampment on one of the principal passages round a place besieged, to prevent relief and intercept convoys.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">The after-part of a vessel's side, generally corresponding in extent with the quarter-deck; also, the part of the yardarm outside of the slings.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">One of the divisions of an escutcheon when it is divided into four portions by a horizontal and a perpendicular line meeting in the fess point.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">A division of a town, city, or county; a particular district; a locality; as, the Latin quarter in Paris.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">A small upright timber post, used in partitions; -- in the United States more commonly called stud.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">The fourth part of the distance from one point of the compass to another, being the fourth part of 11ยก 15', that is, about 2ยก 49'; -- called also quarter point.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">Proper station; specific place; assigned position; special location.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">A station at which officers and men are posted in battle; -- usually in the plural.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">Place of lodging or temporary residence; shelter; entertainment; -- usually in the plural.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">A station or encampment occupied by troops; a place of lodging for soldiers or officers; as, winter quarters.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">Treatment shown by an enemy; mercy; especially, the act of sparing the life a conquered enemy; a refraining from pushing one's advantage to extremes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">Friendship; amity; concord.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">To lodge; to have a temporary residence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter</value>
            <value column="1">To drive a carriage so as to prevent the wheels from going into the ruts, or so that a rut shall be between the wheels.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter round</value>
            <value column="1">An ovolo.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarter-deck</value>
            <value column="1">That part of the upper deck abaft the mainmast, including the poop deck when there is one.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterage</value>
            <value column="1">A quarterly allowance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartered</value>
            <value column="1">of Quartter</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterfoil</value>
            <value column="1">An ornamental foliation having four lobes, or foils.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterhung</value>
            <value column="1">Having trunnions the axes of which lie below the bore; -- said of a cannon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartering</value>
            <value column="1">of Quartter</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartering</value>
            <value column="1">Coming from a point well abaft the beam, but not directly astern; -- said of waves or any moving object.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartering</value>
            <value column="1">At right angles, as the cranks of a locomotive, which are in planes forming a right angle with each other.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartering</value>
            <value column="1">A station.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartering</value>
            <value column="1">Assignment of quarters for soldiers; quarters.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartering</value>
            <value column="1">The division of a shield containing different coats of arms into four or more compartments.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartering</value>
            <value column="1">One of the different coats of arms arranged upon an escutcheon, denoting the descent of the bearer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartering</value>
            <value column="1">A series of quarters, or small upright posts. See Quarter, n., 1 (m) (Arch.)</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterlies</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarterly</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterly</value>
            <value column="1">Containing, or consisting of, a fourth part; as, quarterly seasons.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterly</value>
            <value column="1">Recurring during, or at the end of, each quarter; as, quarterly payments of rent; a quarterly meeting.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterly</value>
            <value column="1">A periodical work published once a quarter, or four times in a year.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterly</value>
            <value column="1">By quarters; once in a quarter of a year; as, the returns are made quarterly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterly</value>
            <value column="1">In quarters, or quarterings; as, to bear arms quarterly; in four or more parts; -- said of a shield thus divided by lines drawn through it at right angles.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartermaster</value>
            <value column="1">An officer whose duty is to provide quarters, provisions, storage, clothing, fuel, stationery, and transportation for a regiment or other body of troops, and superintend the supplies.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartermaster</value>
            <value column="1">A petty officer who attends to the helm, binnacle, signals, and the like, under the direction of the master.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartern</value>
            <value column="1">A quarter. Specifically: (a) The fourth part of a pint; a gill. (b) The fourth part of a peck, or of a stone (14 ibs.).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartern</value>
            <value column="1">A loaf of bread weighing about four pounds; -- called also quartern loaf.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarteron</value>
            <value column="1">A quarter; esp., a quarter of a pound, or a quarter of a hundred.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarteron</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quarteroon</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarteroon</value>
            <value column="1">A quadroon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterpace</value>
            <value column="1">A platform of a staircase where the stair turns at a right angle only. See Halfpace.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterstaff</value>
            <value column="1">A long and stout staff formerly used as a weapon of defense and offense; -- so called because in holding it one hand was placed in the middle, and the other between the middle and the end.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarterstaves</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarterstaff</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartet</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quartette</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartette</value>
            <value column="1">A composition in four parts, each performed by a single voice or instrument.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartette</value>
            <value column="1">The set of four person who perform a piece of music in four parts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartette</value>
            <value column="1">A stanza of four lines.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartic</value>
            <value column="1">Of the fourth degree.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartic</value>
            <value column="1">A quantic of the fourth degree. See Quantic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartic</value>
            <value column="1">A curve or surface whose equation is of the fourth degree in the variables.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartile</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Quadrate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartine</value>
            <value column="1">A supposed fourth integument of an ovule, counting from the outside.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarto</value>
            <value column="1">Having four leaves to the sheet; of the form or size of a quarto.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quarto</value>
            <value column="1">Originally, a book of the size of the fourth of sheet of printing paper; a size leaves; in present usage, a book of a square or nearly square form, and usually of large size.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartos</value>
            <value column="1">of Quarto</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartridge</value>
            <value column="1">Quarterage.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartter</value>
            <value column="1">To divide into four equal parts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartter</value>
            <value column="1">To divide; to separate into parts or regions.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartter</value>
            <value column="1">To furnish with shelter or entertainment; to supply with the means of living for a time; especially, to furnish shelter to; as, to quarter soldiers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartter</value>
            <value column="1">To furnish as a portion; to allot.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartter</value>
            <value column="1">To arrange (different coats of arms) upon one escutcheon, as when a man inherits from both father and mother the right to bear arms.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartz</value>
            <value column="1">A form of silica, or silicon dioxide (SiO2), occurring in hexagonal crystals, which are commonly colorless and transparent, but sometimes also yellow, brown, purple, green, and of other colors; also in cryptocrystalline massive forms varying in color and degree of transparency, being sometimes opaque.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartziferous</value>
            <value column="1">Consisting chiefly of quartz; containing quartz.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartzite</value>
            <value column="1">Massive quartz occurring as a rock; a metamorphosed sandstone; -- called also quartz rock.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartzoid</value>
            <value column="1">A form of crystal common with quartz, consisting of two six-sided pyramids, base to base.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartzose</value>
            <value column="1">Containing, or resembling, quartz; partaking of the nature or qualities of quartz.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quartzy</value>
            <value column="1">Quartzose.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quas</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of beer. Same as Quass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaschi</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quasje</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quash</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Squash.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quash</value>
            <value column="1">To abate, annul, overthrow, or make void; as, to quash an indictment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quash</value>
            <value column="1">To beat down, or beat in pieces; to dash forcibly; to crush.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quash</value>
            <value column="1">To crush; to subdue; to suppress or extinguish summarily and completely; as, to quash a rebellion.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quash</value>
            <value column="1">To be shaken, or dashed about, with noise.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quashed</value>
            <value column="1">of Quash</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quashee</value>
            <value column="1">A negro of the West Indies.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quashing</value>
            <value column="1">of Quash</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quasi</value>
            <value column="1">As if; as though; as it were; in a manner sense or degree; having some resemblance to; qualified; -- used as an adjective, or a prefix with a noun or an adjective; as, a quasi contract, an implied contract, an obligation which has arisen from some act, as if from a contract; a quasi corporation, a body that has some, but not all, of the peculiar attributes of a corporation; a quasi argument, that which resembles, or is used as, an argument; quasi historical, apparently historical, seeming to be historical.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quasimodo</value>
            <value column="1">The first Sunday after Easter; Low Sunday.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quasje</value>
            <value column="1">The brown coati. See Coati.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quass</value>
            <value column="1">A thin, sour beer, made by pouring warm water on rye or barley meal and letting it ferment, -- much used by the Russians.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quassation</value>
            <value column="1">The act of shaking, or the state of being shaken.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quassia</value>
            <value column="1">The wood of several tropical American trees of the order Simarubeae, as Quassia amara, Picraena excelsa, and Simaruba amara. It is intensely bitter, and is used in medicine and sometimes as a substitute for hops in making beer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quassin</value>
            <value column="1">The bitter principle of quassia, extracted as a white crystalline substance; -- formerly called quassite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quat</value>
            <value column="1">A pustule.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quat</value>
            <value column="1">An annoying, worthless person.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quat</value>
            <value column="1">To satiate; to satisfy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quata</value>
            <value column="1">The coaita.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quatch</value>
            <value column="1">Squat; flat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quater-cousin</value>
            <value column="1">A cousin within the first four degrees of kindred.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternary</value>
            <value column="1">Consisting of four; by fours, or in sets of four.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternary</value>
            <value column="1">Later than, or subsequent to, the Tertiary; Post-tertiary; as, the Quaternary age, or Age of man.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternary</value>
            <value column="1">The number four.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternary</value>
            <value column="1">The Quaternary age, era, or formation. See the Chart of Geology.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternate</value>
            <value column="1">Composed of, or arranged in, sets of four; quaternary; as, quaternate leaves.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternion</value>
            <value column="1">The number four.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternion</value>
            <value column="1">A set of four parts, things, or person; four things taken collectively; a group of four words, phrases, circumstances, facts, or the like.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternion</value>
            <value column="1">A word of four syllables; a quadrisyllable.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternion</value>
            <value column="1">The quotient of two vectors, or of two directed right lines in space, considered as depending on four geometrical elements, and as expressible by an algebraic symbol of quadrinomial form.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternion</value>
            <value column="1">To divide into quaternions, files, or companies.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternity</value>
            <value column="1">The number four.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaternity</value>
            <value column="1">The union of four in one, as of four persons; -- analogous to the theological term trinity.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quateron</value>
            <value column="1">See 2d Quarteron.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quatorzain</value>
            <value column="1">A poem of fourteen lines; a sonnet.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quatorze</value>
            <value column="1">The four aces, kings, queens, knaves, or tens, in the game of piquet; -- so called because quatorze counts as fourteen points.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quatrain</value>
            <value column="1">A stanza of four lines rhyming alternately.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quatre</value>
            <value column="1">A card, die. or domino, having four spots, or pips</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quatrefeuille</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quatrefoil</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quatrefoil</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Quarterfoil.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quatuor</value>
            <value column="1">A quartet; -- applied chiefly to instrumental compositions.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quave</value>
            <value column="1">See Quaver.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quave</value>
            <value column="1">To quaver.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quavemire</value>
            <value column="1">See Quagmire.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaver</value>
            <value column="1">To tremble; to vibrate; to shake.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaver</value>
            <value column="1">Especially, to shake the voice; to utter or form sound with rapid or tremulous vibrations, as in singing; also, to trill on a musical instrument</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaver</value>
            <value column="1">To utter with quavers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaver</value>
            <value column="1">A shake, or rapid and tremulous vibration, of the voice, or of an instrument of music.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaver</value>
            <value column="1">An eighth note. See Eighth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quavered</value>
            <value column="1">of Quaver</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quaverer</value>
            <value column="1">One who quavers; a warbler.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quavering</value>
            <value column="1">of Quaver</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quay</value>
            <value column="1">A mole, bank, or wharf, formed toward the sea, or at the side of a harbor, river, or other navigable water, for convenience in loading and unloading vessels.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quay</value>
            <value column="1">To furnish with quays.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quayage</value>
            <value column="1">Wharfage.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quayd</value>
            <value column="1">p. p. of Quail.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Que</value>
            <value column="1">A half farthing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queach</value>
            <value column="1">A thick, bushy plot; a thicket.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queach</value>
            <value column="1">To stir; to move. See Quick, v. i.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queachy</value>
            <value column="1">Yielding or trembling under the feet, as moist or boggy ground; shaking; moving.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queachy</value>
            <value column="1">Like a queach; thick; bushy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quean</value>
            <value column="1">A woman; a young or unmarried woman; a girl.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quean</value>
            <value column="1">A low woman; a wench; a slut.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queasily</value>
            <value column="1">In a queasy manner.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queasiness</value>
            <value column="1">The state of being queasy; nausea; qualmishness; squeamishness.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queasy</value>
            <value column="1">Sick at the stomach; affected with nausea; inclined to vomit; qualmish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queasy</value>
            <value column="1">Fastidious; squeamish; delicate; easily disturbed; unsettled; ticklish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quebec group</value>
            <value column="1">The middle of the three groups into which the rocks of the Canadian period have been divided in the American Lower Silurian system. See the Chart of Geology.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quebracho</value>
            <value column="1">A Chilian apocynaceous tree (Aspidosperma Quebracho); also, its bark, which is used as a febrifuge, and for dyspn/a of the lung, or bronchial diseases; -- called also white quebracho, to distinguish it from the red quebracho, a Mexican anacardiaceous tree (Loxopterygium Lorentzii) whose bark is said to have similar properties.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quebrith</value>
            <value column="1">Sulphur.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quech</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Queck</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queck</value>
            <value column="1">A word occurring in a corrupt passage of Bacon's Essays, and probably meaning, to stir, to move.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queen</value>
            <value column="1">The wife of a king.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queen</value>
            <value column="1">A woman who is the sovereign of a kingdom; a female monarch; as, Elizabeth, queen of England; Mary, queen of Scots.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queen</value>
            <value column="1">A woman eminent in power or attractions; the highest of her kind; as, a queen in society; -- also used figuratively of cities, countries, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queen</value>
            <value column="1">The fertile, or fully developed, female of social bees, ants, and termites.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queen</value>
            <value column="1">The most powerful, and except the king the most important, piece in a set of chessmen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queen</value>
            <value column="1">A playing card bearing the picture of a queen; as, the queen of spades.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queen</value>
            <value column="1">A male homosexual, esp. one who is effeminate or dresses in women's clothing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queen</value>
            <value column="1">To act the part of a queen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queen</value>
            <value column="1">To make a queen (or other piece, at the player's discretion) of by moving it to the eighth row; as, to queen a pawn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queen truss</value>
            <value column="1">A truss framed with queen-posts; a queen-post truss.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queencraft</value>
            <value column="1">Craft or skill in policy on the part of a queen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queendom</value>
            <value column="1">The dominion, condition, or character of a queen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queened</value>
            <value column="1">of Queen</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queenfish</value>
            <value column="1">A California sciaenoid food fish (Seriphys politus). The back is bluish, and the sides and belly bright silvery. Called also kingfish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queenhood</value>
            <value column="1">The state, personality, or character of a queen; queenliness.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queening</value>
            <value column="1">of Queen</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queening</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several kinds of apples, as summer queening, scarlet queening, and early queening. An apple called the queening was cultivated in England two hundred years ago.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queenliness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality of being queenly; the; characteristic of a queen; stateliness; eminence among women in attractions or power.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queenly</value>
            <value column="1">Like, becoming, or suitable to, a queen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queenship</value>
            <value column="1">The state, rank, or dignity of a queen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queensland nut</value>
            <value column="1">The nut of an Australian tree (Macadamia ternifolia). It is about an inch in diameter, and contains a single round edible seed, or sometimes two hemispherical seeds. So called from Queensland in Australia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queer</value>
            <value column="1">At variance with what is usual or normal; differing in some odd way from what is ordinary; odd; singular; strange; whimsical; as, a queer story or act.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queer</value>
            <value column="1">Mysterious; suspicious; questionable; as, a queer transaction.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queer</value>
            <value column="1">Counterfeit money.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queerish</value>
            <value column="1">Rather queer; somewhat singular.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queerly</value>
            <value column="1">In a queer or odd manner.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queerness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being queer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queest</value>
            <value column="1">The European ringdove (Columba palumbus); the cushat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quegh</value>
            <value column="1">A drinking vessel. See Quaich.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queint</value>
            <value column="1">See Quaint.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queint</value>
            <value column="1">imp. &amp; p. p. of Quench.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queintise</value>
            <value column="1">See Quaintise.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quell</value>
            <value column="1">To die.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quell</value>
            <value column="1">To be subdued or abated; to yield; to abate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quell</value>
            <value column="1">To take the life of; to kill.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quell</value>
            <value column="1">To overpower; to subdue; to put down.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quell</value>
            <value column="1">To quiet; to allay; to pacify; to cause to yield or cease; as, to quell grief; to quell the tumult of the soul.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quell</value>
            <value column="1">Murder.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quelled</value>
            <value column="1">of Quell</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queller</value>
            <value column="1">A killer; as, Jack the Giant Queller.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queller</value>
            <value column="1">One who quells; one who overpowers or subdues.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quelling</value>
            <value column="1">of Quell</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quellio</value>
            <value column="1">A ruff for the neck.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quelquechose</value>
            <value column="1">A trifle; a kickshaw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queme</value>
            <value column="1">To please.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quemeful</value>
            <value column="1">Kindly; merciful.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quench</value>
            <value column="1">To extinguish; to overwhelm; to make an end of; -- said of flame and fire, of things burning, and figuratively of sensations and emotions; as, to quench flame; to quench a candle; to quench thirst, love, hate, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quench</value>
            <value column="1">To cool suddenly, as heated steel, in tempering.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quench</value>
            <value column="1">To become extinguished; to go out; to become calm or cool.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quenchable</value>
            <value column="1">Capable of being quenched.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quenched</value>
            <value column="1">of Quench</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quencher</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, quenches.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quenching</value>
            <value column="1">of Quench</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quenchless</value>
            <value column="1">Incapable of being quenched; inextinguishable; as, quenchless fire or fury.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quenelle</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of delicate forcemeat, commonly poached and used as a dish by itself or for garnishing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quenouille training</value>
            <value column="1">A method of training trees or shrubs in the shape of a cone or distaff by tying down the branches and pruning.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quercitannic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or designating, a tannic acid found in oak bark and extracted as a yellowish brown amorphous substance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quercite</value>
            <value column="1">A white crystalline substance, C6H7(OH)5, found in acorns, the fruit of the oak (Quercus). It has a sweet taste, and is regarded as a pentacid alcohol.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quercitin</value>
            <value column="1">A yellow crystalline substance, occurring quite widely distributed in the vegetable kingdom, as is apple-tree bark, horse-chestnut leaves, etc., but originally obtained by the decomposition of quercitrin. Called also meletin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quercitrin</value>
            <value column="1">A glucoside extracted from the bark of the oak (Quercus) as a bitter citron-yellow crystalline substance, used as a pigment and called quercitron.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quercitron</value>
            <value column="1">The yellow inner bark of the Quercus tinctoria, the American black oak, yellow oak, dyer's oak, or quercitron oak, a large forest tree growing from Maine to eastern Texas.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quercitron</value>
            <value column="1">Quercitrin, used as a pigment. See Quercitrin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quercus</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of trees constituted by the oak. See Oak.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querele</value>
            <value column="1">A complaint to a court. See Audita Querela.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querent</value>
            <value column="1">A complainant; a plaintiff.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querent</value>
            <value column="1">An inquirer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queried</value>
            <value column="1">of Query</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queries</value>
            <value column="1">of Query</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querimony</value>
            <value column="1">A complaint or complaining.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querist</value>
            <value column="1">One who inquires, or asks questions.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querken</value>
            <value column="1">To stifle or choke.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querl</value>
            <value column="1">To twirl; to turn or wind round; to coil; as, to querl a cord, thread, or rope.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querl</value>
            <value column="1">A coil; a twirl; as, the qwerl of hair on the fore leg of a blooded horse.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quermonious</value>
            <value column="1">Complaining; querulous; apt to complain.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quern</value>
            <value column="1">A mill for grinding grain, the upper stone of which was turned by hand; -- used before the invention of windmills and watermills.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querpo</value>
            <value column="1">The inner or body garments taken together. See Cuerpo.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querquedule</value>
            <value column="1">A teal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querquedule</value>
            <value column="1">The pintail duck.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querry</value>
            <value column="1">A groom; an equerry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querulential</value>
            <value column="1">Querulous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querulous</value>
            <value column="1">Given to quarreling; quarrelsome.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querulous</value>
            <value column="1">Apt to find fault; habitually complaining; disposed to murmur; as, a querulous man or people.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querulous</value>
            <value column="1">Expressing complaint; fretful; whining; as, a querulous tone of voice.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Query</value>
            <value column="1">A question; an inquiry to be answered or solved.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Query</value>
            <value column="1">A question in the mind; a doubt; as, I have a query about his sincerity.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Query</value>
            <value column="1">An interrogation point [?] as the sign of a question or a doubt.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Query</value>
            <value column="1">To ask questions; to make inquiry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Query</value>
            <value column="1">To have a doubt; as, I query if he is right.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Query</value>
            <value column="1">To put questions about; to elicit by questioning; to inquire into; as, to query the items or the amount; to query the motive or the fact.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Query</value>
            <value column="1">To address questions to; to examine by questions.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Query</value>
            <value column="1">To doubt of; to regard with incredulity.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Query</value>
            <value column="1"><![CDATA[To write " query" (qu., qy., or ?) against, as a doubtful spelling, or sense, in a proof. See Quaere.]]></value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Querying</value>
            <value column="1">of Query</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quesal</value>
            <value column="1">The long-tailed, or resplendent, trogon (Pharomachus mocinno, formerly Trogon resplendens), native of Southern Mexico and Central America. Called also quetzal, and golden trogon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quest</value>
            <value column="1">The act of seeking, or looking after anything; attempt to find or obtain; search; pursuit; as, to rove in quest of game, of a lost child, of property, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quest</value>
            <value column="1">Request; desire; solicitation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quest</value>
            <value column="1">Those who make search or inquiry, taken collectively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quest</value>
            <value column="1">Inquest; jury of inquest.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quest</value>
            <value column="1">To search for; to examine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quest</value>
            <value column="1">To go on a quest; to make a search; to go in pursuit; to beg.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questant</value>
            <value column="1">One who undertakes a quest; a seeker.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quester</value>
            <value column="1">One who seeks; a seeker.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">The act of asking; interrogation; inquiry; as, to examine by question and answer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">Discussion; debate; hence, objection; dispute; doubt; as, the story is true beyond question; he obeyed without question.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">Examination with reference to a decisive result; investigation; specifically, a judicial or official investigation; also, examination under torture.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">That which is asked; inquiry; interrogatory; query.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">Hence, a subject of investigation, examination, or debate; theme of inquiry; matter to be inquired into; as, a delicate or doubtful question.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">Talk; conversation; speech; speech.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">To ask questions; to inquire.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">To argue; to converse; to dispute.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">To inquire of by asking questions; to examine by interrogatories; as, to question a witness.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">To doubt of; to be uncertain of; to query.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">To raise a question about; to call in question; to make objection to.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Question</value>
            <value column="1">To talk to; to converse with.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questionability</value>
            <value column="1">The state or condition of being questionable.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questionable</value>
            <value column="1">Admitting of being questioned; inviting, or seeming to invite, inquiry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questionable</value>
            <value column="1">Liable to question; subject to be doubted or called in question; problematical; doubtful; suspicious.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questionableness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being questionable, doubtful, or suspicious.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questionably</value>
            <value column="1">In a questionable manner.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questionary</value>
            <value column="1">Inquiring; asking questions; testing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questionary</value>
            <value column="1">One who makes it his business to seek after relics and carry them about for sale.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questioned</value>
            <value column="1">of Question</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questioner</value>
            <value column="1">One who asks questions; an inquirer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questioning</value>
            <value column="1">of Question</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questionist</value>
            <value column="1">A questioner; an inquirer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questionist</value>
            <value column="1">A candidate for honors or degrees who is near the time of his examination.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questionless</value>
            <value column="1">Unquestioning; incurious.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questionless</value>
            <value column="1">Beyond a question or doubt; doubtless; certainly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questman</value>
            <value column="1">One legally empowered to make quest of certain matters, esp. of abuses of weights and measures.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questman</value>
            <value column="1">A churchwarden's assistant; a sidesman.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questman</value>
            <value column="1">A collector of parish rents.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questmen</value>
            <value column="1">of Questman</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questmonger</value>
            <value column="1">One who lays informations, and encourages petty lawsuits.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questor</value>
            <value column="1">An officer who had the management of the public treasure; a receiver of taxes, tribute, etc.; treasurer of state.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questorship</value>
            <value column="1">The office, or the term of office, of a questor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questrist</value>
            <value column="1">A seeker; a pursuer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questuary</value>
            <value column="1">Studious of profit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Questuary</value>
            <value column="1">One employed to collect profits.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quet</value>
            <value column="1">The common guillemot.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queue</value>
            <value column="1">A tail-like appendage of hair; a pigtail.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queue</value>
            <value column="1">A line of persons waiting anywhere.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Queue</value>
            <value column="1">To fasten, as hair, in a queue.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quey</value>
            <value column="1">A heifer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qui vive</value>
            <value column="1"><![CDATA[The challenge of a French sentinel, or patrol; -- used like the English challenge: "Who comes there?"]]></value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quib</value>
            <value column="1">A quip; a gibe.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quibble</value>
            <value column="1">A shift or turn from the point in question; a trifling or evasive distinction; an evasion; a cavil.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quibble</value>
            <value column="1">A pun; a low conceit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quibble</value>
            <value column="1">To evade the point in question by artifice, play upon words, caviling, or by raising any insignificant or impertinent question or point; to trifle in argument or discourse; to equivocate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quibble</value>
            <value column="1">To pun; to practice punning.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quibbled</value>
            <value column="1">of Quibble</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quibbler</value>
            <value column="1">One who quibbles; a caviler; also, a punster.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quibbling</value>
            <value column="1">of Quibble</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quibblingly</value>
            <value column="1">Triflingly; evasively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quica</value>
            <value column="1">A small South American opossum (Didelphys quica), native of Guiana and Brazil. It feeds upon insects, small birds, and fruit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quice</value>
            <value column="1">See Queest.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quich</value>
            <value column="1">To stir.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">Alive; living; animate; -- opposed to dead or inanimate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">Characterized by life or liveliness; animated; sprightly; agile; brisk; ready.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">Speedy; hasty; swift; not slow; as, be quick.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">Impatient; passionate; hasty; eager; eager; sharp; unceremonious; as, a quick temper.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">Fresh; bracing; sharp; keen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">Sensitive; perceptive in a high degree; ready; as, a quick ear.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">Pregnant; with child.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">In a quick manner; quickly; promptly; rapidly; with haste; speedily; without delay; as, run quick; get back quick.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">That which is quick, or alive; a living animal or plant; especially, the hawthorn, or other plants used in making a living hedge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">The life; the mortal point; a vital part; a part susceptible of serious injury or keen feeling; the sensitive living flesh; the part of a finger or toe to which the nail is attached; the tender emotions; as, to cut a finger nail to the quick; to thrust a sword to the quick, to taunt one to the quick; -- used figuratively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">Quitch grass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick</value>
            <value column="1">To revive; to quicken; to be or become alive.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick-scented</value>
            <value column="1">Acute of smell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick-sighted</value>
            <value column="1">Having quick sight or acute discernment; quick to see or to discern.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick-witted</value>
            <value column="1">Having ready wit</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quick-wittedness</value>
            <value column="1">Readiness of wit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickbeam</value>
            <value column="1">See Quicken tree.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quicken</value>
            <value column="1">To make alive; to vivify; to revive or resuscitate, as from death or an inanimate state; hence, to excite; to, stimulate; to incite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quicken</value>
            <value column="1">To make lively, active, or sprightly; to impart additional energy to; to stimulate; to make quick or rapid; to hasten; to accelerate; as, to quicken one's steps or thoughts; to quicken one's departure or speed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quicken</value>
            <value column="1">To shorten the radius of (a curve); to make (a curve) sharper; as, to quicken the sheer, that is, to make its curve more pronounced.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quicken</value>
            <value column="1">To come to life; to become alive; to become vivified or enlivened; hence, to exhibit signs of life; to move, as the fetus in the womb.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quicken</value>
            <value column="1">To move with rapidity or activity; to become accelerated; as, his pulse quickened.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quicken tree</value>
            <value column="1">The European rowan tree; -- called also quickbeam, and quickenbeam. See Rowan tree.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickener</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, quickens.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickening</value>
            <value column="1">of Quicken</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickening</value>
            <value column="1">The act or process of making or of becoming quick.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickening</value>
            <value column="1">The first motion of the fetus in the womb felt by the mother, occurring usually about the middle of the term of pregnancy. It has been popularly supposed to be due to the fetus becoming possessed of independent life.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickens</value>
            <value column="1">Quitch grass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickhatch</value>
            <value column="1">The wolverine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quicklime</value>
            <value column="1">Calcium oxide; unslacked lime; -- so called because when wet it develops great heat. See 4th Lime, 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickly</value>
            <value column="1">Speedily; with haste or celerity; soon; without delay; quick.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickness</value>
            <value column="1">The condition or quality of being quick or living; life.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickness</value>
            <value column="1">Activity; briskness; especially, rapidity of motion; speed; celerity; as, quickness of wit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickness</value>
            <value column="1">Acuteness of perception; keen sensibility.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickness</value>
            <value column="1">Sharpness; pungency of taste.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quicksand</value>
            <value column="1">Sand easily moved or readily yielding to pressure; especially, a deep mass of loose or moving sand mixed with water, sometimes found at the mouth of a river or along some coasts, and very dangerous, from the difficulty of extricating a person who begins sinking into it.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickset</value>
            <value column="1">A living plant set to grow, esp. when set for a hedge; specifically, the hawthorn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickset</value>
            <value column="1">Made of quickset.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickset</value>
            <value column="1">To plant with living shrubs or trees for a hedge; as, to quickset a ditch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quicksilver</value>
            <value column="1">The metal mercury; -- so called from its resemblance to liquid silver.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quicksilvered</value>
            <value column="1">Overlaid with quicksilver, or with an amalgam of quicksilver and tinfoil.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quicksilvering</value>
            <value column="1">The mercury and foil on the back of a looking-glass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickstep</value>
            <value column="1">A lively, spirited march; also, a lively style of dancing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickwork</value>
            <value column="1">All the submerged section of a vessel's planking.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickwork</value>
            <value column="1">The planking between the spirketing and the clamps.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quickwork</value>
            <value column="1">The short planks between the portholes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quid</value>
            <value column="1">A portion suitable to be chewed; a cud; as, a quid of tobacco.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quid</value>
            <value column="1">To drop from the mouth, as food when partially chewed; -- said of horses.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quidam</value>
            <value column="1">Somebody; one unknown.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiddany</value>
            <value column="1">A confection of quinces, in consistency between a sirup and marmalade.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiddative</value>
            <value column="1">Constituting, or containing, the essence of a thing; quidditative.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiddit</value>
            <value column="1">A subtilty; an equivocation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quidditative</value>
            <value column="1">Quiddative.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiddities</value>
            <value column="1">of Quiddity</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiddity</value>
            <value column="1">The essence, nature, or distinctive peculiarity, of a thing; that which answers the question, Quid est? or, What is it?</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiddity</value>
            <value column="1">A trifling nicety; a cavil; a quibble.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiddle</value>
            <value column="1">To spend time in trifling employments, or to attend to useful subjects in an indifferent or superficial manner; to dawdle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiddle</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quiddler</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiddled</value>
            <value column="1">of Quiddle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiddler</value>
            <value column="1">One who wastes his energy about trifles.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiddling</value>
            <value column="1">of Quiddle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quidnunc</value>
            <value column="1">One who is curious to know everything that passes; one who knows, or pretends to know, all that is going on.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiesce</value>
            <value column="1">To be silent, as a letter; to have no sound.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiesced</value>
            <value column="1">of Quiesce</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiescence</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quiescency</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiescency</value>
            <value column="1">The state or quality of being quiescent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiescent</value>
            <value column="1">Being in a state of repose; at rest; still; not moving; as, a quiescent body or fluid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiescent</value>
            <value column="1">Not ruffed with passion; unagitated; not in action; not excited; quiet; dormant; resting.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiescent</value>
            <value column="1">Not sounded; silent; as, y is quiescent in &quot;day&quot; and &quot;say.&quot;</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiescent</value>
            <value column="1">A silent letter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiescently</value>
            <value column="1">In a quiescent manner.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiescing</value>
            <value column="1">of Quiesce</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiet</value>
            <value column="1">In a state of rest or calm; without stir, motion, or agitation; still; as, a quiet sea; quiet air.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiet</value>
            <value column="1">Free from noise or disturbance; hushed; still.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiet</value>
            <value column="1">Not excited or anxious; calm; peaceful; placid; settled; as, a quiet life; a quiet conscience.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiet</value>
            <value column="1">Not giving offense; not exciting disorder or trouble; not turbulent; gentle; mild; meek; contented.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiet</value>
            <value column="1">Not showy; not such as to attract attention; undemonstrative; as, a quiet dress; quiet colors; a quiet movement.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiet</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being quiet, or in repose; as an hour or a time of quiet.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiet</value>
            <value column="1">Freedom from disturbance, noise, or alarm; stillness; tranquillity; peace; security.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiet</value>
            <value column="1">To stop motion in; to still; to reduce to a state of rest, or of silence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiet</value>
            <value column="1">To calm; to appease; to pacify; to lull; to allay; to tranquillize; as, to quiet the passions; to quiet clamors or disorders; to quiet pain or grief.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiet</value>
            <value column="1">To become still, silent, or calm; -- often with down; as, be soon quieted down.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietage</value>
            <value column="1">Quietness.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quieted</value>
            <value column="1">of Quiet</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quieter</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, quiets.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quieting</value>
            <value column="1">of Quiet</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietism</value>
            <value column="1">Peace or tranquillity of mind; calmness; indifference; apathy; dispassion; indisturbance; inaction.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietism</value>
            <value column="1">The system of the Quietists, who maintained that religion consists in the withdrawal of the mind from worldly interests and anxieties and its constant employment in the passive contemplation of God and his attributes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietist</value>
            <value column="1">One of a sect of mystics originated in the seventeenth century by Molinos, a Spanish priest living in Rome. See Quietism.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietistic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the Quietists, or to Quietism.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietly</value>
            <value column="1">In a quiet state or manner; without motion; in a state of rest; as, to lie or sit quietly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietly</value>
            <value column="1">Without tumult, alarm, dispute, or disturbance; peaceably; as, to live quietly; to sleep quietly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietly</value>
            <value column="1">Calmly, without agitation or violent emotion; patiently; as, to submit quietly to unavoidable evils.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietly</value>
            <value column="1">Noiselessly; silently; without remark or violent movement; in a manner to attract little or no observation; as, he quietly left the room.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being quiet; freedom from noise, agitation, disturbance, or excitement; stillness; tranquillity; calmness.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietsome</value>
            <value column="1">Calm; still.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietude</value>
            <value column="1">Rest; repose; quiet; tranquillity.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quietus</value>
            <value column="1">Final discharge or acquittance, as from debt or obligation; that which silences claims; (Fig.) rest; death.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">One of the large feathers of a bird's wing, or one of the rectrices of the tail; also, the stock of such a feather.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">A pen for writing made by sharpening and splitting the point or nib of the stock of a feather; as, history is the proper subject of his quill.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">A spine of the hedgehog or porcupine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">The pen of a squid. See Pen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">The plectrum with which musicians strike the strings of certain instruments.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">The tube of a musical instrument.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">Something having the form of a quill</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">The fold or plain of a ruff.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">A spindle, or spool, as of reed or wood, upon which the thread for the woof is wound in a shuttle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">A hollow spindle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">To plaint in small cylindrical ridges, called quillings; as, to quill a ruffle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quill</value>
            <value column="1">To wind on a quill, as thread or yarn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quillaia bark</value>
            <value column="1">The bark of a rosaceous tree (Quillaja Saponaria), native of Chili. The bark is finely laminated, and very heavy with alkaline substances, and is used commonly by the Chilians instead of soap. Also called soap bark.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quillback</value>
            <value column="1">An American fresh-water fish (Ictiobus, / Carpiodes, cyprinus); -- called also carp sucker, sailfish, spearfish, and skimback.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilled</value>
            <value column="1">of Quill</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilled</value>
            <value column="1">Furnished with quills; also, shaped like quills.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quillet</value>
            <value column="1">Subtilty; nicety; quibble.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilling</value>
            <value column="1">of Quill</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilling</value>
            <value column="1">A band of linen, muslin, or the like, fluted, folded, or plaited so as somewhat to resemble a row of quills.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilling</value>
            <value column="1">One of the rounded plaits or flutings of such a band.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quillwort</value>
            <value column="1">Any plant or species of the genus Isoetes, cryptogamous plants with a cluster of elongated four-tubed rushlike leaves, rising from a corm, and containing spores in their enlarged and excavated bases. There are about seventeen American species, usually growing in the mud under still, shallow water. So called from the shape of the shape of the leaves.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilt</value>
            <value column="1">Anything that is quilted; esp., a quilted bed cover, or a skirt worn by women; any cover or garment made by putting wool, cotton, etc., between two cloths and stitching them together; also, any outer bed cover.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilt</value>
            <value column="1">To stitch or sew together at frequent intervals, in order to confine in place the several layers of cloth and wadding of which a garment, comforter, etc., may be made; as, to quilt a coat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilt</value>
            <value column="1">To wad, as a garment, with warm soft material.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilt</value>
            <value column="1">To stitch or sew in lines or patterns.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilted</value>
            <value column="1">of Quilt</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilter</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, quilts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilting</value>
            <value column="1">of Quilt</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilting</value>
            <value column="1">The act of stitching or running in patterns, as in making a quilt.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilting</value>
            <value column="1">A quilting bee. See Bee, 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilting</value>
            <value column="1">The material used for making quilts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quilting</value>
            <value column="1">A coating of strands of rope for a water vessel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quin</value>
            <value column="1">A European scallop (Pecten opercularis), used as food.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinaldine</value>
            <value column="1">A colorless liquid of a slightly pungent odor, C9H6N.CH3, first obtained as a condensation product of aldehyde and aniline, and regarded as a derivative of quinoline; -- called also methyl quinoline.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiname</value>
            <value column="1">Growing in sets of five; -- said especially of leaves composed of five leaflets set at the end of a common petiole.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinary</value>
            <value column="1">Consisting of five; arranged by fives.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinate</value>
            <value column="1">A salt of quinic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinazol</value>
            <value column="1">A complex nitrogenous base related to cinnoline.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quince</value>
            <value column="1">The fruit of a shrub (Cydonia vulgaris) belonging to the same tribe as the apple. It somewhat resembles an apple, but differs in having many seeds in each carpel. It has hard flesh of high flavor, but very acid, and is largely used for marmalade, jelly, and preserves.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quince</value>
            <value column="1">a quince tree or shrub.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quincewort</value>
            <value column="1">The squinancy. Called also quinsywort.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinch</value>
            <value column="1">To stir; to wince.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quincuncial</value>
            <value column="1">Having the form of a quincunx.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quincuncial</value>
            <value column="1">Having the leaves of a pentamerous calyx or corolla so imbricated that two are exterior, two are interior, and the other has one edge exterior and one interior; as, quincuncial aestivation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quincuncially</value>
            <value column="1">In the manner or order of a quincunx.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quincunx</value>
            <value column="1">An arrangement of things by fives in a square or a rectangle, one being placed at each corner and one in the middle; especially, such an arrangement of trees repeated indefinitely, so as to form a regular group with rows running in various directions.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quincunx</value>
            <value column="1">The position of planets when distant from each other five signs, or 150ยก.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quincunx</value>
            <value column="1">A quincuncial arrangement, as of the parts of a flower in aestivation. See Quincuncial, 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quindecagon</value>
            <value column="1">A plane figure with fifteen angles, and consequently fifteen sides.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quindecemvir</value>
            <value column="1">One of a sacerdotal college of fifteen men whose chief duty was to take care of the Sibylline books.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quindecemvirate</value>
            <value column="1">The body or office of the quindecemviri.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quindecemviri</value>
            <value column="1">of Quindecemvir</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quindecemvirs</value>
            <value column="1">of Quindecemvir</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quindecone</value>
            <value column="1">An unsaturated hydrocarbon, C15H26, of the valylene series, produced artificially as an oily liquid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quindecylic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or designating, an acid of the fatty acid series, containing fifteen atoms of carbon; called also pentadecylic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quindem</value>
            <value column="1">A fifteenth part.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quindism</value>
            <value column="1">A fifteenth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinhydrone</value>
            <value column="1">A green crystalline substance formed by the union of quinone with hydroquinone, or as an intermediate product in the oxidation of hydroquinone or the reduction of quinone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinia</value>
            <value column="1">Quinine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinible</value>
            <value column="1">An interval of a fifth; also, a part sung with such intervals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, derived from, or connected with, quinine and related compounds; specifically, designating a nonnitrogenous acid obtained from cinchona bark, coffee, beans, etc., as a white crystalline substance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinicine</value>
            <value column="1">An uncrystallizable alkaloid obtained by the action of heat from quinine, with which it is isomeric.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinidine</value>
            <value column="1">An alkaloid isomeric with, and resembling, quinine, found in certain species of cinchona, from which it is extracted as a bitter white crystalline substance; conchinine. It is used somewhat as a febrifuge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinine</value>
            <value column="1">An alkaloid extracted from the bark of several species of cinchona (esp. Cinchona Calisaya) as a bitter white crystalline substance, C20H24N2O2. Hence, by extension (Med.), any of the salts of this alkaloid, as the acetate, chloride, sulphate, etc., employed as a febrifuge or antiperiodic. Called also quinia, quinina, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quininic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or designating, a nitrogenous acid obtained as a yellow crystalline substance by the oxidation of quinine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quininism</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quinism</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinism</value>
            <value column="1">See Cinchonism.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinizarin</value>
            <value column="1">A yellow crystalline substance produced artificially. It is isomeric with alizarin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinizine</value>
            <value column="1">any one of a series of nitrogenous bases, certain of which are used as antipyretics.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinnat</value>
            <value column="1">The California salmon (Oncorhynchus choicha); -- called also chouicha, king salmon, chinnook salmon, and Sacramento salmon. It is of great commercial importance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinoa</value>
            <value column="1">The seeds of a kind of goosewort (Chenopodium Quinoa), used in Chili and Peru for making porridge or cakes; also, food thus made.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinogen</value>
            <value column="1">A hypothetical radical of quinine and related alkaloids.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinoidine</value>
            <value column="1">A brownish resinous substance obtained as a by-product in the treatment of cinchona bark. It consists of a mixture of several alkaloids.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinoline</value>
            <value column="1">A nitrogenous base, C9H7N obtained as a pungent colorless liquid by the distillation of alkaloids, bones, coal tar, etc. It the nucleus of many organic bodies, especially of certain alkaloids and related substances; hence, by extension, any one of the series of alkaloidal bases of which quinoline proper is the type.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinologist</value>
            <value column="1">One who is versed in quinology.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinology</value>
            <value column="1">The science which treats of the cultivation of the cinchona, and of its use in medicine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinone</value>
            <value column="1">A crystalline substance, C6H4O2 (called also benzoketone), first obtained by the oxidation of quinic acid and regarded as a double ketone; also, by extension, any one of the series of which quinone proper is the type.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinovic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or designating, a crystalline acid obtained from some varieties of cinchona bark.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinovin</value>
            <value column="1">An amorphous bitter glucoside derived from cinchona and other barks. Called also quinova bitter, and quinova.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinoxaline</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of a series of complex nitrogenous bases obtained by the union of certain aniline derivatives with glyoxal or with certain ketones.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinoxyl</value>
            <value column="1">The hypothetical radical of certain quinone derivatives related to rhodizonic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinoyl</value>
            <value column="1">A radical of which quinone is the hydride, analogous to phenyl.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquagesima</value>
            <value column="1">Fiftieth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquangular</value>
            <value column="1">Having five angles or corners.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquarticular</value>
            <value column="1">Relating to the five articles or points; as, the quinquarticular controversy between Arminians and Calvinists.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinque foliolate</value>
            <value column="1">Having five leaflets.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinque-</value>
            <value column="1">A combining form meaning five, five times, fivefold; as, quinquefid, five-cleft; quinquedentate, five-toothed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinqueangled</value>
            <value column="1">Having five angles; quinquangular.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquedentate</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quinquedentated</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquedentated</value>
            <value column="1">Five-toothed; as, a quinquedentate leaf.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquefarious</value>
            <value column="1">Arranged in five vertical rows; pentastichous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquefid</value>
            <value column="1">Sharply cut about halfway to the middle or base into five segments; as, a quinquefid leaf or corolla.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquefoliate</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quinquefoliated</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquefoliated</value>
            <value column="1">Having five leaves or leaflets.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinqueliteral</value>
            <value column="1">Consisting of five letters.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquelobared</value>
            <value column="1">Cut less than halfway into portions, usually somewhat rounded; five-lobed; as, a quinquelobate leaf or corolla.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquelobate</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quinquelobared</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquelobed</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Quinquelobate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquelocular</value>
            <value column="1">Having five cells or loculi; five-celled; as, a quinquelocular pericarp.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquenerved</value>
            <value column="1">Having five nerves; -- said of a leaf with five nearly equal nerves or ribs rising from the end of the petiole.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquennalia</value>
            <value column="1">Public games celebrated every five years.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquennial</value>
            <value column="1">Occurring once in five years, or at the end of every five years; also, lasting five years. A quinquennial event.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquennium</value>
            <value column="1">Space of five years.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquepartite</value>
            <value column="1">Consisting of five parts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquepartite</value>
            <value column="1">Divided into five parts almost to the base.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquereme</value>
            <value column="1">A galley having five benches or banks of oars; as, an Athenian quinquereme.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquesyllable</value>
            <value column="1">A word of five syllables.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquevalve</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quinquevalvular</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquevalvular</value>
            <value column="1">Having five valves, as a pericarp.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquevir</value>
            <value column="1">One of five commissioners appointed for some special object.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinqueviri</value>
            <value column="1">of Quinquevir</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquevirs</value>
            <value column="1">of Quinquevir</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquina</value>
            <value column="1">Peruvian bark.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinquivalent</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Pentavalent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinsy</value>
            <value column="1">An inflammation of the throat, or parts adjacent, especially of the fauces or tonsils, attended by considerable swelling, painful and impeded deglutition, and accompanied by inflammatory fever. It sometimes creates danger of suffocation; -- called also squinancy, and squinzey.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quint</value>
            <value column="1">A set or sequence of five, as in piquet.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quint</value>
            <value column="1">The interval of a fifth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintain</value>
            <value column="1">An object to be tilted at; -- called also quintel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintal</value>
            <value column="1">A hundredweight, either 112 or 100 pounds, according to the scale used. Cf. Cental.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintal</value>
            <value column="1">A metric measure of weight, being 100,000 grams, or 100 kilograms, equal to 220.46 pounds avoirdupois.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintan</value>
            <value column="1">Occurring as the fifth, after four others also, occurring every fifth day, reckoning inclusively; as, a quintan fever.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintan</value>
            <value column="1">An intermittent fever which returns every fifth day, reckoning inclusively, or in which the intermission lasts three days.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintel</value>
            <value column="1">See Quintain.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintessence</value>
            <value column="1">The fifth or last and highest essence or power in a natural body. See Ferment oils, under Ferment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintessence</value>
            <value column="1">Hence: An extract from anything, containing its rarest virtue, or most subtle and essential constituent in a small quantity; pure or concentrated essence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintessence</value>
            <value column="1">To distil or extract as a quintessence; to reduce to a quintessence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintessential</value>
            <value column="1">Of the nature of a quintessence; purest.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintet</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quintette</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintette</value>
            <value column="1">A composition for five voices or instruments; also, the set of five persons who sing or play five-part music.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintic</value>
            <value column="1">Of the fifth degree or order.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintic</value>
            <value column="1">A quantic of the fifth degree. See Quantic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintile</value>
            <value column="1">The aspect of planets when separated the fifth part of the zodiac, or 72ยก.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintilllion</value>
            <value column="1">According to the French notation, which is used on the Continent and in America, the cube of a million, or a unit with eighteen ciphers annexed; according to the English notation, a number produced by involving a million to the fifth power, or a unit with thirty ciphers annexed. See the Note under Numeration.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintin</value>
            <value column="1">See Quintain.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintine</value>
            <value column="1">The embryonic sac of an ovule, sometimes regarded as an innermost fifth integument. Cf. Quartine, and Tercine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintole</value>
            <value column="1">A group of five notes to be played or sung in the time of four of the same species.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintuple</value>
            <value column="1">Multiplied by five; increased to five times the amount; fivefold.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintuple</value>
            <value column="1">To make fivefold, or five times as much or many.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintuple-ribbed</value>
            <value column="1">The same as Quinquenerved.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintupled</value>
            <value column="1">of Quintuple</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quintupling</value>
            <value column="1">of Quintuple</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinzaine</value>
            <value column="1">The fifteenth day after a feast day, including both in the reckoning.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quinze</value>
            <value column="1">A game at cards in which the object is to make fifteen points.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quip</value>
            <value column="1">A smart, sarcastic turn or jest; a taunt; a severe retort; a gibe.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quip</value>
            <value column="1">To taunt; to treat with quips.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quip</value>
            <value column="1">To scoff; to use taunts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quipo</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Quipu.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quipped</value>
            <value column="1">of Quip</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quipping</value>
            <value column="1">of Quip</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quipu</value>
            <value column="1">A contrivance employed by the ancient Peruvians, Mexicans, etc., as a substitute for writing and figures, consisting of a main cord, from which hung at certain distances smaller cords of various colors, each having a special meaning, as silver, gold, corn, soldiers. etc. Single, double, and triple knots were tied in the smaller cords, representing definite numbers. It was chiefly used for arithmetical purposes, and to register important facts and events.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quipus</value>
            <value column="1">of Quipu</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirboilly</value>
            <value column="1">Leather softened by boiling so as to take any required shape. Upon drying, it becomes exceedingly hard, and hence was formerly used for armor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quire</value>
            <value column="1">See Choir.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quire</value>
            <value column="1">To sing in concert.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quire</value>
            <value column="1">A collection of twenty-four sheets of paper of the same size and quality, unfolded or having a single fold; one twentieth of a ream.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirister</value>
            <value column="1">A chorister. See Chorister.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiritation</value>
            <value column="1">A crying for help.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirite</value>
            <value column="1">One of the Quirites.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirites</value>
            <value column="1">Roman citizens.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirk</value>
            <value column="1">A sudden turn; a starting from the point or line; hence, an artful evasion or subterfuge; a shift; a quibble; as, the quirks of a pettifogger.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirk</value>
            <value column="1">A fit or turn; a short paroxysm; a caprice.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirk</value>
            <value column="1">A smart retort; a quibble; a shallow conceit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirk</value>
            <value column="1">An irregular air; as, light quirks of music.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirk</value>
            <value column="1">A piece of ground taken out of any regular ground plot or floor, so as to make a court, yard, etc.; -- sometimes written quink.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirk</value>
            <value column="1">A small channel, deeply recessed in proportion to its width, used to insulate and give relief to a convex rounded molding.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirked</value>
            <value column="1">Having, or formed with, a quirk or quirks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirkish</value>
            <value column="1">Consisting of quirks; resembling a quirk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirky</value>
            <value column="1">Full of quirks; tricky; as, a quirky lawyer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirl</value>
            <value column="1">See Querl.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirpele</value>
            <value column="1">The Indian ferret.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quirt</value>
            <value column="1">A rawhide whip plaited with two thongs of buffalo hide.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quish</value>
            <value column="1">See Cuish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quit</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of numerous species of small passerine birds native of tropical America. See Banana quit, under Banana, and Guitguit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quit</value>
            <value column="1">Released from obligation, charge, penalty, etc.; free; clear; absolved; acquitted.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quit</value>
            <value column="1">of Quit</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quit</value>
            <value column="1">To set at rest; to free, as from anything harmful or oppressive; to relieve; to clear; to liberate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quit</value>
            <value column="1">To release from obligation, accusation, penalty, or the like; to absolve; to acquit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quit</value>
            <value column="1">To discharge, as an obligation or duty; to meet and satisfy, as a claim or debt; to make payment for or of; to requite; to repay.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quit</value>
            <value column="1">To meet the claims upon, or expectations entertained of; to conduct; to acquit; -- used reflexively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quit</value>
            <value column="1">To carry through; to go through to the end.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quit</value>
            <value column="1">To have done with; to cease from; to stop; hence, to depart from; to leave; to forsake; as, to quit work; to quit the place; to quit jesting.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quit</value>
            <value column="1">To away; to depart; to stop doing a thing; to cease.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitch</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Quitch grass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitch</value>
            <value column="1">Figuratively: A vice; a taint; an evil.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitch grass</value>
            <value column="1">A perennial grass (Agropyrum repens) having long running rootstalks, by which it spreads rapidly and pertinaciously, and so becomes a troublesome weed. Also called couch grass, quick grass, quick grass, twitch grass. See Illustration in Appendix.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitclaim</value>
            <value column="1">A release or relinquishment of a claim; a deed of release; an instrument by which some right, title, interest, or claim, which one person has, or is supposed to have, in or to an estate held by himself or another, is released or relinquished, the grantor generally covenanting only against persons who claim under himself.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitclaim</value>
            <value column="1">To release or relinquish a claim to; to release a claim to by deed, without covenants of warranty against adverse and paramount titles.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitclaimed</value>
            <value column="1">of Quitclaim</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitclaiming</value>
            <value column="1">of Quitclaim</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quite</value>
            <value column="1">See Quit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quite</value>
            <value column="1">Completely; wholly; entirely; totally; perfectly; as, the work is not quite done; the object is quite accomplished; to be quite mistaken.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quite</value>
            <value column="1">To a great extent or degree; very; very much; considerably.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitly</value>
            <value column="1">Quite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitrent</value>
            <value column="1">A rent reserved in grants of land, by the payment of which the tenant is quit from other service.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quits</value>
            <value column="1">See the Note under Quit, a.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quittable</value>
            <value column="1">Capable of being quitted.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quittal</value>
            <value column="1">Return; requital; quittance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quittance</value>
            <value column="1">Discharge from a debt or an obligation; acquittance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quittance</value>
            <value column="1">Recompense; return; repayment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quittance</value>
            <value column="1">To repay; to requite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitted</value>
            <value column="1">of Quit</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitter</value>
            <value column="1">One who quits.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitter</value>
            <value column="1">A deliverer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitting</value>
            <value column="1">of Quit</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quittor</value>
            <value column="1">A chronic abscess, or fistula of the coronet, in a horse's foot, resulting from inflammation of the tissues investing the coffin bone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quittuple-nerved</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Quintuple-ribbed</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quitture</value>
            <value column="1">A discharge; an issue.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiver</value>
            <value column="1">Nimble; active.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiver</value>
            <value column="1">To shake or move with slight and tremulous motion; to tremble; to quake; to shudder; to shiver.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiver</value>
            <value column="1">The act or state of quivering; a tremor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiver</value>
            <value column="1">A case or sheath for arrows to be carried on the person.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quivered</value>
            <value column="1">of Quiver</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quivered</value>
            <value column="1">Furnished with, or carrying, a quiver.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quivered</value>
            <value column="1">Sheathed, as in a quiver.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quivering</value>
            <value column="1">of Quiver</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiveringly</value>
            <value column="1">With quivering motion.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quixotic</value>
            <value column="1">Like Don Quixote; romantic to extravagance; absurdly chivalric; apt to be deluded.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quixotically</value>
            <value column="1">In a quixotic way.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quixotism</value>
            <value column="1">That form of delusion which leads to extravagant and absurd undertakings or sacrifices in obedience to a morbidly romantic ideal of duty or honor, as illustrated by the exploits of Don Quixote in knight-errantry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quixotry</value>
            <value column="1">Quixotism; visionary schemes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiz</value>
            <value column="1">A riddle or obscure question; an enigma; a ridiculous hoax.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiz</value>
            <value column="1">One who quizzes others; as, he is a great quiz.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiz</value>
            <value column="1">An odd or absurd fellow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiz</value>
            <value column="1">An exercise, or a course of exercises, conducted as a coaching or as an examination.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiz</value>
            <value column="1">To puzzle; to banter; to chaff or mock with pretended seriousness of discourse; to make sport of, as by obscure questions.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiz</value>
            <value column="1">To peer at; to eye suspiciously or mockingly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiz</value>
            <value column="1">To instruct in or by a quiz. See Quiz, n., 4.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quiz</value>
            <value column="1">To conduct a quiz. See Quiz, n., 4.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quizzed</value>
            <value column="1">of Quiz</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quizzer</value>
            <value column="1">One who quizzes; a quiz.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quizzical</value>
            <value column="1">Relating to quizzing: given to quizzing; of the nature of a quiz; farcical; sportive.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quizzing</value>
            <value column="1">of Quiz</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quizzism</value>
            <value column="1">The act or habit of quizzing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quo warranto</value>
            <value column="1">A writ brought before a proper tribunal, to inquire by what warrant a person or a corporation acts, or exercises certain powers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quob</value>
            <value column="1">To throb; to quiver.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quod</value>
            <value column="1">A quadrangle or court, as of a prison; hence, a prison.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quod</value>
            <value column="1">Quoth; said. See Quoth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoddies</value>
            <value column="1">Herring taken and cured or smoked near Quoddy Head, Maine, or near the entrance of Passamaquoddy Ray.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quodlibet</value>
            <value column="1">A nice point; a subtilty; a debatable point.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quodlibet</value>
            <value column="1">A medley improvised by several performers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quodlibetarian</value>
            <value column="1">One who discusses any subject at pleasure.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quodlibetical</value>
            <value column="1">Not restricted to a particular subject; discussed for curiosity or entertainment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoif</value>
            <value column="1">See Coif.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoifffure</value>
            <value column="1">See Coiffure.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoil</value>
            <value column="1">See Coil.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoin</value>
            <value column="1">Originally, a solid exterior angle, as of a building; now, commonly, one of the selected pieces of material by which the corner is marked.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoin</value>
            <value column="1">A wedgelike piece of stone, wood metal, or other material, used for various purposes</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoin</value>
            <value column="1">to support and steady a stone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoin</value>
            <value column="1">To support the breech of a cannon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoin</value>
            <value column="1">To wedge or lock up a form within a chase.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoin</value>
            <value column="1">To prevent casks from rolling.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoit</value>
            <value column="1">A flattened ring-shaped piece of iron, to be pitched at a fixed object in play; hence, any heavy flat missile used for the same purpose, as a stone, piece of iron, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoit</value>
            <value column="1">A game played with quoits.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoit</value>
            <value column="1">The discus of the ancients. See Discus.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoit</value>
            <value column="1">A cromlech.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoit</value>
            <value column="1">To throw quoits; to play at quoits.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoit</value>
            <value column="1">To throw; to pitch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoke</value>
            <value column="1">imp. of Quake.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoll</value>
            <value column="1">A marsupial of Australia (Dasyurus macrurus), about the size of a cat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quondam</value>
            <value column="1">Having been formerly; former; sometime.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quondam</value>
            <value column="1">A person dismissed or ejected from a position.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quook</value>
            <value column="1">imp. of Quake.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quop</value>
            <value column="1">See Quob.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quorum</value>
            <value column="1">Such a number of the officers or members of any body as is competent by law or constitution to transact business; as, a quorum of the House of Representatives; a constitutional quorum was not present.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quota</value>
            <value column="1">A proportional part or share; the share or proportion assigned to each in a division.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotable</value>
            <value column="1">Capable or worthy of being quoted; as, a quotable writer; a quotable sentence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotation</value>
            <value column="1">The act of quoting or citing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotation</value>
            <value column="1">That which is quoted or cited; a part of a book or writing named, repeated, or adduced as evidence or illustration.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotation</value>
            <value column="1">The naming or publishing of the current price of stocks, bonds, or any commodity; also the price named.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotation</value>
            <value column="1">Quota; share.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotation</value>
            <value column="1">A piece of hollow type metal, lower than type, and measuring two or more pica ems in length and breadth, used in the blank spaces at the beginning and end of chapters, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotationist</value>
            <value column="1">One who makes, or is given to making, quotations.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quote</value>
            <value column="1">To cite, as a passage from some author; to name, repeat, or adduce, as a passage from an author or speaker, by way of authority or illustration; as, to quote a passage from Homer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quote</value>
            <value column="1">To cite a passage from; to name as the authority for a statement or an opinion; as, to quote Shakespeare.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quote</value>
            <value column="1">To name the current price of.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quote</value>
            <value column="1">To notice; to observe; to examine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quote</value>
            <value column="1">To set down, as in writing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quote</value>
            <value column="1">A note upon an author.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoted</value>
            <value column="1">of Quote</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoter</value>
            <value column="1">One who quotes the words of another.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoth</value>
            <value column="1">Said; spoke; uttered; -- used only in the first and third persons in the past tenses, and always followed by its nominative, the word or words said being the object; as, quoth I. quoth he.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotha</value>
            <value column="1">Indeed; forsooth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotidian</value>
            <value column="1">Occurring or returning daily; as, a quotidian fever.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotidian</value>
            <value column="1">Anything returning daily; especially (Med.), an intermittent fever or ague which returns every day.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotient</value>
            <value column="1">The number resulting from the division of one number by another, and showing how often a less number is contained in a greater; thus, the quotient of twelve divided by four is three.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotient</value>
            <value column="1">The result of any process inverse to multiplication. See the Note under Multiplication.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotiety</value>
            <value column="1">The relation of an object to number.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quoting</value>
            <value column="1">of Quote</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quotum</value>
            <value column="1">Part or proportion; quota.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Quran</value>
            <value column="1">See Koran. R () R, the eighteenth letter of the English alphabet, is a vocal consonant. It is sometimes called a semivowel, and a liquid. See Guide to Pronunciation, // 178, 179, and 250-254.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Qvacked</value>
            <value column="1">of Quack</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">quartzous</value>
            <value column="1">Quarzose.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">quickened</value>
            <value column="1">of Quicken</value>
         
</rows> 