
    <rows>
         
            <value column="0">Y</value>
            <value column="1">Something shaped like the letter Y; a forked piece resembling in form the letter Y.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Y</value>
            <value column="1">One of the forked holders for supporting the telescope of a leveling instrument, or the axis of a theodolite; a wye.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Y</value>
            <value column="1">A forked or bifurcated pipe fitting.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Y</value>
            <value column="1">A portion of track consisting of two diverging tracks connected by a cross track.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Y</value>
            <value column="1">I.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Y level</value>
            <value column="1">See under Y, n.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Y's</value>
            <value column="1">of Y</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Y-</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of I-</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Y-</value>
            <value column="1">A prefix of obscure meaning, originally used with verbs, adverbs, adjectives, nouns, and pronouns. In the Middle English period, it was little employed except with verbs, being chiefly used with past participles, though occasionally with the infinitive Ycleped, or yclept, is perhaps the only word not entirely obsolete which shows this use.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ya</value>
            <value column="1">Yea.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yacare</value>
            <value column="1">A South American crocodilian (Jacare sclerops) resembling the alligator in size and habits. The eye orbits are connected together, and surrounded by prominent bony ridges. Called also spectacled alligator, and spectacled cayman.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yacca</value>
            <value column="1">A West Indian name for two large timber trees (Podocarpus coriaceus, and P. Purdicanus) of the Yew family. The wood, which is much used, is pale brownish with darker streaks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yacht</value>
            <value column="1">A light and elegantly furnished vessel, used either for private parties of pleasure, or as a vessel of state to convey distinguished persons from one place to another; a seagoing vessel used only for pleasure trips, racing, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yacht</value>
            <value column="1">To manage a yacht; to voyage in a yacht.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yachter</value>
            <value column="1">One engaged in sailing a jacht.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yachting</value>
            <value column="1">Sailing for pleasure in a yacht.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yachtman</value>
            <value column="1">See Yachtsman.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yachtsman</value>
            <value column="1">One who owns or sails a yacht; a yachter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yachtsmen</value>
            <value column="1">of Yachtsman</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaf</value>
            <value column="1">Gave. See Give.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaffingale</value>
            <value column="1">The yaffle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaffle</value>
            <value column="1">The European green woodpecker (Picus, / Genius, viridis). It is noted for its loud laughlike note. Called also eccle, hewhole, highhoe, laughing bird, popinjay, rain bird, yaffil, yaffler, yaffingale, yappingale, yackel, and woodhack.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yager</value>
            <value column="1">In the German army, one belonging to a body of light infantry armed with rifles, resembling the chasseur of the French army.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaguarundi</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Jaguarondi.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yajur-Veda</value>
            <value column="1">See Veda.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yak</value>
            <value column="1">A bovine mammal (Poephagus grunnies) native of the high plains of Central Asia. Its neck, the outer side of its legs, and its flanks, are covered with long, flowing, fine hair. Its tail is long and bushy, often white, and is valued as an ornament and for other purposes in India and China. There are several domesticated varieties, some of which lack the mane and the long hair on the flanks. Called also chauri gua, grunting cow, grunting ox, sarlac, sarlik, and sarluc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yakamilk</value>
            <value column="1">See Trumpeter, 3 (a).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yakare</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Yacare.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yakin</value>
            <value column="1">A large Asiatic antelope (Budorcas taxicolor) native of the higher parts of the Himalayas and other lofty mountains. Its head and neck resemble those of the ox, and its tail is like that of the goat. Called also budorcas.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yakoots</value>
            <value column="1">(Ethnol.) A nomadic Mongolian tribe native of Northern Siberia, and supposed to be of Turkish stock. They are mainly pastoral in their habits.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaksha</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of demigod attendant on Kuvera, the god of wealth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yalah</value>
            <value column="1">The oil of the mahwa tree.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yam</value>
            <value column="1">A large, esculent, farinaceous tuber of various climbing plants of the genus Dioscorea; also, the plants themselves. Mostly natives of warm climates. The plants have netted-veined, petioled leaves, and pods with three broad wings. The commonest species is D. sativa, but several others are cultivated.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yama</value>
            <value column="1">The king of the infernal regions, corresponding to the Greek Pluto, and also the judge of departed souls. In later times he is more exclusively considered the dire judge of all, and the tormentor of the wicked. He is represented as of a green color, with red garments, having a crown on his head, his eyes inflamed, and sitting on a buffalo, with a club and noose in his hands.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yamma</value>
            <value column="1">The llama.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yamp</value>
            <value column="1">An umbelliferous plant (Carum Gairdneri); also, its small fleshy roots, which are eaten by the Indians from Idaho to California.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yang</value>
            <value column="1">The cry of the wild goose; a honk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yang</value>
            <value column="1">To make the cry of the wild goose.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yank</value>
            <value column="1">A jerk or twitch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yank</value>
            <value column="1">To twitch; to jerk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yank</value>
            <value column="1">An abbreviation of Yankee.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yanked</value>
            <value column="1">of Yank</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yankee</value>
            <value column="1">A nickname for a native or citizen of New England, especially one descended from old New England stock; by extension, an inhabitant of the Northern States as distinguished from a Southerner; also, applied sometimes by foreigners to any inhabitant of the United States.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yankee</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to a Yankee; characteristic of the Yankees.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yankee-Doodle</value>
            <value column="1">The name of a tune adopted popularly as one of the national airs of the United States.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yankee-Doodle</value>
            <value column="1">Humorously, a Yankee.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yankeeism</value>
            <value column="1">A Yankee idiom, word, custom, or the like.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yanking</value>
            <value column="1">of Yank</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaourt</value>
            <value column="1">A fermented drink, or milk beer, made by the Turks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yap</value>
            <value column="1">To bark; to yelp.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yap</value>
            <value column="1">A bark; a yelp.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yapock</value>
            <value column="1">A South American aquatic opossum (Chironectes variegatus) found in Guiana and Brazil. Its hind feet are webbed, and its fore feet do not have an opposable thumb for climbing. Called also water opossum.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yapon</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Yaupon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarage</value>
            <value column="1">The power of moving, or being managed, at sea; -- said with reference to a ship.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yard</value>
            <value column="1">A rod; a stick; a staff.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yard</value>
            <value column="1">A branch; a twig.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yard</value>
            <value column="1">A long piece of timber, as a rafter, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yard</value>
            <value column="1">A measure of length, equaling three feet, or thirty-six inches, being the standard of English and American measure.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yard</value>
            <value column="1">The penis.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yard</value>
            <value column="1">A long piece of timber, nearly cylindrical, tapering toward the ends, and designed to support and extend a square sail. A yard is usually hung by the center to the mast. See Illust. of Ship.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yard</value>
            <value column="1">An inclosure; usually, a small inclosed place in front of, or around, a house or barn; as, a courtyard; a cowyard; a barnyard.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yard</value>
            <value column="1">An inclosure within which any work or business is carried on; as, a dockyard; a shipyard.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yard</value>
            <value column="1">To confine (cattle) to the yard; to shut up, or keep, in a yard; as, to yard cows.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yardarm</value>
            <value column="1">Either half of a square-rigged vessel's yard, from the center or mast to the end.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yardful</value>
            <value column="1">As much as a yard will contain; enough to fill a yard.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yardfuls</value>
            <value column="1">of Yardful</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yardland</value>
            <value column="1">A measure of land of uncertain quantity, varying from fifteen to forty acres; a virgate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yardstick</value>
            <value column="1">A stick three feet, or a yard, in length, used as a measure of cloth, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yardwand</value>
            <value column="1">A yardstick.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yare</value>
            <value column="1">Ready; dexterous; eager; lively; quick to move.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yare</value>
            <value column="1">Soon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarely</value>
            <value column="1">In a yare manner.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yark</value>
            <value column="1">To yerk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarke</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Saki.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarn</value>
            <value column="1">Spun wool; woolen thread; also, thread of other material, as of cotton, flax, hemp, or silk; material spun and prepared for use in weaving, knitting, manufacturing sewing thread, or the like.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarn</value>
            <value column="1">One of the threads of which the strands of a rope are composed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarn</value>
            <value column="1">A story told by a sailor for the amusement of his companions; a story or tale; as, to spin a yarn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarnen</value>
            <value column="1">Made of yarn; consisting of yarn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarnut</value>
            <value column="1">See Yernut.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarr</value>
            <value column="1">To growl or snarl as a dog.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarrish</value>
            <value column="1">Having a rough, dry taste.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarrow</value>
            <value column="1">An American and European composite plant (Achillea Millefolium) with very finely dissected leaves and small white corymbed flowers. It has a strong, and somewhat aromatic, odor and taste, and is sometimes used in making beer, or is dried for smoking. Called also milfoil, and nosebleed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yarwhip</value>
            <value column="1">The European bar-tailed godwit; -- called also yardkeep, and yarwhelp. See Godwit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yataghan</value>
            <value column="1">A long knife, or short saber, common among Mohammedan nations, usually having a double curve, sometimes nearly straight.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yate</value>
            <value column="1">A gate. See 1st Gate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaud</value>
            <value column="1">See Yawd.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaul</value>
            <value column="1">See Yawl.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaulp</value>
            <value column="1">To yaup.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaup</value>
            <value column="1">To cry out like a child; to yelp.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaup</value>
            <value column="1">A cry of distress, rage, or the like, as the cry of a sickly bird, or of a child in pain.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaup</value>
            <value column="1">The blue titmouse.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yauper</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, yaups.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaupon</value>
            <value column="1">A shrub (Ilex Cassine) of the Holly family, native from Virginia to Florida. The smooth elliptical leaves are used as a substitute for tea, and were formerly used in preparing the black drink of the Indians of North Carolina. Called also South-Sea tea.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaw</value>
            <value column="1">To rise in blisters, breaking in white froth, as cane juice in the clarifiers in sugar works.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaw</value>
            <value column="1">To steer wild, or out of the line of her course; to deviate from her course, as when struck by a heavy sea; -- said of a ship.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaw</value>
            <value column="1">A movement of a vessel by which she temporarily alters her course; a deviation from a straight course in steering.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaw-weed</value>
            <value column="1">A low, shrubby, rubiaceous plant (Morinda Royoc) growing along the seacoast of the West Indies. It has small, white, odorous flowers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawd</value>
            <value column="1">A jade; an old horse or mare.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawed</value>
            <value column="1">of Yaw</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawing</value>
            <value column="1">of Yaw</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawl</value>
            <value column="1">A small ship's boat, usually rowed by four or six oars.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawl</value>
            <value column="1">To cry out like a dog or cat; to howl; to yell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawl-rigged</value>
            <value column="1">Having two masts with fore-and-aft sails, but differing from a schooner in that the after mast is very small, and stepped as far aft as possible. See Illustration in Appendix.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawn</value>
            <value column="1">To open the mouth involuntarily through drowsiness, dullness, or fatigue; to gape; to oscitate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawn</value>
            <value column="1">To open wide; to gape, as if to allow the entrance or exit of anything.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawn</value>
            <value column="1">To open the mouth, or to gape, through surprise or bewilderment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawn</value>
            <value column="1">To be eager; to desire to swallow anything; to express desire by yawning; as, to yawn for fat livings.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawn</value>
            <value column="1">An involuntary act, excited by drowsiness, etc., consisting of a deep and long inspiration following several successive attempts at inspiration, the mouth, fauces, etc., being wide open.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawn</value>
            <value column="1">The act of opening wide, or of gaping.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawn</value>
            <value column="1">A chasm, mouth, or passageway.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawned</value>
            <value column="1">of Yawn</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawning</value>
            <value column="1">of Yawn</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawningly</value>
            <value column="1">In a yawning manner.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yawp</value>
            <value column="1">See Yaup.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yaws</value>
            <value column="1">A disease, occurring in the Antilles and in Africa, characterized by yellowish or reddish tumors, of a contagious character, which, in shape and appearance, often resemble currants, strawberries, or raspberries. There are several varieties of this disease, variously known as framboesia, pian, verrugas, and crab-yaws.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ybe</value>
            <value column="1">Been.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ycleped</value>
            <value column="1">of Clepe</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ycleped</value>
            <value column="1">Called; named; -- obsolete, except in archaic or humorous writings.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ydo</value>
            <value column="1">Done.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ydrad</value>
            <value column="1">Dreaded.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ye</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Ye</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ye</value>
            <value column="1"><![CDATA[an old method of printing the article the (AS. /e), the "y" being used in place of the Anglo-Saxon thorn (/). It is sometimes incorrectly pronounced ye. See The, and Thorn, n., 4.]]></value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ye</value>
            <value column="1">An eye.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ye</value>
            <value column="1">The plural of the pronoun of the second person in the nominative case.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ye</value>
            <value column="1">Yea; yes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yea</value>
            <value column="1">Yes; ay; a word expressing assent, or an affirmative, or an affirmative answer to a question, now superseded by yes. See Yes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yea</value>
            <value column="1">More than this; not only so, but; -- used to mark the addition of a more specific or more emphatic clause. Cf. Nay, adv., 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yea</value>
            <value column="1">An affirmative vote; one who votes in the affirmative; as, a vote by yeas and nays.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yead</value>
            <value column="1">Properly, a variant of the defective imperfect yode, but sometimes mistaken for a present. See the Note under Yede.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yean</value>
            <value column="1">To bring forth young, as a goat or a sheep; to ean.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeaned</value>
            <value column="1">of Yean</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeaning</value>
            <value column="1">of Yean</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeanling</value>
            <value column="1">A lamb or a kid; an eanling.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Year</value>
            <value column="1">The time of the apparent revolution of the sun trough the ecliptic; the period occupied by the earth in making its revolution around the sun, called the astronomical year; also, a period more or less nearly agreeing with this, adopted by various nations as a measure of time, and called the civil year; as, the common lunar year of 354 days, still in use among the Mohammedans; the year of 360 days, etc. In common usage, the year consists of 365 days, and every fourth year (called bissextile, or leap year) of 366 days, a day being added to February on that year, on account of the excess above 365 days (see Bissextile).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Year</value>
            <value column="1">The time in which any planet completes a revolution about the sun; as, the year of Jupiter or of Saturn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Year</value>
            <value column="1">Age, or old age; as, a man in years.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeara</value>
            <value column="1">The California poison oak (Rhus diversiloba). See under Poison, a.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearbook</value>
            <value column="1">A book published yearly; any annual report or summary of the statistics or facts of a year, designed to be used as a reference book; as, the Congregational Yearbook.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearbook</value>
            <value column="1">A book containing annual reports of cases adjudged in the courts of England.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeared</value>
            <value column="1">Containing years; having existed or continued many years; aged.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearling</value>
            <value column="1">An animal one year old, or in the second year of its age; -- applied chiefly to cattle, sheep, and horses.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearling</value>
            <value column="1">Being a year old.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearly</value>
            <value column="1">Happening, accruing, or coming every year; annual; as, a yearly income; a yearly feast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearly</value>
            <value column="1">Lasting a year; as, a yearly plant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearly</value>
            <value column="1">Accomplished in a year; as, the yearly circuit, or revolution, of the earth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearly</value>
            <value column="1">Annually; once a year to year; as, blessings yearly bestowed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearn</value>
            <value column="1">To pain; to grieve; to vex.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearn</value>
            <value column="1">To be pained or distressed; to grieve; to mourn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearn</value>
            <value column="1">To curdle, as milk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearn</value>
            <value column="1">To be filled with longing desire; to be harassed or rendered uneasy with longing, or feeling the want of a thing; to strain with emotions of affection or tenderness; to long; to be eager.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearned</value>
            <value column="1">of Yearn</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearnful</value>
            <value column="1">Desirous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearning</value>
            <value column="1">of Yearn</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearningly</value>
            <value column="1">With yearning.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearnings</value>
            <value column="1">The maws, or stomachs, of young calves, used as a rennet for curdling milk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yearth</value>
            <value column="1">The earth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeast</value>
            <value column="1">The foam, or troth (top yeast), or the sediment (bottom yeast), of beer or other in fermentation, which contains the yeast plant or its spores, and under certain conditions produces fermentation in saccharine or farinaceous substances; a preparation used for raising dough for bread or cakes, and making it light and puffy; barm; ferment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeast</value>
            <value column="1">Spume, or foam, of water.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeast</value>
            <value column="1">A form of fungus which grows as indvidual rounded cells, rather than in a mycelium, and reproduces by budding; esp. members of the orders Endomycetales and Moniliales. Some fungi may grow both as a yeast or as a mycelium, depending on the conditions of growth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeast-bitten</value>
            <value column="1">A term used of beer when the froth of the yeast has reentered the body of the beer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeastiness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being yeasty, or frothy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeasty</value>
            <value column="1">Frothy; foamy; spumy, like yeast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yedding</value>
            <value column="1">The song of a minstrel; hence, any song.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yede</value>
            <value column="1">Went. See Yode.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeel</value>
            <value column="1">An eel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeldhall</value>
            <value column="1">Guildhall.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeldrin</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Yeldrine</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeldrine</value>
            <value column="1">The yellow-hammer; -- called also yeldrock, and yoldrin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yelk</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Yolk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yell</value>
            <value column="1">To cry out, or shriek, with a hideous noise; to cry or scream as with agony or horror.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yell</value>
            <value column="1">To utter or declare with a yell; to proclaim in a loud tone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yell</value>
            <value column="1">A sharp, loud, hideous outcry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yelled</value>
            <value column="1">of Yell</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yelling</value>
            <value column="1">of Yell</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellow</value>
            <value column="1">Being of a bright saffronlike color; of the color of gold or brass; having the hue of that part of the rainbow, or of the solar spectrum, which is between the orange and the green.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellow</value>
            <value column="1">A bright golden color, reflecting more light than any other except white; the color of that part of the spectrum which is between the orange and green.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellow</value>
            <value column="1">A yellow pigment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellow</value>
            <value column="1">To make yellow; to cause to have a yellow tinge or color; to dye yellow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellow</value>
            <value column="1">To become yellow or yellower.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellow-covered</value>
            <value column="1">Covered or bound in yellow paper.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellow-eyed</value>
            <value column="1">Having yellow eyes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellow-golds</value>
            <value column="1">A certain plant, probably the yellow oxeye.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowammer</value>
            <value column="1">See Yellow-hammer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowbill</value>
            <value column="1">The American scoter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowbird</value>
            <value column="1">The American goldfinch, or thistle bird. See Goldfinch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowbird</value>
            <value column="1">The common yellow warbler; -- called also summer yellowbird. See Illust. of Yellow warbler, under Yellow, a.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowed</value>
            <value column="1">of Yellow</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowfin</value>
            <value column="1">A large squeteague.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowfish</value>
            <value column="1">A rock trout (Pleurogrammus monopterygius) found on the coast of Alaska; -- called also striped fish, and Atka mackerel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowhammer</value>
            <value column="1">A common European finch (Emberiza citrinella). The color of the male is bright yellow on the breast, neck, and sides of the head, with the back yellow and brown, and the top of the head and the tail quills blackish. Called also yellow bunting, scribbling lark, and writing lark.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowhammer</value>
            <value column="1">The flicker.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowing</value>
            <value column="1">of Yellow</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowing</value>
            <value column="1">The act or process of making yellow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowish</value>
            <value column="1">Somewhat yellow; as, amber is of a yellowish color.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowlegs</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several species of long-legged sandpipers of the genus Totanus, in which the legs are bright yellow; -- called also stone snipe, tattler, telltale, yellowshanks; and yellowshins. See Tattler, 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being yellow; as, the yellowness of an orange.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowness</value>
            <value column="1">Jealousy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowroot</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several plants with yellow roots.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowroot</value>
            <value column="1">See Xanthorhiza.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowroot</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Orangeroot.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellows</value>
            <value column="1">A disease of the bile in horses, cattle, and sheep, causing yellowness of the eyes; jaundice.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellows</value>
            <value column="1">A disease of plants, esp. of peach trees, in which the leaves turn to a yellowish color; jeterus.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellows</value>
            <value column="1">A group of butterflies in which the predominating color is yellow. It includes the common small yellow butterflies. Called also redhorns, and sulphurs. See Sulphur.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowseed</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of pepper grass (Lepidium campestre).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowshanks</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Yellowshins</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowshins</value>
            <value column="1">See Yellolegs.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowtail</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several species of marine carangoid fishes of the genus Seriola; especially, the large California species (S. dorsalis) which sometimes weighs thirty or forty pounds, and is highly esteemed as a food fish; -- called also cavasina, and white salmon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowtail</value>
            <value column="1">The mademoiselle, or silver perch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowtail</value>
            <value column="1">The menhaden.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowtail</value>
            <value column="1">The runner, 12.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowtail</value>
            <value column="1">A California rockfish (Sebastodes flavidus).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowtail</value>
            <value column="1">The sailor's choice (Diplodus rhomboides).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowthroat</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several species of American ground warblers of the genus Geothlypis, esp. the Maryland yellowthroat (G. trichas), which is a very common species.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowtop</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of grass, perhaps a species of Agrostis.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowwood</value>
            <value column="1">The wood of any one of several different kinds of trees; also, any one of the trees themselves. Among the trees so called are the Cladrastis tinctoria, an American leguminous tree; the several species of prickly ash (Xanthoxylum); the Australian Flindersia Oxleyana, a tree related to the mahogany; certain South African species of Podocarpus, trees related to the yew; the East Indian Podocarpus latifolia; and the true satinwood (Chloroxylon Swietenia). All these Old World trees furnish valuable timber.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yellowwort</value>
            <value column="1">A European yellow-flowered, gentianaceous (Chlora perfoliata). The whole plant is intensely bitter, and is sometimes used as a tonic, and also in dyeing yellow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yelp</value>
            <value column="1">To boast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yelp</value>
            <value column="1">To utter a sharp, quick cry, as a hound; to bark shrilly with eagerness, pain, or fear; to yaup.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yelp</value>
            <value column="1">A sharp, quick cry; a bark.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yelped</value>
            <value column="1">of Yelp</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yelper</value>
            <value column="1">An animal that yelps, or makes a yelping noise.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yelper</value>
            <value column="1">The avocet; -- so called from its sharp, shrill cry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yelper</value>
            <value column="1">The tattler.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yelping</value>
            <value column="1">of Yelp</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeman</value>
            <value column="1">A yeoman.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yen</value>
            <value column="1">of Ye</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yen</value>
            <value column="1">The unit of value and account in Japan. Since Japan's adoption of the gold standard, in 1897, the value of the yen has been about 50 cents. The yen is equal to 100 sen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yend</value>
            <value column="1">To throw; to cast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yenite</value>
            <value column="1">A silicate of iron and lime occurring in black prismatic crystals; -- also called ilvaite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeoman</value>
            <value column="1">A common man, or one of the commonly of the first or most respectable class; a freeholder; a man free born.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeoman</value>
            <value column="1">A servant; a retainer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeoman</value>
            <value column="1">A yeoman of the guard; also, a member of the yeomanry cavalry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeoman</value>
            <value column="1">An interior officer under the boatswain, gunner, or carpenters, charged with the stowage, account, and distribution of the stores.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeomanlike</value>
            <value column="1">Resembling, or suitable to, a yeoman; yeomanly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeomanly</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to a yeoman; becoming or suitable to, a yeoman; yeomanlike.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeomanry</value>
            <value column="1">The position or rank of a yeoman.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeomanry</value>
            <value column="1">The collective body of yeomen, or freeholders.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeomanry</value>
            <value column="1">The yeomanry cavalry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeomen</value>
            <value column="1">of Yeoman</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeorling</value>
            <value column="1">The European yellow-hammer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yer</value>
            <value column="1">Ere; before.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yerba</value>
            <value column="1">An herb; a plant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yerd</value>
            <value column="1">See 1st &amp; 2d Yard.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yerk</value>
            <value column="1">To throw or thrust with a sudden, smart movement; to kick or strike suddenly; to jerk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yerk</value>
            <value column="1">To strike or lash with a whip.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yerk</value>
            <value column="1">To throw out the heels; to kick; to jerk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yerk</value>
            <value column="1">To move a quick, jerking motion.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yerk</value>
            <value column="1">A sudden or quick thrust or motion; a jerk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yerked</value>
            <value column="1">of Yerk</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yerking</value>
            <value column="1">of Yerk</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yern</value>
            <value column="1">See 3d Yearn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yern</value>
            <value column="1">Eager; brisk; quick; active.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yerne</value>
            <value column="1">Eagerly; briskly; quickly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yernut</value>
            <value column="1">An earthnut, or groundnut. See Groundnut (d).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yerst</value>
            <value column="1">See Erst.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yes</value>
            <value column="1">Ay; yea; -- a word which expresses affirmation or consent; -- opposed to no.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yest</value>
            <value column="1">See Yeast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yester</value>
            <value column="1">Last; last past; next before; of or pertaining to yesterday.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yester-evening</value>
            <value column="1">The evening of yesterday; the evening last past.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yester-morning</value>
            <value column="1">The morning of yesterday.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yesterday</value>
            <value column="1">The day last past; the day next before the present.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yesterday</value>
            <value column="1">Fig.: A recent time; time not long past.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yesterday</value>
            <value column="1">On the day last past; on the day preceding to-day; as, the affair took place yesterday.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yestereve</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Yester-evening</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yestermorn</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Yester-morning</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yestern</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to yesterday; relating to the day last past.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yesternight</value>
            <value column="1">The last night; the night last past.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yesternight</value>
            <value column="1">On the last night.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yesternoon</value>
            <value column="1">The noon of yesterday; the noon last past.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yesterweek</value>
            <value column="1">The week last past; last week.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yesteryear</value>
            <value column="1">The year last past; last year.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yestreen</value>
            <value column="1">Yester-evening; yesternight; last night.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yesty</value>
            <value column="1">See Yeasty.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yet</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several species of large marine gastropods belonging to the genus Yetus, or Cymba; a boat shell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yet</value>
            <value column="1">In addition; further; besides; over and above; still.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yet</value>
            <value column="1">At the same time; by continuance from a former state; still.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yet</value>
            <value column="1">Up to the present time; thus far; hitherto; until now; -- and with the negative, not yet, not up to the present time; not as soon as now; as, Is it time to go? Not yet. See As yet, under As, conj.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yet</value>
            <value column="1">Before some future time; before the end; eventually; in time.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yet</value>
            <value column="1">Even; -- used emphatically.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yet</value>
            <value column="1">Nevertheless; notwithstanding; however.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeve</value>
            <value column="1">To give.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yeven</value>
            <value column="1">Given.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yew</value>
            <value column="1">See Yaw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yew</value>
            <value column="1">An evergreen tree (Taxus baccata) of Europe, allied to the pines, but having a peculiar berrylike fruit instead of a cone. It frequently grows in British churchyards.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yew</value>
            <value column="1">The wood of the yew. It is light red in color, compact, fine-grained, and very elastic. It is preferred to all other kinds of wood for bows and whipstocks, the best for these purposes coming from Spain.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yew</value>
            <value column="1">A bow for shooting, made of the yew.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yew</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to yew trees; made of the wood of a yew tree; as, a yew whipstock.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yewen</value>
            <value column="1">Made of yew; as, yewen bows.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yex</value>
            <value column="1">To hiccough.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yex</value>
            <value column="1">A hiccough.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yezdegerdian</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to Yezdegerd, the last Sassanian monarch of Persia, who was overthrown by the Mohammedans; as, the Yezdegerdian era, which began on the 16th of June, a. d. 632. The era is still used by the Parsees.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yezdi</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Izedi.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yezidee</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Yezidi</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yezidi</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Izedi.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yfere</value>
            <value column="1">Together. See Ifere.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ygdrasyl</value>
            <value column="1">See in the Dictionary of Noted Names in Fiction.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yghe</value>
            <value column="1">Eye.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ygo</value>
            <value column="1">Gone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yground</value>
            <value column="1">p. p. of Grind.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yholde</value>
            <value column="1">p. p. of Hold.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yield</value>
            <value column="1">To give in return for labor expended; to produce, as payment or interest on what is expended or invested; to pay; as, money at interest yields six or seven per cent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yield</value>
            <value column="1">To furnish; to afford; to render; to give forth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yield</value>
            <value column="1">To give up, as something that is claimed or demanded; to make over to one who has a claim or right; to resign; to surrender; to relinquish; as a city, an opinion, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yield</value>
            <value column="1">To admit to be true; to concede; to allow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yield</value>
            <value column="1">To permit; to grant; as, to yield passage.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yield</value>
            <value column="1">To give a reward to; to bless.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yield</value>
            <value column="1">To give up the contest; to submit; to surrender; to succumb.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yield</value>
            <value column="1">To comply with; to assent; as, I yielded to his request.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yield</value>
            <value column="1">To give way; to cease opposition; to be no longer a hindrance or an obstacle; as, men readily yield to the current of opinion, or to customs; the door yielded.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yield</value>
            <value column="1">To give place, as inferior in rank or excellence; as, they will yield to us in nothing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yield</value>
            <value column="1">Amount yielded; product; -- applied especially to products resulting from growth or cultivation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yieldable</value>
            <value column="1">Disposed to yield or comply.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yieldance</value>
            <value column="1">The act of producing; yield; as, the yieldance of the earth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yieldance</value>
            <value column="1">The act of yielding; concession.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yielded</value>
            <value column="1">of Yield</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yielder</value>
            <value column="1">One who yields.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yielding</value>
            <value column="1">of Yield</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yielding</value>
            <value column="1">Inclined to give way, or comply; flexible; compliant; accommodating; as, a yielding temper.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yieldless</value>
            <value column="1">Without yielding; unyielding.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yift</value>
            <value column="1">Gift.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yin</value>
            <value column="1">A Chinese weight of 2/ pounds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yis</value>
            <value column="1">Yes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yit</value>
            <value column="1">Yet.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yite</value>
            <value column="1">The European yellow-hammer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yive</value>
            <value column="1">To give.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yle</value>
            <value column="1">Isle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yliche</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Ylike</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ylike</value>
            <value column="1">Like; alike.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yllanraton</value>
            <value column="1">The agouara.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ymaked</value>
            <value column="1">Made.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ymel</value>
            <value column="1">Among.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ynambu</value>
            <value column="1">A South American tinamou (Rhynchotus rufescens); -- called also perdiz grande, and rufous tinamou. See Illust. of Tinamou.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ynough</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Ynow</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ynow</value>
            <value column="1">Enough.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yockel</value>
            <value column="1">The yaffle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yode</value>
            <value column="1">Went; walked; proceeded.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yodel</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Yodle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yodel</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Yodle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yodeled</value>
            <value column="1">of Yodle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yodeling</value>
            <value column="1">of Yodle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yodle</value>
            <value column="1">To sing in a manner common among the Swiss and Tyrolese mountaineers, by suddenly changing from the head voice, or falsetto, to the chest voice, and the contrary; to warble.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yodle</value>
            <value column="1">A song sung by yodeling, as by the Swiss mountaineers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yodled</value>
            <value column="1">of Yodle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yodler</value>
            <value column="1">One who yodels.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yodling</value>
            <value column="1">of Yodle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoga</value>
            <value column="1">A species of asceticism among the Hindoos, which consists in a complete abstraction from all worldly objects, by which the votary expects to obtain union with the universal spirit, and to acquire superhuman faculties.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yogi</value>
            <value column="1">A follower of the yoga philosophy; an ascetic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoicks</value>
            <value column="1">A cry of encouragement to foxhounds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoit</value>
            <value column="1">The European yellow-hammer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yojan</value>
            <value column="1">A measure of distance, varying from four to ten miles, but usually about five.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">A bar or frame of wood by which two oxen are joined at the heads or necks for working together.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">A frame or piece resembling a yoke, as in use or shape.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">A frame of wood fitted to a person's shoulders for carrying pails, etc., suspended on each side; as, a milkmaid's yoke.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">A frame worn on the neck of an animal, as a cow, a pig, a goose, to prevent passage through a fence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">A frame or convex piece by which a bell is hung for ringing it. See Illust. of Bell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">A crosspiece upon the head of a boat's rudder. To its ends lines are attached which lead forward so that the boat can be steered from amidships.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">A bent crosspiece connecting two other parts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">A tie securing two timbers together, not used for part of a regular truss, but serving a temporary purpose, as to provide against unusual strain.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">A band shaped to fit the shoulders or the hips, and joined to the upper full edge of the waist or the skirt.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">Fig.: That which connects or binds; a chain; a link; a bond connection.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">A mark of servitude; hence, servitude; slavery; bondage; service.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">Two animals yoked together; a couple; a pair that work together.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">The quantity of land plowed in a day by a yoke of oxen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">A portion of the working day; as, to work two yokes, that is, to work both portions of the day, or morning and afternoon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">To put a yoke on; to join in or with a yoke; as, to yoke oxen, or pair of oxen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">To couple; to join with another.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">To enslave; to bring into bondage; to restrain; to confine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke</value>
            <value column="1">To be joined or associated; to be intimately connected; to consort closely; to mate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoke-toed</value>
            <value column="1">Having two toes in front and two behind, as the trogons and woodpeckers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yokeage</value>
            <value column="1">See Rokeage.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoked</value>
            <value column="1">of Yoke</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yokefellow</value>
            <value column="1">An associate or companion in, or as in; a mate; a fellow; especially, a partner in marriage.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yokel</value>
            <value column="1">A country bumpkin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yokelet</value>
            <value column="1">A small farm; -- so called as requiring but one yoke of oxen to till it.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yokemate</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Yokefellow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoking</value>
            <value column="1">of Yoke</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yold</value>
            <value column="1">of Yield</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yold</value>
            <value column="1">Yielded.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yolden</value>
            <value column="1">Yielded.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yolk</value>
            <value column="1">The yellow part of an egg; the vitellus.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yolk</value>
            <value column="1">An oily secretion which naturally covers the wool of sheep.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoll</value>
            <value column="1">To yell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yon</value>
            <value column="1">At a distance, but within view; yonder.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yon</value>
            <value column="1">Yonder.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoncopin</value>
            <value column="1">A local name in parts of the Mississippi Valley for the American lotus (Nelumbo lutea).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yond</value>
            <value column="1">Furious; mad; angry; fierce.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yond</value>
            <value column="1">Yonder.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yonder</value>
            <value column="1">At a distance, but within view.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yonder</value>
            <value column="1">Being at a distance within view, or conceived of as within view; that or those there; yon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yoni</value>
            <value column="1">The symbol under which Sakti, or the personification of the female power in nature, is worshiped. Cf. Lingam.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yonker</value>
            <value column="1">A young fellow; a younker.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yore</value>
            <value column="1">In time long past; in old time; long since.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">York use</value>
            <value column="1">The one of the three printed uses of England which was followed in the north. It was based on the Sarum use. See Use, n., 6.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yorker</value>
            <value column="1">A tice.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yorkshire</value>
            <value column="1">A county in the north of England.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yot</value>
            <value column="1">To unite closely.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yote</value>
            <value column="1">To pour water on; to soak in, or mix with, water.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">You</value>
            <value column="1">The pronoun of the second person, in the nominative, dative, and objective case, indicating the person or persons addressed. See the Note under Ye.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youl</value>
            <value column="1">To yell; to yowl.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Young</value>
            <value column="1">Not long born; still in the first part of life; not yet arrived at adolescence, maturity, or age; not old; juvenile; -- said of animals; as, a young child; a young man; a young fawn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Young</value>
            <value column="1">Being in the first part, pr period, of growth; as, a young plant; a young tree.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Young</value>
            <value column="1">Having little experience; inexperienced; unpracticed; ignorant; weak.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Young</value>
            <value column="1">The offspring of animals, either a single animal or offspring collectively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youngger</value>
            <value column="1">One who is younger; an inferior in age; a junior.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youngish</value>
            <value column="1">Somewhat young.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youngling</value>
            <value column="1">A young person; a youth; also, any animal in its early life.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youngling</value>
            <value column="1">Young; youthful.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youngly</value>
            <value column="1">Like a young person or thing; young; youthful.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youngly</value>
            <value column="1">In a young manner; in the period of youth; early in life.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youngly</value>
            <value column="1">Ignorantly; weakly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youngness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being young.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youngster</value>
            <value column="1">A young person; a youngling; a lad.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youngth</value>
            <value column="1">Youth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youngthly</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or resembling, youth; youthful.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Younker</value>
            <value column="1">A young person; a stripling; a yonker.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youpon</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Yaupon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Your</value>
            <value column="1">The form of the possessive case of the personal pronoun you.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yours</value>
            <value column="1">See the Note under Your.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yourself</value>
            <value column="1">An emphasized or reflexive form of the pronoun of the second person; -- used as a subject commonly with you; as, you yourself shall see it; also, alone in the predicate, either in the nominative or objective case; as, you have injured yourself.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yourselves</value>
            <value column="1">of Yourself</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youth</value>
            <value column="1">of Youth</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youth</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being young; youthfulness; juvenility.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youth</value>
            <value column="1">The part of life that succeeds to childhood; the period of existence preceding maturity or age; the whole early part of life, from childhood, or, sometimes, from infancy, to manhood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youth</value>
            <value column="1">A young person; especially, a young man.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youth</value>
            <value column="1">Young persons, collectively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youthful</value>
            <value column="1">Not yet mature or aged; young.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youthful</value>
            <value column="1">Also used figuratively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youthful</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the early part of life; suitable to early life; as, youthful days; youthful sports.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youthful</value>
            <value column="1">Fresh; vigorous, as in youth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youthhood</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being a youth; the period of youth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youthly</value>
            <value column="1">Young; youthful.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youths</value>
            <value column="1">of Youth</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youthsome</value>
            <value column="1">Youthful.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youthy</value>
            <value column="1">Young.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Youze</value>
            <value column="1">The cheetah.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yow</value>
            <value column="1">You.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yowe</value>
            <value column="1">A ewe.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yowl</value>
            <value column="1">To utter a loud, long, and mournful cry, as a dog; to howl; to yell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yowl</value>
            <value column="1">A loud, protracted, and mournful cry, as that of a dog; a howl.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yowley</value>
            <value column="1">The European yellow-hammer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yox</value>
            <value column="1">See Yex.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ypight</value>
            <value column="1">See Pight.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ypocras</value>
            <value column="1">Hippocras.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ypres lace</value>
            <value column="1">Fine bobbin lace made at Ypres in Belgium, usually exactly like Valenciennes lace.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ypsiliform</value>
            <value column="1">Resembling the / in appearance; -- said of the germinal spot in the ripe egg at one of the stages of fecundation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ypsiloid</value>
            <value column="1">In the form of the letter Y; Y-shaped.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yraft</value>
            <value column="1">Bereft.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yren</value>
            <value column="1">Iron.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yronne</value>
            <value column="1">Run.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ys</value>
            <value column="1">of Y</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ysame</value>
            <value column="1">Together.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yt</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Yt</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yt</value>
            <value column="1"><![CDATA[an old method of printing that (AS. /aet, /aet) the "y" taking the place of the old letter "thorn" (/). Cf. Ye, the.]]></value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ythrowe</value>
            <value column="1">p. p. of Throw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ytterbic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or derived from, ytterbium; containing ytterbium.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ytterbium</value>
            <value column="1">A rare element of the boron group, sometimes associated with yttrium or other related elements, as in euxenite and gadolinite. Symbol Yb; provisional atomic weight 173.2. Cf. Yttrium.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yttria</value>
            <value column="1">The oxide, Y2O3, or earth, of yttrium.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yttric</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, derived from, or containing, yttrium.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yttriferous</value>
            <value column="1">Bearing or containing yttrium or the allied elements; as, gadolinite is one of the yttriferous minerals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yttrious</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Yttric.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yttrium</value>
            <value column="1">A rare metallic element of the boron-aluminium group, found in gadolinite and other rare minerals, and extracted as a dark gray powder. Symbol Y. Atomic weight, 89.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yttro-cerite</value>
            <value column="1">A mineral of a violet-blue color, inclining to gray and white. It is a hydrous fluoride of cerium, yttrium, and calcium.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yttro-columbite</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Yttro-tantalite</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yttro-tantalite</value>
            <value column="1">A tantalate of uranium, yttrium, and calcium, of a brown or black color.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yu</value>
            <value column="1">Jade.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yucca</value>
            <value column="1">See Flicker, n., 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yucca</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of American liliaceous, sometimes arborescent, plants having long, pointed, and often rigid, leaves at the top of a more or less woody stem, and bearing a large panicle of showy white blossoms.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yuck</value>
            <value column="1">To itch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yuck</value>
            <value column="1">To scratch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yuckel</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Yockel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yuen</value>
            <value column="1">The crowned gibbon (Hylobates pileatus), native of Siam, Southern China, and the Island of Hainan. It is entirely arboreal in its habits, and has very long arms. the males are dark brown or blackish, with a caplike mass of long dark hair, and usually with a white band around the face. The females are yellowish white, with a dark spot on the breast and another on the crown. Called also wooyen, and wooyen ape.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yufts</value>
            <value column="1">Russia leather.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yug</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Yuga</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yuga</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of the four ages, Krita, or Satya, Treta, Dwapara, and Kali, into which the Hindoos divide the duration or existence of the world.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yuke</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Yuck.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yulan</value>
            <value column="1">A species of Magnolia (M. conspicua) with large white blossoms that open before the leaves. See the Note under Magnolia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yule</value>
            <value column="1">Christmas or Christmastide; the feast of the Nativity of our Savior.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yuletide</value>
            <value column="1">Christmas time; Christmastide; the season of Christmas.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yumas</value>
            <value column="1">A tribe of Indians native of Arizona and the adjacent parts of Mexico and California. They are agricultural, and cultivate corn, wheat, barley, melons, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yunx</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of birds comprising the wrynecks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yupon</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Yaupon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yux</value>
            <value column="1">See Yex, n.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Yvel</value>
            <value column="1">Evil; ill.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ywar</value>
            <value column="1">Aware; wary.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ywis</value>
            <value column="1">Certainly; most likely; truly; probably. Z () Z, the twenty-sixth and last letter of the English alphabet, is a vocal consonant. It is taken from the Latin letter Z, which came from the Greek alphabet, this having it from a Semitic source. The ultimate origin is probably Egyptian. Etymologically, it is most closely related to s, y, and j; as in glass, glaze; E. yoke, Gr. /, L. yugum; E. zealous, jealous. See Guide to Pronunciation, // 273, 274.</value>
         
</rows> 