
    <rows>
         
            <value column="0">Za</value>
            <value column="1">An old solfeggio name for B flat; the seventh harmonic, as heard in the or aeolian string; -- so called by Tartini. It was long considered a false, but is the true note of the chord of the flat seventh.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zabaism</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zabism</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zabian</value>
            <value column="1">See Sabian.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zabism</value>
            <value column="1">See Sabianism.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zacco</value>
            <value column="1">See Zocco.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zachun</value>
            <value column="1">An oil pressed by the Arabs from the fruit of a small thorny tree (Balanites Aegyptiaca), and sold to piligrims for a healing ointment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zaerthe</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Z/rthe.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zaffer</value>
            <value column="1">A pigment obtained, usually by roasting cobalt glance with sand or quartz, as a dark earthy powder. It consists of crude cobalt oxide, or of an impure cobalt arseniate. It is used in porcelain painting, and in enameling pottery, to produce a blue color, and is often confounded with smalt, from which, however, it is distinct, as it contains no potash. The name is often loosely applied to mixtures of zaffer proper with silica, or oxides of iron, manganese, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zaim</value>
            <value column="1">A Turkish chief who supports a mounted militia bearing the same name.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zaimet</value>
            <value column="1">A district from which a Zaim draws his revenue.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zain</value>
            <value column="1">A horse of a dark color, neither gray nor white, and having no spots.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zalambdodont</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to a tribe (Zalambdodonta) of Insectivora in which the molar teeth have but one V-shaped ridge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zalambdodont</value>
            <value column="1">One of the Zalambdodonta. The tenrec, solenodon, and golden moles are examples.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zamang</value>
            <value column="1">An immense leguminous tree (Pithecolobium Saman) of Venezuela. Its branches form a hemispherical mass, often one hundred and eighty feet across. The sweet pulpy pods are used commonly for feeding cattle. Also called rain tree.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zambo</value>
            <value column="1">The child of a mulatto and a negro; also, the child of an Indian and a negro; colloquially or humorously, a negro; a sambo.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zambos</value>
            <value column="1">of Zambo</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zamia</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of cycadaceous plants, having the appearance of low palms, but with exogenous wood. See Coontie, and Illust. of Strobile.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zamindar</value>
            <value column="1">A landowner; also, a collector of land revenue; now, usually, a kind of feudatory recognized as an actual proprietor so long as he pays to the government a certain fixed revenue.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zamindari</value>
            <value column="1">The jurisdiction of a zamindar; the land possessed by a zamindar.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zamindary</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zamindari</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zamite</value>
            <value column="1">A fossil cycad of the genus Zamia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zamouse</value>
            <value column="1">A West African buffalo (Bubalus brachyceros) having short horns depressed at the base, and large ears fringed internally with three rows of long hairs. It is destitute of a dewlap. Called also short-horned buffalo, and bush cow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zampogna</value>
            <value column="1">A sort of bagpipe formerly in use among Italian peasants. It is now almost obsolete.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zander</value>
            <value column="1">A European pike perch (Stizostedion lucioperca) allied to the wall-eye; -- called also sandari, sander, sannat, schill, and zant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zandmole</value>
            <value column="1">The sand mole.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zanies</value>
            <value column="1">of Zany</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zante</value>
            <value column="1">See Zantewood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zante currant</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of seedless grape or raisin; -- so called from Zante, one of the Ionian Islands.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zantewood</value>
            <value column="1">A yellow dyewood; fustet; -- called also zante, and zante fustic. See Fustet, and the Note under Fustic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zantewood</value>
            <value column="1">Satinwood (Chloroxylon Swietenia).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zantiot</value>
            <value column="1">A native or inhabitant of Zante, one of the Ionian Islands.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zany</value>
            <value column="1">A merry-andrew; a buffoon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zany</value>
            <value column="1">To mimic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zanyism</value>
            <value column="1">State or character of a zany; buffoonery.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zaphara</value>
            <value column="1">Zaffer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zaphrentis</value>
            <value column="1">An extinct genus of cyathophylloid corals common in the Paleozoic formations. It is cup-shaped with numerous septa, and with a deep pit in one side of the cup.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zapotilla</value>
            <value column="1">See Sapodilla.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zaptiah</value>
            <value column="1">A Turkish policeman.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zarathustrian</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zarathustric</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zarathustric</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to Zarathustra, or Zoroaster; Zoroastrian.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zarathustrism</value>
            <value column="1">See Zoroastrianism.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zaratite</value>
            <value column="1">A hydrous carbonate of nickel occurring as an emerald-green incrustation on chromite; -- called also emerald nickel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zareba</value>
            <value column="1">An improvised stockade; especially, one made of thorn bushes, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zarnich</value>
            <value column="1">Native sulphide of arsenic, including sandarach, or realgar, and orpiment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zarthe</value>
            <value column="1">A European bream (Abramis vimba).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zati</value>
            <value column="1">A species of macaque (Macacus pileatus) native of India and Ceylon. It has a crown of long erect hair, and tuft of radiating hairs on the back of the head. Called also capped macaque.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zauschneria</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of flowering plants. Zauschneria Californica is a suffrutescent perennial, with showy red flowers much resembling those of the garden fuchsia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zax</value>
            <value column="1">A tool for trimming and puncturing roofing slates.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zayat</value>
            <value column="1">A public shed, or portico, for travelers, worshipers, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zea</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of large grasses of which the Indian corn (Zea Mays) is the only species known. Its origin is not yet ascertained. See Maize.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeal</value>
            <value column="1">Passionate ardor in the pursuit of anything; eagerness in favor of a person or cause; ardent and active interest; engagedness; enthusiasm; fervor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeal</value>
            <value column="1">A zealot.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeal</value>
            <value column="1">To be zealous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zealant</value>
            <value column="1">One who is zealous; a zealot; an enthusiast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zealed</value>
            <value column="1">Full of zeal; characterized by zeal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zealful</value>
            <value column="1">Full of zeal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zealless</value>
            <value column="1">Wanting zeal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zealot</value>
            <value column="1">One who is zealous; one who engages warmly in any cause, and pursues his object with earnestness and ardor; especially, one who is overzealous, or carried away by his zeal; one absorbed in devotion to anything; an enthusiast; a fanatical partisan.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zealotical</value>
            <value column="1">Like, or suitable to, a zealot; ardently zealous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zealotism</value>
            <value column="1">The character or conduct of a zealot; zealotry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zealotist</value>
            <value column="1">A zealot.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zealotry</value>
            <value column="1">The character and behavior of a zealot; excess of zeal; fanatical devotion to a cause.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zealous</value>
            <value column="1">Filled with, or characterized by, zeal; warmly engaged, or ardent, in behalf of an object.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zealous</value>
            <value column="1">Filled with religious zeal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zebec</value>
            <value column="1">See Xebec.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zebra</value>
            <value column="1">Either one of two species of South African wild horses remarkable for having the body white or yellowish white, and conspicuously marked with dark brown or brackish bands.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zebrawood</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of cabinet wood having beautiful black, brown, and whitish stripes, the timber of a tropical American tree (Connarus Guianensis).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zebrawood</value>
            <value column="1">The wood of a small West Indian myrtaceous tree (Eugenia fragrans).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zebrawood</value>
            <value column="1">The wood of an East Indian tree of the genus Guettarda.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zebrine</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or resembling, the zebra.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zebu</value>
            <value column="1">A bovine mammal (Ros Indicus) extensively domesticated in India, China, the East Indies, and East Africa. It usually has short horns, large pendulous ears, slender legs, a large dewlap, and a large, prominent hump over the shoulders; but these characters vary in different domestic breeds, which range in size from that of the common ox to that of a large mastiff.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zebub</value>
            <value column="1">A large noxious fly of Abyssinia, which like the tsetse fly, is destructive to cattle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zechin</value>
            <value column="1">See Sequin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zechstein</value>
            <value column="1">The upper division of the Permian (Dyas) of Europe. The prevailing rock is a magnesian limestone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zed</value>
            <value column="1">The letter Z; -- called also zee, and formerly izzard.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zedoary</value>
            <value column="1">A medicinal substance obtained in the East Indies, having a fragrant smell, and a warm, bitter, aromatic taste. It is used in medicine as a stimulant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeekoe</value>
            <value column="1">A hippopotamus.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zehner</value>
            <value column="1">An Austrian silver coin equal to ten kreutzers, or about five cents.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zein</value>
            <value column="1">A nitrogenous substance of the nature of gluten, obtained from the seeds of Indian corn (Zea) as a soft, yellowish, amorphous substance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zemindar</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Zamindar.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zemindari</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Zamindary.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zemindary</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zemindari</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zemni</value>
            <value column="1">The blind mole rat (Spalax typhlus), native of Eastern Europe and Asia. Its eyes and ears are rudimentary, and its fur is soft and brownish, more or less tinged with gray. It constructs extensive burrows.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zenana</value>
            <value column="1">The part of a dwelling appropriated to women.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zend</value>
            <value column="1">Properly, the translation and exposition in the Huzv/resh, or literary Pehlevi, language, of the Avesta, the Zoroastrian sacred writings; as commonly used, the language (an ancient Persian dialect) in which the Avesta is written.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zend-Avesta</value>
            <value column="1">The sacred writings of the ancient Persian religion, attributed to Zoroaster, but chiefly of a later date.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zendik</value>
            <value column="1">An atheist or unbeliever; -- name given in the East to those charged with disbelief of any revealed religion, or accused of magical heresies.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zenick</value>
            <value column="1">A South African burrowing mammal (Suricata tetradactyla), allied to the civets. It is grayish brown, with yellowish transverse stripes on the back. Called also suricat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zenik</value>
            <value column="1">See Zenick.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zenith</value>
            <value column="1">That point in the visible celestial hemisphere which is vertical to the spectator; the point of the heavens directly overhead; -- opposed to nadir.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zenith</value>
            <value column="1">hence, figuratively, the point of culmination; the greatest height; the height of success or prosperity.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zenithal</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the zenith.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeolite</value>
            <value column="1">A term now used to designate any one of a family of minerals, hydrous silicates of alumina, with lime, soda, potash, or rarely baryta. Here are included natrolite, stilbite, analcime, chabazite, thomsonite, heulandite, and others. These species occur of secondary origin in the cavities of amygdaloid, basalt, and lava, also, less frequently, in granite and gneiss. So called because many of these species intumesce before the blowpipe.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeolitic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to a zeolite; consisting of, or resembling, a zeolite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeolitiform</value>
            <value column="1">Having the form of a zeolite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zephyr</value>
            <value column="1">The west wind; poetically, any soft, gentle breeze.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zephyrus</value>
            <value column="1">The west wind, or zephyr; -- usually personified, and made the most mild and gentle of all the sylvan deities.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zequin</value>
            <value column="1">See Sequin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zerda</value>
            <value column="1">The fennec.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeriba</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Zareba.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zero</value>
            <value column="1">A cipher; nothing; naught.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zero</value>
            <value column="1">The point from which the graduation of a scale, as of a thermometer, commences.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zero</value>
            <value column="1">Fig.: The lowest point; the point of exhaustion; as, his patience had nearly reached zero.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeroes</value>
            <value column="1">of Zero</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeros</value>
            <value column="1">of Zero</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zest</value>
            <value column="1">A piece of orange or lemon peel, or the aromatic oil which may be squeezed from such peel, used to give flavor to liquor, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zest</value>
            <value column="1">Hence, something that gives or enhances a pleasant taste, or the taste itself; an appetizer; also, keen enjoyment; relish; gusto.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zest</value>
            <value column="1">The woody, thick skin inclosing the kernel of a walnut.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zest</value>
            <value column="1">To cut into thin slips, as the peel of an orange, lemon, etc.; to squeeze, as peel, over the surface of anything.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zest</value>
            <value column="1">To give a relish or flavor to; to heighten the taste or relish of; as, to zest wine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zested</value>
            <value column="1">of Zest</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zesting</value>
            <value column="1">of Zest</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeta</value>
            <value column="1">A Greek letter corresponding to our z.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zetetic</value>
            <value column="1">Seeking; proceeding by inquiry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zetetic</value>
            <value column="1">A seeker; -- a name adopted by some of the Pyrrhonists.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zetetics</value>
            <value column="1">A branch of algebra which relates to the direct search for unknown quantities.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeuglodon</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of extinct Eocene whales, remains of which have been found in the Gulf States. The species had very long and slender bodies and broad serrated teeth. See Phocodontia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeuglodont</value>
            <value column="1">Any species of Zeuglodonta.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeuglodonta</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Phocodontia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeugma</value>
            <value column="1"><![CDATA[A figure by which an adjective or verb, which agrees with a nearer word, is, by way of supplement, referred also to another more remote; as, "hic illius arma, hic currus fuit;" where fuit, which agrees directly with currus, is referred also to arma.]]></value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeugmatic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to zeugma; characterized by zeugma.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeugobranchiata</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Zygobranchia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeus</value>
            <value column="1">The chief deity of the Greeks, and ruler of the upper world (cf. Hades). He was identified with Jupiter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeuzerian</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of a group of bombycid moths of which the genus Zeuzera is the type. Some of these moths are of large size. The goat moth is an example.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zeylanite</value>
            <value column="1">See Ceylanite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zibet</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zibeth</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zibeth</value>
            <value column="1">A carnivorous mammal (Viverra zibetha) closely allied to the civet, from which it differs in having the spots on the body less distinct, the throat whiter, and the black rings on the tail more numerous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ziega</value>
            <value column="1">Curd produced from milk by adding acetic acid, after rennet has ceased to cause coagulation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zietrisikite</value>
            <value column="1">A mineral wax, vert similar to ozocerite. It is found at Zietrisika, Moldavia, whence its name.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zif</value>
            <value column="1">The second month of the Jewish ecclesiastical year, corresponding to our May.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zigger</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zighyr</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zighyr</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Sicker.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zigzag</value>
            <value column="1">Something that has short turns or angles.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zigzag</value>
            <value column="1">A molding running in a zigzag line; a chevron, or series of chevrons. See Illust. of Chevron, 3.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zigzag</value>
            <value column="1">See Boyau.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zigzag</value>
            <value column="1">Having short, sharp turns; running this way and that in an onward course.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zigzag</value>
            <value column="1">To form with short turns.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zigzag</value>
            <value column="1">To move in a zigzag manner; also, to have a zigzag shape.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zigzagged</value>
            <value column="1">of Zigzag</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zigzaggery</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being zigzag; crookedness.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zigzagging</value>
            <value column="1">of Zigzag</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zigzaggy</value>
            <value column="1">Having sharp turns.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zilla</value>
            <value column="1">A low, thorny, suffrutescent, crucifeous plant (Zilla myagroides) found in the deserts of Egypt. Its leaves are boiled in water, and eaten, by the Arabs.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zillah</value>
            <value column="1">A district or local division, as of a province.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zimb</value>
            <value column="1">A large, venomous, two-winged fly, native of Abyssinia. It is allied to the tsetse fly, and, like the latter, is destructive to cattle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ziment-water</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of water found in copper mines; water impregnated with copper.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinc</value>
            <value column="1">An abundant element of the magnesium-cadmium group, extracted principally from the minerals zinc blende, smithsonite, calamine, and franklinite, as an easily fusible bluish white metal, which is malleable, especially when heated. It is not easily oxidized in moist air, and hence is used for sheeting, coating galvanized iron, etc. It is used in making brass, britannia, and other alloys, and is also largely consumed in electric batteries. Symbol Zn. Atomic weight 64.9.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinc</value>
            <value column="1">To coat with zinc; to galvanize.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincane</value>
            <value column="1">Zinc chloride.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinced</value>
            <value column="1">of Zinc</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, containing, or resembling, zinc; zincous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincide</value>
            <value column="1">A binary compound of zinc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinciferous</value>
            <value column="1">Containing or affording zinc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincification</value>
            <value column="1">The act or process of applying zinc; the condition of being zincified, or covered with zinc; galvanization.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincify</value>
            <value column="1">To coat or impregnate with zinc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincing</value>
            <value column="1">of Zinc</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincing</value>
            <value column="1">The act or process of applying zinc; galvanization.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincite</value>
            <value column="1">Native zinc oxide; a brittle, translucent mineral, of an orange-red color; -- called also red zinc ore, and red oxide of zinc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincked</value>
            <value column="1">of Zinc</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincking</value>
            <value column="1">of Zinc</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincking</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zincing</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincky</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to zinc, or having its appearance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinco-</value>
            <value column="1">A combining form from zinc; in chemistry, designating zinc as an element of certain double compounds. Also used adjectively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinco-polar</value>
            <value column="1">Electrically polarized like the surface of the zinc presented to the acid in a battery, which has zincous affinity.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincode</value>
            <value column="1">The positive electrode of an electrolytic cell; anode.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincographer</value>
            <value column="1">An engraver on zinc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincography</value>
            <value column="1">The art or process of engraving or etching on zinc, in which the design is left in relief in the style of a wood cut, the rest of the ground being eaten away by acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincoid</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or resembling, zinc; -- said of the electricity of the zincous plate in connection with a copper plate in a voltaic circle; also, designating the positive pole.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincongraphic</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zincongraphical</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincongraphical</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to zincography; as, zincographic processes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincous</value>
            <value column="1">Of, pertaining to, or containing, zinc; zincic; as, zincous salts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincous</value>
            <value column="1">Hence, formerly, basic, basylous, as opposed to chlorous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zincous</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the positive pole of a galvanic battery; electro-positive.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zingari</value>
            <value column="1">of Zingaro</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zingaro</value>
            <value column="1">A gypsy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zingel</value>
            <value column="1">A small, edible, freshwater European perch (Aspro zingel), having a round, elongated body and prominent snout.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zingiberaceous</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to ginger, or to a tribe (Zingibereae) of endogenous plants of the order Scitamineae. See Scitamineous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zink</value>
            <value column="1">See Zinc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinkenite</value>
            <value column="1">A steel-gray metallic mineral, a sulphide of antimony and lead.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinky</value>
            <value column="1">See Zincky.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinnia</value>
            <value column="1">Any plant of the composite genus Zinnia, Mexican herbs with opposite leaves and large gay-colored blossoms. Zinnia elegans is the commonest species in cultivation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinnwaldite</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of mica containing lithium, often associated with tin ore.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinsang</value>
            <value column="1">The delundung.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zinziberaceous</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Zingiberaceous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zion</value>
            <value column="1">A hill in Jerusalem, which, after the capture of that city by the Israelites, became the royal residence of David and his successors.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zion</value>
            <value column="1">Hence, the theocracy, or church of God.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zion</value>
            <value column="1">The heavenly Jerusalem; heaven.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ziphioid</value>
            <value column="1">See Xiphioid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zirco-</value>
            <value column="1">A combining form (also used adjectively) designating zirconium as an element of certain double compounds; zircono-; as in zircofluoric acid, sodium zircofluoride.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zircofluoride</value>
            <value column="1">A double fluoride of zirconium and hydrogen, or some other positive element or radical; as, zircofluoride of sodium.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zircon</value>
            <value column="1">A mineral occurring in tetragonal crystals, usually of a brown or gray color. It consists of silica and zirconia. A red variety, used as a gem, is called hyacinth. Colorless, pale-yellow or smoky-brown varieties from Ceylon are called jargon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zircona</value>
            <value column="1">Zirconia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zirconate</value>
            <value column="1">A salt of zirconic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zirconia</value>
            <value column="1">The oxide of zirconium, obtained as a white powder, and possessing both acid and basic properties. On account of its infusibility, and brilliant luminosity when incandescent, it is used as an ingredient of sticks for the Drummomd light.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zirconic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, containing, or resembling, zirconium; as, zirconic oxide; zirconic compounds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zirconium</value>
            <value column="1">A rare element of the carbon-silicon group, intermediate between the metals and nonmetals, obtained from the mineral zircon as a dark sooty powder, or as a gray metallic crystalline substance. Symbol Zr. Atomic weight, 90.4.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zircono</value>
            <value column="1">See Zirco-.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zirconoid</value>
            <value column="1">A double eight-sided pyramid, a form common with tetragonal crystals; -- so called because this form often occurs in crystals of zircon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zither</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument of music used in Austria and Germany. It has from thirty to forty wires strung across a shallow sounding-board, which lies horizontally on a table before the performer, who uses both hands in playing on it. [Not to be confounded with the old lute-shaped cittern, or cithern.]</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zittern</value>
            <value column="1">See Cittern.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zizania</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of grasses including Indian rice. See Indian rice, under Rice.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zizel</value>
            <value column="1">The suslik.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoa</value>
            <value column="1">of Zoon</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoanthacea</value>
            <value column="1">A suborder of Actinaria, including Zoanthus and allied genera, which are permanently attached by their bases.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoantharia</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Anthozoa.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoantharian</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the Zoantharia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoantharian</value>
            <value column="1">One of the Anthozoa.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoanthodeme</value>
            <value column="1">The zooids of a compound anthozoan, collectively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoanthoid</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the Zoanthacea.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoanthropy</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of monomania in which the patient believes himself transformed into one of the lower animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoanthus</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of Actinaria, including numerous species, found mostly in tropical seas. The zooids or polyps resemble small, elongated actinias united together at their bases by fleshy stolons, and thus forming extensive groups. The tentacles are small and bright colored.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zobo</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of domestic cattle reared in Asia for its flesh and milk. It is supposed to be a hybrid between the zebu and the yak.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zocco</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zoccolo</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoccolo</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Socle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zocle</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Socle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zodiac</value>
            <value column="1">An imaginary belt in the heavens, 16ยก or 18ยก broad, in the middle of which is the ecliptic, or sun's path. It comprises the twelve constellations, which one constituted, and from which were named, the twelve signs of the zodiac.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zodiac</value>
            <value column="1">A figure representing the signs, symbols, and constellations of the zodiac.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zodiac</value>
            <value column="1">A girdle; a belt.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zodiacal</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the zodiac; situated within the zodiac; as, the zodiacal planets.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoea</value>
            <value column="1">A peculiar larval stage of certain decapod Crustacea, especially of crabs and certain Anomura.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoetrope</value>
            <value column="1">An optical toy, in which figures made to revolve on the inside of a cylinder, and viewed through slits in its circumference, appear like a single figure passing through a series of natural motions as if animated or mechanically moved.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zohar</value>
            <value column="1">A Jewish cabalistic book attributed by tradition to Rabbi Simon ben Yochi, who lived about the end of the 1st century, a. d. Modern critics believe it to be a compilation of the 13th century.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to animals, or animal life.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoide</value>
            <value column="1">See Meride.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoilean</value>
            <value column="1">Having the characteristic of Zoilus, a bitter, envious, unjust critic, who lived about 270 years before Christ.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoilism</value>
            <value column="1">Resemblance to Zoilus in style or manner; carping criticism; detraction.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoisite</value>
            <value column="1">A grayish or whitish mineral occurring in orthorhombic, prismatic crystals, also in columnar masses. It is a silicate of alumina and lime, and is allied to epidote.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zokor</value>
            <value column="1">An Asiatic burrowing rodent (Siphneus aspalax) resembling the mole rat. It is native of the Altai Mountains.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zollverein</value>
            <value column="1">Literally, a customs union; specifically, applied to the several customs unions successively formed under the leadership of Prussia among certain German states for establishing liberty of commerce among themselves and common tariff on imports, exports, and transit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zomboruk</value>
            <value column="1">See Zumbooruk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zona</value>
            <value column="1">A zone or band; a layer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zonae</value>
            <value column="1">of Zona</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zonal</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to a zone; having the form of a zone or zones.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zonar</value>
            <value column="1">A belt or girdle which the Christians and Jews of the Levant were obliged to wear to distinguish them from Mohammedans.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zonaria</value>
            <value column="1">A division of Mammalia in which the placenta is zonelike.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zonate</value>
            <value column="1">Divided by parallel planes; as, zonate tetraspores, found in certain red algae.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zone</value>
            <value column="1">A girdle; a cincture.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zone</value>
            <value column="1">One of the five great divisions of the earth, with respect to latitude and temperature.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zone</value>
            <value column="1">The portion of the surface of a sphere included between two parallel planes; the portion of a surface of revolution included between two planes perpendicular to the axis.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zone</value>
            <value column="1">A band or stripe extending around a body.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zone</value>
            <value column="1">A band or area of growth encircling anything; as, a zone of evergreens on a mountain; the zone of animal or vegetable life in the ocean around an island or a continent; the Alpine zone, that part of mountains which is above the limit of tree growth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zone</value>
            <value column="1">A series of planes having mutually parallel intersections.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zone</value>
            <value column="1">Circuit; circumference.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zone</value>
            <value column="1">To girdle; to encircle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoned</value>
            <value column="1">Wearing a zone, or girdle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoned</value>
            <value column="1">Having zones, or concentric bands; striped.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoned</value>
            <value column="1">Zonate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoneless</value>
            <value column="1">Not having a zone; ungirded.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zonnar</value>
            <value column="1">See Zonar.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zonular</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to a zone; zone-shaped.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zonule</value>
            <value column="1">A little zone, or girdle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zonulet</value>
            <value column="1">A zonule.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zonure</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several of South African lizards of the genus Zonura, common in rocky situations.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoo-</value>
            <value column="1">A combining form from Gr. zwo^,n an animal, as in zoogenic, zoology, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoochemical</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to zoochemistry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoochemistry</value>
            <value column="1">Animal chemistry; particularly, the description of the chemical compounds entering into the composition of the animal body, in distinction from biochemistry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoochemy</value>
            <value column="1">Animal chemistry; zoochemistry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoochlorella</value>
            <value column="1">One of the small green granulelike bodies found in the interior of certain stentors, hydras, and other invertebrates.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoocyst</value>
            <value column="1">A cyst formed by certain Protozoa and unicellular plants which the contents divide into a large number of granules, each of which becomes a germ.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoocytia</value>
            <value column="1">of Zoocytium</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoocytium</value>
            <value column="1">The common support, often branched, of certain species of social Infusoria.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoodendria</value>
            <value column="1">of Zoodendrium</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoodendrium</value>
            <value column="1">The branched, and often treelike, support of the colonies of certain Infusoria.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zooecia</value>
            <value column="1">of Zooecium</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zooecium</value>
            <value column="1">One of the cells or tubes which inclose the feeling zooids of Bryozoa. See Illust. of Sea Moss.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zooerythrine</value>
            <value column="1">A peculiar organic red coloring matter found in the feathers of various birds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoogamous</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining zoogamy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoogamy</value>
            <value column="1">The sexual reproduction of animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoogenic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to zoogeny, animal production.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoogeny</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zoogony</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoogeographical</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to zoography.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoogeography</value>
            <value column="1">The study or description of the geographical distribution of animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoogloea</value>
            <value column="1">A colony or mass of bacteria imbedded in a viscous gelatinous substance. The zoogloea is characteristic of a transitory stage through which rapidly multiplying bacteria pass in the course of their evolution. Also used adjectively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoogony</value>
            <value column="1">The doctrine of the formation of living beings.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoographer</value>
            <value column="1">One who describes animals, their forms and habits.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoographic</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zoographical</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoographical</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the description of animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoographist</value>
            <value column="1">A zoographer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoography</value>
            <value column="1">A description of animals, their forms and habits.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zooid</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or resembling, an animal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zooid</value>
            <value column="1">An organic body or cell having locomotion, as a spermatic cell or spermatozooid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zooid</value>
            <value column="1">An animal in one of its inferior stages of development, as one of the intermediate forms in alternate generation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zooid</value>
            <value column="1">One of the individual animals in a composite group, as of Anthozoa, Hydroidea, and Bryozoa; -- sometimes restricted to those individuals in which the mouth and digestive organs are not developed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zooidal</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to a zooid; as, a zooidal form.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoolatry</value>
            <value column="1">The worship of animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoologer</value>
            <value column="1">A zoologist.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoological</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to zoology, or the science of animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoologically</value>
            <value column="1">In a zoological manner; according to the principles of zoology.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoologies</value>
            <value column="1">of Zoology</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoologist</value>
            <value column="1">One who is well versed in zoology.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoology</value>
            <value column="1">That part of biology which relates to the animal kingdom, including the structure, embryology, evolution, classification, habits, and distribution of all animals, both living and extinct.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoology</value>
            <value column="1">A treatise on this science.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoomelanin</value>
            <value column="1">A pigment giving the black color to the feathers of many birds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoomorphic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to zoomorphism.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoomorphism</value>
            <value column="1">The transformation of men into beasts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoomorphism</value>
            <value column="1">The quality of representing or using animal forms; as, zoomorphism in ornament.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoomorphism</value>
            <value column="1">The representation of God, or of gods, in the form, or with the attributes, of the lower animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoon</value>
            <value column="1">An animal which is the sole product of a single egg; -- opposed to zooid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoon</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of the perfectly developed individuals of a compound animal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoonic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to animals; obtained from animal substances.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoonite</value>
            <value column="1">One of the segments of the body of an articulate animal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoonite</value>
            <value column="1">One of the theoretic transverse divisions of any segmented animal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoonomy</value>
            <value column="1">The laws of animal life, or the science which treats of the phenomena of animal life, their causes and relations.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoonule</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Zoonite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoopathology</value>
            <value column="1">Animal pathology.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophaga</value>
            <value column="1">An artificial group comprising various carnivorous and insectivorous animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophagan</value>
            <value column="1">A animal that feeds on animal food.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophagous</value>
            <value column="1">Feeding on animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophilist</value>
            <value column="1">A lover of animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophily</value>
            <value column="1">Love of animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophite</value>
            <value column="1">A zoophyte.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophoric</value>
            <value column="1">Bearing or supporting the figure of an animal; as, a zoophoric column.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophorous</value>
            <value column="1">The part between the architrave and cornice; the frieze; -- so called from the figures of animals carved upon it.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophyta</value>
            <value column="1">An extensive artificial and heterogeneous group of animals, formerly adopted by many zoologists. It included the c/lenterates, echinoderms, sponges, Bryozoa, Protozoa, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophyte</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of numerous species of invertebrate animals which more or less resemble plants in appearance, or mode of growth, as the corals, gorgonians, sea anemones, hydroids, bryozoans, sponges, etc., especially any of those that form compound colonies having a branched or treelike form, as many corals and hydroids.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophyte</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of the Zoophyta.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophytic</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zoophytical</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophytical</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to zoophytes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophytoid</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or resembling, a zoophyte.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophytological</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to zoophytology; as, zoophytological observations.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoophytology</value>
            <value column="1">The natural history zoophytes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoopraxiscope</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument similar to, or the same as, the, the phenakistoscope, by means of which pictures projected upon a screen are made to exhibit the natural movements of animals, and the like.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoopsychology</value>
            <value column="1">Animal psychology.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoosperm</value>
            <value column="1">One of the spermatic particles; spermatozoid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoosporangium</value>
            <value column="1">A spore, or conceptacle containing zoospores.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoospore</value>
            <value column="1">A spore provided with one or more slender cilia, by the vibration of which it swims in the water. Zoospores are produced by many green, and by some olive-brown, algae. In certain species they are divided into the larger macrozoospores and the smaller microzoospores. Called also sporozoid, and swarmspore.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoospore</value>
            <value column="1">See Swarmspore.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoosporic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to zoospores; of the nature of zoospores.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zootic</value>
            <value column="1">Containing the remains of organized bodies; -- said of rock or soil.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zootomical</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to zootomy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zootomist</value>
            <value column="1">One who dissects animals, or is skilled in zootomy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zootomy</value>
            <value column="1">The dissection or the anatomy of animals; -- distinguished from androtomy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zootrophic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the nourishment of animals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoozoo</value>
            <value column="1">The wood pigeon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zope</value>
            <value column="1">A European fresh-water bream (Abramis ballerus).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zopilote</value>
            <value column="1">The urubu, or American black vulture.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoril</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Zorilla.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zorilla</value>
            <value column="1">Either one of two species of small African carnivores of the genus Ictonyx allied to the weasels and skunks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoroastrian</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to Zoroaster, or his religious system.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoroastrian</value>
            <value column="1">A follower of Zoroaster; one who accepts Zoroastrianism.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoroastrianism</value>
            <value column="1">The religious system of Zoroaster, the legislator and prophet of the ancient Persians, which was the national faith of Persia; mazdeism. The system presupposes a good spirit (Ormuzd) and an opposing evil spirit (Ahriman). Cf. Fire worship, under Fire, and Parsee.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoroastrism</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Zoroastrianism.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoster</value>
            <value column="1">Shingles.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zostera</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of plants of the Naiadaceae, or Pondweed family. Zostera marina is commonly known as sea wrack, and eelgrass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zosterops</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of birds that comprises the white-eyes. See White-eye.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zouave</value>
            <value column="1">One of an active and hardy body of soldiers in the French service, originally Arabs, but now composed of Frenchmen who wear the Arab dress.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zouave</value>
            <value column="1">Hence, one of a body of soldiers who adopt the dress and drill of the Zouaves, as was done by a number of volunteer regiments in the army of the United States in the Civil War, 1861-65.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zounds</value>
            <value column="1">An exclamation formerly used as an oath, and an expression of anger or wonder.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zoutch</value>
            <value column="1">To stew, as flounders, eels, etc., with just enough or liquid to cover them.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zu/is</value>
            <value column="1">A tribe of Pueblo Indians occupying a village in New Mexico, on the Zu/i River.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zubr</value>
            <value column="1">The aurochs.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zuche</value>
            <value column="1">A stump of a tree.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zuchetto</value>
            <value column="1">A skullcap covering the tonsure, worn under the berretta. The pope's is white; a cardinal's red; a bishop's purple; a priest's black.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zufolo</value>
            <value column="1">A little flute or flageolet, especially that which is used to teach birds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zuisin</value>
            <value column="1">The American widgeon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zulus</value>
            <value column="1">The most important tribe belonging to the Kaffir race. They inhabit a region on the southeast coast of Africa, but formerly occupied a much more extensive country. They are noted for their warlike disposition, courage, and military skill.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zumbooruk</value>
            <value column="1">A small cannon supported by a swiveled rest on the back of a camel, whence it is fired, -- used in the East.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zumic</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zumometer</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zumological</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zumometer</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zumology</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zumometer</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zumometer</value>
            <value column="1">See Zymic, Zymological, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zunyite</value>
            <value column="1">A fluosilicate of alumina occurring in tetrahedral crystals at the Zu/i mine in Colorado.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zwanziger</value>
            <value column="1">An Austrian silver coin equivalent to 20 kreutzers, or about 10 cents.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygantra</value>
            <value column="1">of Zygantrum</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygantrum</value>
            <value column="1">See under Zygosphene.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygapophyses</value>
            <value column="1">of Zygapophysis</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygapophysis</value>
            <value column="1">One of the articular processes of a vertebra, of which there are usually four, two anterior and two posterior. See under Vertebra.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygenid</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of numerous species of moths of the family Zygaenidae, most of which are bright colored. The wood nymph and the vine forester are examples. Also used adjectively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygobranchia</value>
            <value column="1">A division of marine gastropods in which the gills are developed on both sides of the body and the renal organs are also paired. The abalone (Haliotis) and the keyhole limpet (Fissurella) are examples.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygobranchiate</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the Zygobranchia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygodactyl</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zygodactyle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygodactylae</value>
            <value column="1">The zygodactylous birds. In a restricted sense applied to a division of birds which includes the barbets, toucans, honey guides, and other related birds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygodactyle</value>
            <value column="1">Any zygodactylous bird.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygodactyli</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Scansores.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygodactylic</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zygodactylous</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygodactylous</value>
            <value column="1">Yoke-footed; having the toes disposed in pairs; -- applied to birds which have two toes before and two behind, as the parrot, cuckoo, woodpecker, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygoma</value>
            <value column="1">The jugal, malar, or cheek bone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygoma</value>
            <value column="1">The zygomatic process of the temporal bone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygoma</value>
            <value column="1">The whole zygomatic arch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygomatic</value>
            <value column="1">Of, pertaining to, or in the region of, the zygoma.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygomorphic</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zygomorphous</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygomorphous</value>
            <value column="1">Symmetrical bilaterally; -- said of organisms, or parts of organisms, capable of division into two symmetrical halves only in a single plane.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygosis</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Conjugation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygosperm</value>
            <value column="1">A spore formed by the union of the contents of two similar cells, either of the same or of distinct individual plants. Zygosperms are found in certain orders of algae and fungi.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygosphene</value>
            <value column="1">A median process on the front part of the neural arch of the vertebrae of most snakes and some lizards, which fits into a fossa, called the zygantrum, on the back part of the arch in front.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygospore</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Zygosperm.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zygospore</value>
            <value column="1">A spore formed by the union of several zoospores; -- called also zygozoospore.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zylonite</value>
            <value column="1">Celluloid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymase</value>
            <value column="1">A soluble ferment, or enzyme. See Enzyme.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zyme</value>
            <value column="1">A ferment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zyme</value>
            <value column="1">The morbific principle of a zymotic disease.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or produced by, fermentation; -- formerly, by confusion, used to designate lactic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymogen</value>
            <value column="1">A mother substance, or antecedent, of an enzyme or chemical ferment; -- applied to such substances as, not being themselves actual ferments, may by internal changes give rise to a ferment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymogene</value>
            <value column="1">One of a physiological group of globular bacteria which produces fermentations of diverse nature; -- distinguished from pathogene.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymogenic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or formed by, a zymogene.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymogenic</value>
            <value column="1">Capable of producing a definite zymogen or ferment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymologic</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zymological</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymological</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to zymology.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymologist</value>
            <value column="1">One who is skilled in zymology, or in the fermentation of liquors.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymology</value>
            <value column="1">A treatise on the fermentation of liquors, or the doctrine of fermentation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymome</value>
            <value column="1">A glutinous substance, insoluble in alcohol, resembling legumin; -- now called vegetable fibrin, vegetable albumin, or gluten casein.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymometer</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Zymosimeter</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymophyte</value>
            <value column="1">A bacteroid ferment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymose</value>
            <value column="1">Invertin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymosimeter</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument for ascertaining the degree of fermentation occasioned by the mixture of different liquids, and the degree of heat which they acquire in fermentation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymosis</value>
            <value column="1">A fermentation; hence, an analogous process by which an infectious disease is believed to be developed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymosis</value>
            <value column="1">A zymotic disease.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymotic</value>
            <value column="1">Of, pertaining to, or caused by, fermentation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zymotic</value>
            <value column="1">Designating, or pertaining to, a certain class of diseases. See Zymotic disease, below.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zyophyte</value>
            <value column="1">Any plant of a proposed class or grand division (Zygophytes, Zygophyta, or Zygosporeae), in which reproduction consists in the union of two similar cells. Cf. Oophyte.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zythem</value>
            <value column="1">See Zythum.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zythepsary</value>
            <value column="1">A brewery.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Zythum</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of ancient malt beverage; a liquor made from malt and wheat.</value>
         
</rows> 