
    <rows>
         
            <value column="0">Xanthamide</value>
            <value column="1">An amido derivative of xanthic acid obtained as a white crystalline substance, C2H5O.CS.NH2; -- called also xanthogen amide.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthate</value>
            <value column="1">A salt of xanthic; a xanthogenate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthelasma</value>
            <value column="1">See Xanthoma.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthian</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to Xanthus, an ancient town on Asia Minor; -- applied especially to certain marbles found near that place, and now in the British Museum.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthic</value>
            <value column="1">Tending toward a yellow color, or to one of those colors, green being excepted, in which yellow is a constituent, as scarlet, orange, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthic</value>
            <value column="1">Possessing, imparting, or producing a yellow color; as, xanthic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to xanthic acid, or its compounds; xanthogenic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to xanthin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthide</value>
            <value column="1">A compound or derivative of xanthogen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthidia</value>
            <value column="1">of Xanthidium</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthidium</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of minute unicellular algae of the desmids. These algae have a rounded shape and are armed with glochidiate or branched aculei. Several species occur in ditches, and others are found fossil in flint or hornstone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthin</value>
            <value column="1">A crystalline nitrogenous body closely related to both uric acid and hypoxanthin, present in muscle tissue, and occasionally found in the urine and in some urinary calculi. It is also present in guano. So called from the yellow color of certain of its salts (nitrates).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthin</value>
            <value column="1">A yellow insoluble coloring matter extracted from yellow flowers; specifically, the coloring matter of madder.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthin</value>
            <value column="1">One of the gaseous or volatile decomposition products of the xanthates, and probably identical with carbon disulphide.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthinine</value>
            <value column="1">A complex nitrogenous substance related to urea and uric acid, produced as a white powder; -- so called because it forms yellow salts, and because its solution forms a blue fluorescence like quinine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthium</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of composite plants in which the scales of the involucre are united so as to form a kind of bur; cocklebur; clotbur.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xantho-</value>
            <value column="1">A combining form from Gr. xanqo`s yellow; as in xanthocobaltic salts. Used also adjectively in chemistry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthocarpous</value>
            <value column="1">Having yellow fruit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthochroi</value>
            <value column="1">A division of the Caucasian races, comprising the lighter-colored members.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthochroic</value>
            <value column="1">Having a yellowish or fair complexion; of or pertaining to the Xanthochroi.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthodontous</value>
            <value column="1">Having yellow teeth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthogen</value>
            <value column="1">The hypothetical radical supposed to be characteristic of xanthic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthogen</value>
            <value column="1">Persulphocyanogen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthogenate</value>
            <value column="1">A salt of xanthic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthogenic</value>
            <value column="1">Producing a yellow color or compound; xanthic. See Xanthic acid, under Xanthic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthoma</value>
            <value column="1">A skin disease marked by the development or irregular yellowish patches upon the skin, especially upon the eyelids; -- called also xanthelasma.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthophane</value>
            <value column="1">The yellow pigment present in the inner segments of the retina in animals. See Chromophane.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthophyll</value>
            <value column="1">A yellow coloring matter found in yellow autumn leaves, and also produced artificially from chlorophyll; -- formerly called also phylloxanthin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthopous</value>
            <value column="1">Having a yellow stipe, or stem.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthoproteic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or derived from, xanthoprotein; showing the characters of xanthoprotein; as, xanthoproteic acid; the xanthoproteic reaction for albumin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthoprotein</value>
            <value column="1">A yellow acid substance formed by the action of hot nitric acid on albuminous or proteid matter. It is changed to a deep orange-yellow color by the addition of ammonia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthopuccine</value>
            <value column="1">One of three alkaloids found in the root of the yellow puccoon (Hydrastis Canadensis). It is a yellow crystalline substance, and resembles berberine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthorhamnin</value>
            <value column="1">A glucoside extracted from Persian berries as a yellow crystalline powder, used as a dyestuff.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthorhiza</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of shrubby ranunculaceous plants of North America, including only the species Xanthorhiza apiifolia, which has roots of a deep yellow color; yellowroot. The bark is intensely bitter, and is sometimes used as a tonic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthorhoea</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of endogenous plants, native to Australia, having a thick, sometimes arborescent, stem, and long grasslike leaves. See Grass tree.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthose</value>
            <value column="1">An orange-yellow substance found in pigment spots of certain crabs.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthosis</value>
            <value column="1">The yellow discoloration often observed in cancerous tumors.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthospermous</value>
            <value column="1">Having yellow seeds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthous</value>
            <value column="1">Yellow; specifically (Ethnol.), of or pertaining to those races of man which have yellowish, red, auburn, or brown hair.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthoxylene</value>
            <value column="1">A liquid hydrocarbon of the terpene series extracted from the seeds of a Japanese prickly ash (Xanthoxylum pipertium) as an aromatic oil.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xanthoxylum</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of prickly shrubs or small trees, the bark and rots of which are of a deep yellow color; prickly ash.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xebec</value>
            <value column="1">A small three-masted vessel, with projecting bow stern and convex decks, used in the Mediterranean for transporting merchandise, etc. It carries large square sails, or both. Xebecs were formerly armed and used by corsairs.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xeme</value>
            <value column="1">An Arctic fork-tailed gull (Xema Sabinii).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenelasia</value>
            <value column="1">A Spartan institution which prohibited strangers from residing in Sparta without permission, its object probably being to preserve the national simplicity of manners.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenia</value>
            <value column="1">of Xenium</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenium</value>
            <value column="1">A present given to a guest or stranger, or to a foreign ambassador.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenodochium</value>
            <value column="1">A house for the reception of strangers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenodochium</value>
            <value column="1">In the Middle Ages, a room in a monastery for the reception and entertainment of strangers and pilgrims, and for the relief of paupers. [Called also Xenodocheion.]</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenodochy</value>
            <value column="1">Reception of strangers; hospitality.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenogamy</value>
            <value column="1">Cross fertilization.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenogenesis</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Heterogenesis.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenogenesis</value>
            <value column="1">The fancied production of an organism of one kind by an organism of another.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenogenetic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to xenogenesis; as, the xenogenetic origin of microzymes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenomania</value>
            <value column="1">A mania for, or an inordinate attachment to, foreign customs, institutions, manners, fashions, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenomi</value>
            <value column="1">A suborder of soft-rayed fresh-water fishes of which the blackfish of Alaska (Dallia pectoralis) is the type.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenopterygii</value>
            <value column="1">A suborder of fishes including Gobiesox and allied genera. These fishes have soft-rayed fins, and a ventral sucker supported in front by the pectoral fins. They are destitute of scales.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenotime</value>
            <value column="1">A native phosphate of yttrium occurring in yellowish-brown tetragonal crystals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenurine</value>
            <value column="1">A cabassou.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenyl</value>
            <value column="1">The radical characteristic of xenylic compounds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xenylic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, derived from, designating, certain amido compounds obtained by reducing certain nitro derivatives of diphenyl.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xeraphim</value>
            <value column="1">An old money of account in Bombay, equal to three fifths of a rupee.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xeres</value>
            <value column="1">Sherry. See Sherry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xerif</value>
            <value column="1">A shereef.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xeriff</value>
            <value column="1">A gold coin formerly current in Egypt and Turkey, of the value of about 9s. 6d., or about $2.30; -- also, in Morocco, a ducat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xeroderma</value>
            <value column="1">Ichthyosis.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xeroderma</value>
            <value column="1">A skin disease characterized by the presence of numerous small pigmented spots resembling freckles, with which are subsequently mingled spots of atrophied skin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xeronate</value>
            <value column="1">A salt of xeronic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xeronic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or designating, an acid, C8H12O4, related to fumaric acid, and obtained from citraconic acid as an oily substance having a bittersweet taste; -- so called from its tendency to form its anhydride.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xerophagy</value>
            <value column="1">Among the primitive Christians, the living on a diet of dry food in Lent and on other fasts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xerophilous</value>
            <value column="1">Drought-loving; able withstand the absence or lack of moisture.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xerophthalmia</value>
            <value column="1">An abnormal dryness of the eyeball produced usually by long-continued inflammation and subsequent atrophy of the conjunctiva.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xerophthalmy</value>
            <value column="1">Xerophthalmia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphias</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of fishes comprising the common swordfish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphias</value>
            <value column="1">The constellation Dorado.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphias</value>
            <value column="1">A comet shaped like a sword</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphidium</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of plants of the order Haemodraceae, having two-ranked, sword-shaped leaves.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphioid</value>
            <value column="1">Of, pertaining to, or resembling, a cetacean of the genus Xiphius or family Xiphiidae.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphiplastra</value>
            <value column="1">of Xiphiplastron</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphiplastron</value>
            <value column="1">The posterior, or fourth, lateral plate in the plastron of turtles; -- called also xiphisternum.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphisterna</value>
            <value column="1">of Xiphisternum</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphisternum</value>
            <value column="1">The posterior segment, or extremity, of the sternum; -- sometimes called metasternum, ensiform cartilage, ensiform process, or xiphoid process.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphisternum</value>
            <value column="1">The xiphiplastron.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphius</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of cetaceans having a long, pointed, bony beak, usually two tusklike teeth in the lower jaw, but no teeth in the upper jaw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphodon</value>
            <value column="1">An extinct genus of artiodactylous mammals found in the European Tertiary formations. It had slender legs, didactylous feet, and small canine teeth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphoid</value>
            <value column="1">Like a sword; ensiform.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphoid</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the xiphoid process; xiphoidian.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphoidian</value>
            <value column="1">Xiphoid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphophyllous</value>
            <value column="1">Having sword-shaped leaves.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphosura</value>
            <value column="1">See Xiphura.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xiphura</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Limuloidea. Called also Xiphosura.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylamide</value>
            <value column="1">An acid amide derivative of xylic acid, obtained as a white crystalline substance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylanthrax</value>
            <value column="1">Wood coal, or charcoal; -- so called in distinction from mineral coal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylate</value>
            <value column="1">A salt of xylic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylem</value>
            <value column="1">That portion of a fibrovascular bundle which has developed, or will develop, into wood cells; -- distinguished from phloem.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylene</value>
            <value column="1">Any of a group of three metameric hydrocarbons of the aromatic series, found in coal and wood tar, and so named because found in crude wood spirit. They are colorless, oily, inflammable liquids, C6H4.(CH3)2, being dimethyl benzenes, and are called respectively orthoxylene, metaxylene, and paraxylene. Called also xylol.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylenol</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of six metameric phenol derivatives of xylene, obtained as crystalline substances, (CH3)2.C6H3.OH.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xyletic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or designating, a complex acid related to mesitylenic acid, obtained as a white crystalline substance by the action of sodium and carbon dioxide on crude xylenol.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, derived from, or related to, xylene; specifically, designating any one of several metameric acids produced by the partial oxidation of mesitylene and pseudo-cumene.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylidic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or designating, either one of two distinct acids which are derived from xylic acid and related compounds, and are metameric with uvitic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylidine</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of six metameric hydrocarbons, (CH3)2.C6H3.NH2, resembling aniline, and related to xylene. They are liquids, or easily fusible crystalline substances, of which three are derived from metaxylene, two from orthoxylene, and one from paraxylene. They are called the amido xylenes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylindein</value>
            <value column="1">A green or blue pigment produced by Peziza in certain kinds of decayed wood, as the beech, oak, birch, etc., and extracted as an amorphous powder resembling indigo.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylite</value>
            <value column="1">A liquid hydrocarbon found in crude wood spirits.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylitone</value>
            <value column="1">A yellow oil having a geraniumlike odor, produced as a side product in making phorone; -- called also xylite oil.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylo-</value>
            <value column="1">A combining form from Gr. xy`lon wood; as in xylogen, xylograph.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylobalsamum</value>
            <value column="1">The dried twigs of a Syrian tree (Balsamodendron Gileadense).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylocarpous</value>
            <value column="1">Bearing fruit which becomes hard or woody.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylocopa</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of hymenopterous insects including the carpenter. See Carpenter bee, under Carpenter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylogen</value>
            <value column="1">Nascent wood; wood cells in a forming state.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylogen</value>
            <value column="1">Lignin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylograph</value>
            <value column="1">An engraving on wood, or the impression from such an engraving; a print by xylography.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylographer</value>
            <value column="1">One who practices xylography.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylographic</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Xylographical</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylographical</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to xylography, or wood engraving.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylography</value>
            <value column="1">The art of engraving on wood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylography</value>
            <value column="1">The art of making prints from the natural grain of wood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylography</value>
            <value column="1">A method pf printing in colors upon wood for purposes of house decoration.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xyloid</value>
            <value column="1">Resembling wood; having the nature of wood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xyloidin</value>
            <value column="1">A substance resembling pyroxylin, obtained by the action of nitric acid on starch; -- called also nitramidin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylol</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Xylene.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylonite</value>
            <value column="1">See Zylonite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylophaga</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of marine bivalves which bore holes in wood. They are allied to Pholas.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylophagan</value>
            <value column="1">One of a tribe of beetles whose larvae bore or live in wood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylophagan</value>
            <value column="1">Any species of Xylophaga.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylophagan</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of the Xylophagides.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylophagides</value>
            <value column="1">A tribe or family of dipterous flies whose larvae live in decayed wood. Some of the tropical species are very large.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylophagous</value>
            <value column="1">Eating, boring in, or destroying, wood; -- said especially of certain insect larvae, crustaceans, and mollusks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylophagous</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the genus Xylophaga.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylophilan</value>
            <value column="1">One of a tribe of beetles (Xylophili) whose larvae live on decayed wood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylophilous</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the xylophilans.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylophone</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument common among the Russians, Poles, and Tartars, consisting of a series of strips of wood or glass graduated in length to the musical scale, resting on belts of straw, and struck with two small hammers. Called in Germany strohfiedel, or straw fiddle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylophone</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument to determine the vibrative properties of different kinds of wood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xyloplastic</value>
            <value column="1">Formed of wood pulp by molds; relating to casts made of wood pulp in molds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylopyrography</value>
            <value column="1">The art or practice of burning pictures on wood with a hot iron; -- called also poker painting. See Poker picture, under Poker.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xyloquinone</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of a group of quinone compounds obtained respectively by the oxidation of certain xylidine compounds. In general they are yellow crystalline substances.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylorcin</value>
            <value column="1">A derivative of xylene obtained as a white crystalline substance which on exposure in the air becomes red; -- called also betaorcin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylostein</value>
            <value column="1">A glucoside found in the poisonous berries of a species of honeysuckle (Lonicera xylosteum), and extracted as a bitter, white, crystalline substance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylotile</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Parkesine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylotrya</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of marine bivalves closely allied to Teredo, and equally destructive to timber. One species (Xylotrya fimbriata) is very common on the Atlantic coast of the United States.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylyl</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of three metameric radicals which are characteristic respectively of the three xylenes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xylylene</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of three metameric radicals, CH2.C6H4.CH2, derived respectively from the three xylenes. Often used adjectively; as, xylylene alcohol.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xyridaceous</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to a natural order (Xyrideae) of endogenous plants, of which Xyris is the type.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xyris</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of endogenous herbs with grassy leaves and small yellow flowers in short, scaly-bracted spikes; yellow-eyed grass. There are about seventeen species in the Atlantic United States.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xyst</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Xystus</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xystarch</value>
            <value column="1">An office/ having the superintendence of the xyst.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xyster</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument for scraping bones. Y () Y, the twenty-fifth letter of the English alphabet, at the beginning of a word or syllable, except when a prefix (see Y-), is usually a fricative vocal consonant; as a prefix, and usually in the middle or at the end of a syllable, it is a vowel. See Guide to Pronunciation, // 145, 178-9, 272.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Xystus</value>
            <value column="1">A long and open portico, for athletic exercises, as wrestling, running, etc., for use in winter or in stormy weather.</value>
         
</rows> 