     
    <rows>
         
            <value column="0">KNavishness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being knavish; knavery; dishonesty.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaama</value>
            <value column="1">The hartbeest.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kabala</value>
            <value column="1">See Cabala.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kabassou</value>
            <value column="1">See Cabassou.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kabob</value>
            <value column="1">See Cabob, n. &amp; v. t.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kabook</value>
            <value column="1">A clay ironstone found in Ceylon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kabyle</value>
            <value column="1">A Berber, as in Algiers or Tunis. See Berber.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kadder</value>
            <value column="1">The jackdaw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kadi</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kadiaster</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kadiaster</value>
            <value column="1">A Turkish judge. See Cadi.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kafal</value>
            <value column="1">The Arabian name of two trees of the genus Balsamodendron, which yield a gum resin and a red aromatic wood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaffir</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kafir</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaffle</value>
            <value column="1">See Coffle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kafilah</value>
            <value column="1">See Cafila.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kafir</value>
            <value column="1">One of a race which, with the Hottentots and Bushmen, inhabit South Africa. They inhabit the country north of Cape Colony, the name being now specifically applied to the tribes living between Cape Colony and Natal; but the Zulus of Natal are true Kaffirs.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kafir</value>
            <value column="1">One of a race inhabiting Kafiristan in Central Asia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaftan</value>
            <value column="1">See Caftan.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kage</value>
            <value column="1">A chantry chapel inclosed with lattice or screen work.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kagu</value>
            <value column="1">A singular, crested, grallatorial bird (Rhinochetos jubatus), native of New Caledonia. It is gray above, paler beneath, and the feathers of the wings and tail are handsomely barred with brown, black, and gray. It is allied to the sun bittern.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaguan</value>
            <value column="1">The colugo.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kahani</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of notary public, or attorney, in the Levant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kahau</value>
            <value column="1">A long-nosed monkey (Semnopithecus nasalis), native of Borneo. The general color of the body is bright chestnut, with the under parts, shoulders, and sides of the head, golden yellow, and the top of the head and upper part of the back brown. Called also proboscis monkey.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kail</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of headless cabbage. Same as Kale, 1.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kail</value>
            <value column="1">Any cabbage, greens, or vegetables.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kail</value>
            <value column="1">A broth made with kail or other vegetables; hence, any broth; also, a dinner.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaimacam</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Caimacam.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kain</value>
            <value column="1">Poultry, etc., required by the lease to be paid in kind by a tenant to his landlord.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kainit</value>
            <value column="1">Salts of potassium used in the manufacture of fertilizers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kainite</value>
            <value column="1">A compound salt consisting chiefly of potassium chloride and magnesium sulphate, occurring at the Stassfurt salt mines in Prussian Saxony.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kainozoic</value>
            <value column="1">See Cenozoic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaique</value>
            <value column="1">See Caique.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kairine</value>
            <value column="1">A pale buff or white crystalline alkaloid derived from quinoline, and used as an antipyretic in medicine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kairoline</value>
            <value column="1">An organic base obtained from quinoline. It is used as a febrifuge, and resembles kairine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaiser</value>
            <value column="1">The ancient title of emperors of Germany assumed by King William of Prussia when crowned sovereign of the new German empire in 1871.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaka</value>
            <value column="1">A New Zealand parrot of the genus Nestor, especially the brown parrot (Nestor meridionalis).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kakapo</value>
            <value column="1">A singular nocturnal parrot (Strigops habroptilus), native of New Zealand. It lives in holes during the day, but is active at night. It resembles an owl in its colors and general appearance. It has large wings, but can fly only a short distance. Called also owl parrot, night parrot, and night kaka.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kakaralli</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of wood common in Demerara, durable in salt water, because not subject to the depredations of the sea worm and barnacle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kakistocracy</value>
            <value column="1">Government by the worst men.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kakoxene</value>
            <value column="1">See Cacoxene.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalan</value>
            <value column="1">The sea otter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalasie</value>
            <value column="1">A long-tailed monkey of Borneo (Semnopithecus rubicundus). It has a tuft of long hair on the head.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kale</value>
            <value column="1">A variety of cabbage in which the leaves do not form a head, being nearly the original or wild form of the species.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kale</value>
            <value column="1">See Kail, 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaleege</value>
            <value column="1">One of several species of large, crested, Asiatic pheasants, belonging to the genus Euplocamus, and allied to the firebacks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaleidophon</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kaleidophone</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaleidophone</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument invented by Professor Wheatstone, consisting of a reflecting knob at the end of a vibrating rod or thin plate, for making visible, in the motion of a point of light reflected from the knob, the paths or curves corresponding with the musical notes produced by the vibrations.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaleidoscope</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument invented by Sir David Brewster, which contains loose fragments of colored glass, etc., and reflecting surfaces so arranged that changes of position exhibit its contents in an endless variety of beautiful colors and symmetrical forms. It has been much employed in arts of design.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaleidoscopic</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kaleidoscopical</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaleidoscopical</value>
            <value column="1">Of, pertaining to, or formed by, a kaleidoscope; variegated.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalendar</value>
            <value column="1">See Calendar.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalendarial</value>
            <value column="1">See Calendarial.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalender</value>
            <value column="1">See 3d Calender.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalends</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Calends.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kali</value>
            <value column="1">The last and worst of the four ages of the world; -- considered to have begun B. C. 3102, and to last 432,000 years.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kali</value>
            <value column="1">The black, destroying goddess; -- called also Doorga, Anna Purna.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kali</value>
            <value column="1">The glasswort (Salsola Kali).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalif</value>
            <value column="1">See Caliph.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaliform</value>
            <value column="1">Formed like kali, or glasswort.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaligenous</value>
            <value column="1">Forming alkalies with oxygen, as some metals.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalium</value>
            <value column="1">Potassium; -- so called by the German chemists.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalki</value>
            <value column="1">The name of Vishnu in his tenth and last avatar.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalmia</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of North American shrubs with poisonous evergreen foliage and corymbs of showy flowers. Called also mountain laurel, ivy bush, lamb kill, calico bush, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalmuck</value>
            <value column="1">See Calmucks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalmuck</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of shaggy cloth, resembling bearskin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalmuck</value>
            <value column="1">A coarse, dyed, cotton cloth, made in Prussia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalong</value>
            <value column="1">A fruit bat, esp. the Indian edible fruit bat (Pteropus edulis).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaloyer</value>
            <value column="1">See Caloyer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalpa</value>
            <value column="1">One of the Brahmanic eons, a period of 4,320,000,000 years. At the end of each Kalpa the world is annihilated.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kalsomine</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Calcimine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kam</value>
            <value column="1">Crooked; awry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kama</value>
            <value column="1">The Hindoo Cupid. He is represented as a beautiful youth, with a bow of sugar cane or flowers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kamala</value>
            <value column="1">The red dusty hairs of the capsules of an East Indian tree (Mallotus Philippinensis) used for dyeing silk. It is violently emetic, and is used in the treatment of tapeworm.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kame</value>
            <value column="1">A low ridge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kami</value>
            <value column="1">A title given to the celestial gods of the first mythical dynasty of Japan and extended to the demigods of the second dynasty, and then to the long line of spiritual princes still represented by the mikado.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kamichi</value>
            <value column="1">A curious South American bird (Anhima, / Palamedea, cornuta), often domesticated by the natives and kept with poultry, which it defends against birds of prey. It has a long, slender, hornlike ornament on its head, and two sharp spurs on each wing. Although its beak, feet, and legs resemble those of gallinaceous birds, it is related in anatomical characters to the ducks and geese (Anseres). Called also horned screamer. The name is sometimes applied also to the chaja. See Chaja, and Screamer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kamptulicon</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of elastic floor cloth, made of India rubber, gutta-percha, linseed oil, and powdered cork.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kampylite</value>
            <value column="1">A variety of mimetite or arseniate of lead in hexagonal prisms of a fine orange yellow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kamsin</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Khamsin</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kamtschadales</value>
            <value column="1">An aboriginal tribe inhabiting the southern part of Kamtschatka.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kan</value>
            <value column="1">To know; to ken.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kan</value>
            <value column="1">See Khan.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kanacka</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kanaka</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kanaka</value>
            <value column="1">A native of the Sandwich Islands.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kanchil</value>
            <value column="1">A small chevrotain of the genus Tragulus, esp. T. pygmaeus, or T. kanchil, inhabiting Java, Sumatra, and adjacent islands; a deerlet. It is noted for its agility and cunning.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kand</value>
            <value column="1">Fluor spar; -- so called by Cornish miners.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kangaroo</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of numerous species of jumping marsupials of the family Macropodidae. They inhabit Australia, New Guinea, and adjacent islands, They have long and strong hind legs and a large tail, while the fore legs are comparatively short and feeble. The giant kangaroo (Macropus major) is the largest species, sometimes becoming twelve or fourteen feet in total length. The tree kangaroos, belonging to the genus Dendrolagus, live in trees; the rock kangaroos, of the genus Petrogale, inhabit rocky situations; and the brush kangaroos, of the genus Halmaturus, inhabit wooded districts. See Wallaby.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kansas</value>
            <value column="1">A tribe of Indians allied to the Winnebagoes and Osages. They formerly inhabited the region which is now the State of Kansas, but were removed to the Indian Territory.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kantian</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to Immanuel Kant, the German philosopher; conformed or relating to any or all of the philosophical doctrines of Immanuel Kant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kantian</value>
            <value column="1">A follower of Kant; a Kantist.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kantianism</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kantism</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kantism</value>
            <value column="1">The doctrine or theory of Kant; the Kantian philosophy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kantist</value>
            <value column="1">A disciple or follower of Kant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kanttry</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Cantred.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaolin</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kaoline</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaoline</value>
            <value column="1">A very pure white clay, ordinarily in the form of an impalpable powder, and used to form the paste of porcelain; China clay; porcelain clay. It is chiefly derived from the decomposition of common feldspar.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaolinization</value>
            <value column="1">The process by which feldspar is changed into kaolin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaolinize</value>
            <value column="1">To convert into kaolin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kapelle</value>
            <value column="1">A chapel; hence, the choir or orchestra of a prince's chapel; now, a musical establishment, usually orchestral.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kapellmeister</value>
            <value column="1">See Capellmeister.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kapia</value>
            <value column="1">The fossil resin of the kauri tree of New Zealand.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kapnomar</value>
            <value column="1">) See Capnomor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karagane</value>
            <value column="1">A species of gray fox found in Russia.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karaism</value>
            <value column="1">Doctrines of the Karaites.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karaite</value>
            <value column="1">A sect of Jews who adhere closely to the letter of the Scriptures, rejecting the oral law, and allowing the Talmud no binding authority; -- opposed to the Rabbinists.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karatas</value>
            <value column="1">A West Indian plant of the Pineapple family (Nidularium Karatas).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karma</value>
            <value column="1">One's acts considered as fixing one's lot in the future existence. (Theos.) The doctrine of fate as the inflexible result of cause and effect; the theory of inevitable consequence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karmathian</value>
            <value column="1">One of a Mohammedan sect founded in the ninth century by Karmat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karn</value>
            <value column="1">A pile of rocks; sometimes, the solid rock. See Cairn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karob</value>
            <value column="1">The twenty-fourth part of a grain; -- a weight used by goldsmiths.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karpholite</value>
            <value column="1">A fibrous mineral occurring in tufts of a straw-yellow color. It is a hydrous silicate of alumina and manganese.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karreo</value>
            <value column="1">One of the dry table-lands of South Africa, which often rise terracelike to considerable elevations.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karroos</value>
            <value column="1">of Karreo</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karstenite</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Anhydrite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karvel</value>
            <value column="1">See Carvel, and Caravel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karyokinesis</value>
            <value column="1">The indirect division of cells in which, prior to division of the cell protoplasm, complicated changes take place in the nucleus, attended with movement of the nuclear fibrils; -- opposed to karyostenosis. The nucleus becomes enlarged and convoluted, and finally the threads are separated into two groups which ultimately become disconnected and constitute the daughter nuclei. Called also mitosis. See Cell development, under Cell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karyokinetic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to karyokinesis; as, karyokinetic changes of cell division.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karyomiton</value>
            <value column="1">The reticular network of fine fibers, of which the nucleus of a cell is in part composed; -- in opposition to kytomiton, or the network in the body of the cell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karyoplasma</value>
            <value column="1">The protoplasmic substance of the nucleus of a cell: nucleoplasm; -- in opposition to kytoplasma, the protoplasm of the cell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Karyostenosis</value>
            <value column="1">Direct cell division (in which there is first a simple division of the nucleus, without any changes in its structure, followed by division of the protoplasm of the karyostenotic mode of nuclear division.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kasack</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Cossack.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kat</value>
            <value column="1">An Arabian shrub Catha edulis) the leaves of which are used as tea by the Arabs.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Katabolic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to katabolism; as, katabolic processes, which give rise to substances (katastates) of decreasing complexity and increasing stability.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Katabolism</value>
            <value column="1">Destructive or downward metabolism; regressive metamorphism; -- opposed to anabolism. See Disassimilation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Katastate</value>
            <value column="1">(Physiol.) A substance formed by a katabolic process; -- opposed to anastate. See Katabolic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kate</value>
            <value column="1">The brambling finch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kathetal</value>
            <value column="1">Making a right angle; perpendicular, as two lines or two sides of a triangle, which include a right angle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kathetometer</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Cathetometer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kattinumdoo</value>
            <value column="1">A caoutchouc like substance obtained from the milky juice of the East Indian Euphorbia Kattimundoo. It is used as a cement.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Katydid</value>
            <value column="1">A large, green, arboreal, orthopterous insect (Cyrtophyllus concavus) of the family Locustidae, common in the United States. The males have stridulating organs at the bases of the front wings. During the summer and autumn, in the evening, the males make a peculiar, loud, shrill sound, resembling the combination Katy-did, whence the name.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kauri</value>
            <value column="1">A lofty coniferous tree of New Zealand Agathis, / Dammara, australis), furnishing valuable timber and yielding one kind of dammar resin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kava</value>
            <value column="1">A species of Macropiper (M. methysticum), the long pepper, from the root of which an intoxicating beverage is made by the Polynesians, by a process of mastication; also, the beverage itself.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kavass</value>
            <value column="1">An armed constable; also, a government servant or courier.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kavasses</value>
            <value column="1">of Kavass</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaw</value>
            <value column="1">See Caw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kawaka</value>
            <value column="1">a New Zealand tree, the Cypress cedar (Libocedrus Doniana), having a valuable, fine-grained, reddish wood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kawn</value>
            <value column="1">An inn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kayak</value>
            <value column="1">A light canoe, made of skins stretched over a frame, and usually capable of carrying but one person, who sits amidships and uses a double-bladed paddle. It is peculiar to the Eskimos and other Arctic tribes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kayaker</value>
            <value column="1">One who uses a kayak.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kayko</value>
            <value column="1">The dog salmon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kayles</value>
            <value column="1">A game; ninepins.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kaynard</value>
            <value column="1">A lazy or cowardly person; a rascal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keck</value>
            <value column="1">To heave or to retch, as in an effort to vomit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keck</value>
            <value column="1">An effort to vomit; queasiness.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kecked</value>
            <value column="1">of Keck</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kecking</value>
            <value column="1">of Keck</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keckle</value>
            <value column="1">See Keck, v. i. &amp; n.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keckle</value>
            <value column="1">To wind old rope around, as a cable, to preserve its surface from being fretted, or to wind iron chains around, to defend from the friction of a rocky bottom, or from the ice.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keckled</value>
            <value column="1">of Keckle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keckling</value>
            <value column="1">of Keckle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keckling</value>
            <value column="1">Old rope or iron chains wound around a cable. See Keckle, v. t.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kecklish</value>
            <value column="1">Inclined to vomit; squeamish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kecksies</value>
            <value column="1">of Kecksy</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kecksy</value>
            <value column="1">The hollow stalk of an umbelliferous plant, such as the cow parsnip or the hemlock.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kecky</value>
            <value column="1">Resembling a kecksy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kedge</value>
            <value column="1">To move (a vessel) by carrying out a kedge in a boat, dropping it overboard, and hauling the vessel up to it.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kedge</value>
            <value column="1">A small anchor used whenever a large one can be dispensed witch. See Kedge, v. t., and Anchor, n.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kedged</value>
            <value column="1">of Kedge</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kedger</value>
            <value column="1">A small anchor; a kedge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kedging</value>
            <value column="1">of Kedge</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kedlook</value>
            <value column="1">See Charlock.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kee</value>
            <value column="1">See Kie, Ky, and Kine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keech</value>
            <value column="1">A mass or lump of fat rolled up by the butcher.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keel</value>
            <value column="1">To cool; to skim or stir.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keel</value>
            <value column="1">A brewer's cooling vat; a keelfat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keel</value>
            <value column="1">A longitudinal timber, or series of timbers scarfed together, extending from stem to stern along the bottom of a vessel. It is the principal timber of the vessel, and, by means of the ribs attached on each side, supports the vessel's frame. In an iron vessel, a combination of plates supplies the place of the keel of a wooden ship. See Illust. of Keelson.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keel</value>
            <value column="1">Fig.: The whole ship.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keel</value>
            <value column="1">A barge or lighter, used on the Type for carrying coal from Newcastle; also, a barge load of coal, twenty-one tons, four cwt.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keel</value>
            <value column="1">The two lowest petals of the corolla of a papilionaceous flower, united and inclosing the stamens and pistil; a carina. See Carina.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keel</value>
            <value column="1">A projecting ridge along the middle of a flat or curved surface.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keel</value>
            <value column="1">To traverse with a keel; to navigate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keel</value>
            <value column="1">To turn up the keel; to show the bottom.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keelage</value>
            <value column="1">The right of demanding a duty or toll for a ship entering a port; also, the duty or toll.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeled</value>
            <value column="1">of Keel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeled</value>
            <value column="1">Keel-shaped; having a longitudinal prominence on the back; as, a keeled leaf.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeled</value>
            <value column="1">Having a median ridge; carinate; as, a keeled scale.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeler</value>
            <value column="1">One employed in managing a Newcastle keel; -- called also keelman.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeler</value>
            <value column="1">A small or shallow tub; esp., one used for holding materials for calking ships, or one used for washing dishes, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keelfat</value>
            <value column="1">A cooler; a vat for cooling wort, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keelhaul</value>
            <value column="1">To haul under the keel of a ship, by ropes attached to the yardarms on each side. It was formerly practiced as a punishment in the Dutch and English navies.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keelhauled</value>
            <value column="1">of Keelhaul</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keelhauling</value>
            <value column="1">of Keelhaul</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeling</value>
            <value column="1">of Keel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeling</value>
            <value column="1">A cod.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keelivine</value>
            <value column="1">A pencil of black or red lead; -- called also keelyvine pen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keelman</value>
            <value column="1">See Keeler, 1.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keelrake</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Keelhaul.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keels</value>
            <value column="1">Ninepins. See Kayles.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keelson</value>
            <value column="1">A piece of timber in a ship laid on the middle of the floor timbers over the keel, and binding the floor timbers to the keel; in iron vessels, a structure of plates, situated like the keelson of a timber ship.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keelvat</value>
            <value column="1">See Keelfat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keen</value>
            <value column="1">Sharp; having a fine edge or point; as, a keen razor, or a razor with a keen edge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keen</value>
            <value column="1">Acute of mind; sharp; penetrating; having or expressing mental acuteness; as, a man of keen understanding; a keen look; keen features.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keen</value>
            <value column="1">Bitter; piercing; acrimonious; cutting; stinging; severe; as, keen satire or sarcasm.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keen</value>
            <value column="1">Piercing; penetrating; cutting; sharp; -- applied to cold, wind, etc, ; as, a keen wind; the cold is very keen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keen</value>
            <value column="1">Eager; vehement; fierce; as, a keen appetite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keen</value>
            <value column="1">To sharpen; to make cold.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keen</value>
            <value column="1">A prolonged wail for a deceased person. Cf. Coranach.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keen</value>
            <value column="1">To wail as a keener does.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keener</value>
            <value column="1">A professional mourner who wails at a funeral.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keenly</value>
            <value column="1">In a keen manner.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keenness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being keen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To care; to desire.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To hold; to restrain from departure or removal; not to let go of; to retain in one's power or possession; not to lose; to retain; to detain.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To cause to remain in a given situation or condition; to maintain unchanged; to hold or preserve in any state or tenor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To have in custody; to have in some place for preservation; to take charge of.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To preserve from danger, harm, or loss; to guard.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To preserve from discovery or publicity; not to communicate, reveal, or betray, as a secret.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To attend upon; to have the care of; to tend.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To record transactions, accounts, or events in; as, to keep books, a journal, etc. ; also, to enter (as accounts, records, etc. ) in a book.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To maintain, as an establishment, institution, or the like; to conduct; to manage; as, to keep store.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To supply with necessaries of life; to entertain; as, to keep boarders.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To have in one's service; to have and maintain, as an assistant, a servant, a mistress, a horse, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To have habitually in stock for sale.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To continue in, as a course or mode of action; not to intermit or fall from; to hold to; to maintain; as, to keep silence; to keep one's word; to keep possession.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To observe; to adhere to; to fulfill; not to swerve from or violate; to practice or perform, as duty; not to neglect; to be faithful to.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To confine one's self to; not to quit; to remain in; as, to keep one's house, room, bed, etc. ; hence, to haunt; to frequent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To observe duty, as a festival, etc. ; to celebrate; to solemnize; as, to keep a feast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To remain in any position or state; to continue; to abide; to stay; as, to keep at a distance; to keep aloft; to keep near; to keep in the house; to keep before or behind; to keep in favor; to keep out of company, or out reach.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To last; to endure; to remain unimpaired.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To reside for a time; to lodge; to dwell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To take care; to be solicitous; to watch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">To be in session; as, school keeps to-day.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">The act or office of keeping; custody; guard; care; heed; charge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">The state of being kept; hence, the resulting condition; case; as, to be in good keep.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">The means or provisions by which one is kept; maintenance; support; as, the keep of a horse.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">That which keeps or protects; a stronghold; a fortress; a castle; specifically, the strongest and securest part of a castle, often used as a place of residence by the lord of the castle, especially during a siege; the donjon. See Illust. of Castle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">That which is kept in charge; a charge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keep</value>
            <value column="1">A cap for retaining anything, as a journal box, in place.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeper</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, keeps; one who, or that which, holds or has possession of anything.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeper</value>
            <value column="1">One who retains in custody; one who has the care of a prison and the charge of prisoners.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeper</value>
            <value column="1">One who has the care, custody, or superintendence of anything; as, the keeper of a park, a pound, of sheep, of a gate, etc. ; the keeper of attached property; hence, one who saves from harm; a defender; a preserver.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeper</value>
            <value column="1">One who remains or keeps in a place or position.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeper</value>
            <value column="1">A ring, strap, clamp, or any device for holding an object in place; as: (a) The box on a door jamb into which the bolt of a lock protrudes, when shot. (b) A ring serving to keep another ring on the finger. (c) A loop near the buckle of a strap to receive the end of the strap.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeper</value>
            <value column="1">A fruit that keeps well; as, the Roxbury Russet is a good keeper.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keepership</value>
            <value column="1">The office or position of a keeper.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeping</value>
            <value column="1">of Keep</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeping</value>
            <value column="1">A holding; restraint; custody; guard; charge; care; preservation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeping</value>
            <value column="1">Maintenance; support; provision; feed; as, the cattle have good keeping.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeping</value>
            <value column="1">Conformity; congruity; harmony; consistency; as, these subjects are in keeping with each other.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeping</value>
            <value column="1">Harmony or correspondence between the different parts of a work of art; as, the foreground of this painting is not in keeping.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keepsake</value>
            <value column="1">Anything kept, or given to be kept, for the sake of the giver; a token of friendship.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keesh</value>
            <value column="1">See Kish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeve</value>
            <value column="1">A vat or tub in which the mash is made; a mash tub.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeve</value>
            <value column="1">A bleaching vat; a kier.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeve</value>
            <value column="1">A large vat used in dressing ores.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeve</value>
            <value column="1">To set in a keeve, or tub, for fermentation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeve</value>
            <value column="1">To heave; to tilt, as a cart.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeved</value>
            <value column="1">of Keeve</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keever</value>
            <value column="1">See Keeve, n.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keeving</value>
            <value column="1">of Keeve</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keffe-kil</value>
            <value column="1">See Kiefekil.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keg</value>
            <value column="1">A small cask or barrel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keilhau-ite</value>
            <value column="1">A mineral of a brownish black color, related to titanite in form. It consists chiefly of silica, titanium dioxide, lime, and yttria.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keir</value>
            <value column="1">See Kier.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keitloa</value>
            <value column="1">A black, two-horned, African rhinoceros (Atelodus keitloa). It has the posterior horn about as long as the anterior one, or even longer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keld</value>
            <value column="1">Having a kell or covering; webbed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kele</value>
            <value column="1">To cool.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kell</value>
            <value column="1">A kiln.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kell</value>
            <value column="1">A sort of pottage; kale. See Kale, 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kell</value>
            <value column="1">The caul; that which covers or envelops as a caul; a net; a fold; a film.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kell</value>
            <value column="1">The cocoon or chrysalis of an insect.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keloid</value>
            <value column="1">Applied to a variety of tumor forming hard, flat, irregular excrescences upon the skin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keloid</value>
            <value column="1">A keloid tumor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelotomy</value>
            <value column="1">See Celotomy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelp</value>
            <value column="1">The calcined ashes of seaweed, -- formerly much used in the manufacture of glass, now used in the manufacture of iodine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelp</value>
            <value column="1">Any large blackish seaweed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelpfish</value>
            <value column="1">A small California food fish (Heterostichus rostratus), living among kelp. The name is also applied to species of the genus Platyglossus.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelpie</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kelpy</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelpies</value>
            <value column="1">of Kelpy</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelpware</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Kelp, 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelpy</value>
            <value column="1">An imaginary spirit of the waters, horselike in form, vulgarly believed to warn, by preternatural noises and lights, those who are to be drowned.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelson</value>
            <value column="1">See Keelson.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelt</value>
            <value column="1">See Kilt, n.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelt</value>
            <value column="1">Cloth with the nap, generally of native black wool.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelt</value>
            <value column="1">A salmon after spawning.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelt</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Celt, one of Celtic race.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kelter</value>
            <value column="1">Regular order or proper condition.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keltic</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Celtic, a. &amp; n.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kemb</value>
            <value column="1">To comb.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kembed</value>
            <value column="1">of Kemb</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kembing</value>
            <value column="1">of Kemb</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kemelin</value>
            <value column="1">A tub; a brewer's vessel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kemp</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kempty</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kempe</value>
            <value column="1">Rough; shaggy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kemps</value>
            <value column="1">The long flower stems of the ribwort plantain (Plantago Lanceolata).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kempt</value>
            <value column="1">of Kemb</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kempt</value>
            <value column="1">p. p. of Kemb.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kempty</value>
            <value column="1">Coarse, rough hair wool or fur, injuring its quality.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ken</value>
            <value column="1">A house; esp., one which is a resort for thieves.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ken</value>
            <value column="1">To know; to understand; to take cognizance of.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ken</value>
            <value column="1">To recognize; to descry; to discern.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ken</value>
            <value column="1">To look around.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ken</value>
            <value column="1">Cognizance; view; especially, reach of sight or knowledge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kendal</value>
            <value column="1">A cloth colored green by dye obtained from the woad-waxen, formerly used by Flemish weavers at Kendal, in Westmoreland, England.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kendal green</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kendal</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kenned</value>
            <value column="1">of Ken</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kennel</value>
            <value column="1">The water course of a street; a little canal or channel; a gutter; also, a puddle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kennel</value>
            <value column="1">A house for a dog or for dogs, or for a pack of hounds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kennel</value>
            <value column="1">A pack of hounds, or a collection of dogs.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kennel</value>
            <value column="1">The hole of a fox or other beast; a haunt.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kennel</value>
            <value column="1">To lie or lodge; to dwell, as a dog or a fox.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kennel</value>
            <value column="1">To put or keep in a kennel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kennel coal</value>
            <value column="1">See Cannel coal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kenneled</value>
            <value column="1">of Kennel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kennelled</value>
            <value column="1">of Kennel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kennelling</value>
            <value column="1">of Kennel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kenning</value>
            <value column="1">of Ken</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kenning</value>
            <value column="1">Range of sight.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kenning</value>
            <value column="1">The limit of vision at sea, being a distance of about twenty miles.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keno</value>
            <value column="1">A gambling game, a variety of the game of lotto, played with balls or knobs, numbered, and cards also numbered.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kenogenesis</value>
            <value column="1">Modified evolution, in which nonprimitive characters make their appearance in consequence of a secondary adaptation of the embryo to the peculiar conditions of its environment; -- distinguished from palingenesis.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kenogenetic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to kenogenesis; as, kenogenetic processes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kenspeckle</value>
            <value column="1">Having so marked an appearance as easily to be recognized.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kent bugle</value>
            <value column="1">A curved bugle, having six finger keys or stops, by means of which the performer can play upon every key in the musical scale; -- called also keyed bugle, and key bugle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kentle</value>
            <value column="1">A hundred weight; a quintal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kentledge</value>
            <value column="1">Pigs of iron used for ballast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kentucky</value>
            <value column="1">One of the United States.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kephalin</value>
            <value column="1">One of a group of nitrogenous phosphorized principles, supposed by Thudichum to exist in brain tissue.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kept</value>
            <value column="1">of Keep</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kept</value>
            <value column="1">of Keep.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keramic</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Ceramic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keramics</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Ceramics.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keramographic</value>
            <value column="1">Suitable to be written upon; capable of being written upon, as a slate; -- said especially of a certain kind of globe.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerana</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of long trumpet, used among the Persians.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerargyrite</value>
            <value column="1">See Cerargyrite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerasin</value>
            <value column="1">A nitrogenous substance free from phosphorus, supposed to be present in the brain; a body closely related to cerebrin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerasine</value>
            <value column="1">Resembling horn; horny; corneous.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keratin</value>
            <value column="1">A nitrogenous substance, or mixture of substances, containing sulphur in a loose state of combination, and forming the chemical basis of epidermal tissues, such as horn, hair, feathers, and the like. It is an insoluble substance, and, unlike elastin, is not dissolved even by gastric or pancreatic juice. By decomposition with sulphuric acid it yields leucin and tyrosin, as does albumin. Called also epidermose.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keratitis</value>
            <value column="1">Inflammation of the cornea.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keratode</value>
            <value column="1">See Keratose.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keratogenous</value>
            <value column="1">Producing horn; as, the keratogenous membrane within the horny hoof of the horse.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keratoidea</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Keratosa.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keratome</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument for dividing the cornea in operations for cataract.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keratonyxis</value>
            <value column="1">The operation of removing a cataract by thrusting a needle through the cornea of the eye, and breaking up the opaque mass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keratophyte</value>
            <value column="1">A gorgonian coral having a horny axis.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keratosa</value>
            <value column="1">An order of sponges having a skeleton composed of hornlike fibers. It includes the commercial sponges.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keratose</value>
            <value column="1">A tough, horny animal substance entering into the composition of the skeleton of sponges, and other invertebrates; -- called also keratode.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keratose</value>
            <value column="1">Containing hornlike fibers or fibers of keratose; belonging to the Keratosa.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keraunograph</value>
            <value column="1">A figure or picture impressed by lightning upon the human body or elsewhere.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerb</value>
            <value column="1">See Curb.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerbstone</value>
            <value column="1">See Curbstone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kercher</value>
            <value column="1">A kerchief.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerchered</value>
            <value column="1">Covered, or bound round, with a kercher.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerchief</value>
            <value column="1">A square of fine linen worn by women as a covering for the head; hence, anything similar in form or material, worn for ornament on other parts of the person; -- mostly used in compounds; as, neckerchief; breastkerchief; and later, handkerchief.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerchief</value>
            <value column="1">A lady who wears a kerchief.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerchiefed</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kerchieft</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerchiefs</value>
            <value column="1">of Kerchief</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerchieft</value>
            <value column="1">Dressed; hooded; covered; wearing a kerchief.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerf</value>
            <value column="1">A notch, channel, or slit made in any material by cutting or sawing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerish</value>
            <value column="1">Clownish; boorish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerite</value>
            <value column="1">A compound in which tar or asphaltum combined with animal or vegetable oils is vulcanized by sulphur, the product closely resembling rubber; -- used principally as an insulating material in telegraphy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerl</value>
            <value column="1">See Carl.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kermes</value>
            <value column="1">The dried bodies of the females of a scale insect (Coccus ilicis), allied to the cochineal insect, and found on several species of oak near the Mediterranean. They are round, about the size of a pea, contain coloring matter analogous to carmine, and are used in dyeing. They were anciently thought to be of a vegetable nature, and were used in medicine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kermes</value>
            <value column="1">A small European evergreen oak (Quercus coccifera) on which the kermes insect (Coccus ilicis) feeds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kermesse</value>
            <value column="1">See Kirmess.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kern</value>
            <value column="1">A light-armed foot soldier of the ancient militia of Ireland and Scotland; -- distinguished from gallowglass, and often used as a term of contempt.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kern</value>
            <value column="1">Any kind of boor or low-lived person.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kern</value>
            <value column="1">An idler; a vagabond.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kern</value>
            <value column="1">A part of the face of a type which projects beyond the body, or shank.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kern</value>
            <value column="1">To form with a kern. See 2d Kern.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kern</value>
            <value column="1">A churn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kern</value>
            <value column="1">A hand mill. See Quern.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kern</value>
            <value column="1">To harden, as corn in ripening.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kern</value>
            <value column="1">To take the form of kernels; to granulate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerned</value>
            <value column="1">of Kern</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerned</value>
            <value column="1">Having part of the face projecting beyond the body or shank; -- said of type.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kernel</value>
            <value column="1">The essential part of a seed; all that is within the seed walls; the edible substance contained in the shell of a nut; hence, anything included in a shell, husk, or integument; as, the kernel of a nut. See Illust. of Endocarp.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kernel</value>
            <value column="1">A single seed or grain; as, a kernel of corn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kernel</value>
            <value column="1">A small mass around which other matter is concreted; a nucleus; a concretion or hard lump in the flesh.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kernel</value>
            <value column="1">The central, substantial or essential part of anything; the gist; the core; as, the kernel of an argument.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kernel</value>
            <value column="1">To harden or ripen into kernels; to produce kernels.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerneled</value>
            <value column="1">of Kernel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerneled</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kernelled</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerneling</value>
            <value column="1">of Kernel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kernelled</value>
            <value column="1">of Kernel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kernelled</value>
            <value column="1">Having a kernel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kernelling</value>
            <value column="1">of Kernel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kernelly</value>
            <value column="1">Full of kernels; resembling kernels; of the nature of kernels.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerning</value>
            <value column="1">of Kern</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerolite</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Cerolite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerosene</value>
            <value column="1">An oil used for illuminating purposes, formerly obtained from the distillation of mineral wax, bituminous shale, etc., and hence called also coal oil. It is now produced in immense quantities, chiefly by the distillation and purification of petroleum. It consists chiefly of several hydrocarbons of the methane series.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kers</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kerse</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerse</value>
            <value column="1">A cress.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kersey</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of coarse, woolen cloth, usually ribbed, woven from wool of long staple.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerseymere</value>
            <value column="1">See Cassimere.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerseynette</value>
            <value column="1">See Cassinette.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerseys</value>
            <value column="1">of Kersey</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerve</value>
            <value column="1">To carve.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kerver</value>
            <value column="1">A carver.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kesar</value>
            <value column="1">See Kaiser.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keslop</value>
            <value column="1">The stomach of a calf, prepared for rennet.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kess</value>
            <value column="1">To kiss.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kest</value>
            <value column="1">of Cast.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kestrel</value>
            <value column="1">A small, slender European hawk (Falco alaudarius), allied to the sparrow hawk. Its color is reddish fawn, streaked and spotted with white and black. Also called windhover and stannel. The name is also applied to other allied species.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ket</value>
            <value column="1">Carrion; any filth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ketch</value>
            <value column="1">An almost obsolete form of vessel, with a mainmast and a mizzenmast, -- usually from one hundred to two hundred and fifty tons burden.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ketch</value>
            <value column="1">A hangman. See Jack Ketch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ketch</value>
            <value column="1">To catch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ketchup</value>
            <value column="1">A sauce. See Catchup.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ketine</value>
            <value column="1">One of a series of organic bases obtained by the reduction of certain isonitroso compounds of the ketones. In general they are unstable oily substances having a pungent aromatic odor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ketmie</value>
            <value column="1">The name of certain African species of Hibiscus, cultivated for the acid of their mucilage.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ketol</value>
            <value column="1">One of a series of series of complex nitrogenous substances, represented by methyl ketol and related to indol.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ketone</value>
            <value column="1">One of a large class of organic substances resembling the aldehydes, obtained by the distillation of certain salts of organic acids and consisting of carbonyl (CO) united with two hydrocarbon radicals. In general the ketones are colorless volatile liquids having a pungent ethereal odor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ketonic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or derived from, a ketone; as, a ketonic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kettle</value>
            <value column="1">A metallic vessel, with a wide mouth, often without a cover, used for heating and boiling water or other liguids.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kettledrum</value>
            <value column="1">A drum made of thin copper in the form of a hemispherical kettle, with parchment stretched over the mouth of it.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kettledrum</value>
            <value column="1">An informal social party at which a light collation is offered, held in the afternoon or early evening. Cf. Drum, n., 4 and 5.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kettledrummer</value>
            <value column="1">One who plays on a kettledrum.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keuper</value>
            <value column="1">The upper division of the European Triassic. See Chart of Geology.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keved</value>
            <value column="1">of Key</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kevel</value>
            <value column="1">A strong cleat to which large ropes are belayed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kevel</value>
            <value column="1">A stone mason's hammer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kevel</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kevin</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kever</value>
            <value column="1">i. To cover.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keverchief</value>
            <value column="1">A kerchief.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kevin</value>
            <value column="1">The gazelle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kex</value>
            <value column="1">A weed; a kecksy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kex</value>
            <value column="1">A dry husk or covering.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument by means of which the bolt of a lock is shot or drawn; usually, a removable metal instrument fitted to the mechanism of a particular lock and operated by turning in its place.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument which is turned like a key in fastening or adjusting any mechanism; as, a watch key; a bed key, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">That part of an instrument or machine which serves as the means of operating it; as, a telegraph key; the keys of a pianoforte, or of a typewriter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">A position or condition which affords entrance, control, pr possession, etc.; as, the key of a line of defense; the key of a country; the key of a political situation. Hence, that which serves to unlock, open, discover, or solve something unknown or difficult; as, the key to a riddle; the key to a problem.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">That part of a mechanism which serves to lock up, make fast, or adjust to position.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">A piece of wood used as a wedge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">The last board of a floor when laid down.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">A keystone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">That part of the plastering which is forced through between the laths and holds the rest in place.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">A wedge to unite two or more pieces, or adjust their relative position; a cotter; a forelock.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">A bar, pin or wedge, to secure a crank, pulley, coupling, etc., upon a shaft, and prevent relative turning; sometimes holding by friction alone, but more frequently by its resistance to shearing, being usually embedded partly in the shaft and partly in the crank, pulley, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">An indehiscent, one-seeded fruit furnished with a wing, as the fruit of the ash and maple; a samara; -- called also key fruit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1"><![CDATA[A family of tones whose regular members are called diatonic tones, and named key tone (or tonic) or one (or eight), mediant or three, dominant or five, subdominant or four, submediant or six, supertonic or two, and subtonic or seven. Chromatic tones are temporary members of a key, under such names as " sharp four," "flat seven," etc. Scales and tunes of every variety are made from the tones of a key.]]></value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">The fundamental tone of a movement to which its modulations are referred, and with which it generally begins and ends; keynote.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">Fig: The general pitch or tone of a sentence or utterance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key</value>
            <value column="1">To fasten or secure firmly; to fasten or tighten with keys or wedges.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key tone</value>
            <value column="1">See Keynote.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Key-cold</value>
            <value column="1">Cold as a metallic key; lifeless.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keyage</value>
            <value column="1">Wharfage; quayage.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keyboard</value>
            <value column="1">The whole arrangement, or one range, of the keys of an organ, typewriter, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keyed</value>
            <value column="1">Furnished with keys; as, a keyed instrument; also, set to a key, as a tune.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keyhole</value>
            <value column="1">A hole or apertupe in a door or lock, for receiving a key.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keyhole</value>
            <value column="1">A hole or excavation in beams intended to be joined together, to receive the key which fastens them.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keyhole</value>
            <value column="1">a mortise for a key or cotter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keying</value>
            <value column="1">of Key</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keynote</value>
            <value column="1">The tonic or first tone of the scale in which a piece or passage is written; the fundamental tone of the chord, to which all the modulations of the piece are referred; -- called also key tone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keynote</value>
            <value column="1">The fundamental fact or idea; that which gives the key; as, the keynote of a policy or a sermon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keyseat</value>
            <value column="1">To form a key seat, as by cutting. See Key seat, under Key.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keystone</value>
            <value column="1">The central or topmost stone of an arch. This in some styles is made different in size from the other voussoirs, or projects, or is decorated with carving. See Illust. of Arch.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Keyway</value>
            <value column="1">See Key way, under Key.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Khaliff</value>
            <value column="1">See Caliph.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Khamsin</value>
            <value column="1">A hot southwesterly wind in Egypt, coming from the Sahara.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Khamsin</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Kamsin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Khan</value>
            <value column="1">A king; a prince; a chief; a governor; -- so called among the Tartars, Turks, and Persians, and in countries now or formerly governed by them.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Khan</value>
            <value column="1">An Eastern inn or caravansary.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Khanate</value>
            <value column="1">Dominion or jurisdiction of a khan.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Khaya</value>
            <value column="1">A lofty West African tree (Khaya Senegalensis), related to the mahogany, which it resembles in the quality of the wood. The bark is used as a febrifuge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Khedive</value>
            <value column="1">A governor or viceroy; -- a title granted in 1867 by the sultan of Turkey to the ruler of Egypt.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Khenna</value>
            <value column="1">See Henna.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kholah</value>
            <value column="1">The Indian jackal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kholsun</value>
            <value column="1">The dhole.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Khutbah</value>
            <value column="1">An address or public prayer read from the steps of the pulpit in Mohammedan mosques, offering glory to God, praising Mohammed and his descendants, and the ruling princes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiabooca wood</value>
            <value column="1">See Kyaboca wood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiang</value>
            <value column="1">The dziggetai.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kibble</value>
            <value column="1">To bruise; to grind coarsely; as, kibbled oats.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kibble</value>
            <value column="1">A large iron bucket used in Cornwall and Wales for raising ore out of mines.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kibblings</value>
            <value column="1">Portions of small fish used for bait on the banks of Newfoundland.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kibe</value>
            <value column="1">A chap or crack in the flesh occasioned by cold; an ulcerated chilblain.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kibed</value>
            <value column="1">Chapped; cracked with cold; affected with chilblains; as kibed heels.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kibitka</value>
            <value column="1">A tent used by the Kirghiz Tartars.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kibitka</value>
            <value column="1">A rude kind of Russian vehicle, on wheels or on runners, sometimes covered with cloth or leather, and often used as a movable habitation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kibitkas</value>
            <value column="1">of Kibitka</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiblah</value>
            <value column="1">See Keblah.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiby</value>
            <value column="1">Affected with kibes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kichil</value>
            <value column="1">See Kechil.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kick</value>
            <value column="1">To strike, thrust, or hit violently with the foot; as, a horse kicks a groom; a man kicks a dog.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kick</value>
            <value column="1">To thrust out the foot or feet with violence; to strike out with the foot or feet, as in defense or in bad temper; esp., to strike backward, as a horse does, or to have a habit of doing so. Hence, figuratively: To show ugly resistance, opposition, or hostility; to spurn.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kick</value>
            <value column="1">To recoil; -- said of a musket, cannon, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kick</value>
            <value column="1">A blow with the foot or feet; a striking or thrust with the foot.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kick</value>
            <value column="1">The projection on the tang of the blade of a pocket knife, which prevents the edge of the blade from striking the spring. See Illust. of Pocketknife.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kick</value>
            <value column="1">A projection in a mold, to form a depression in the surface of the brick.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kick</value>
            <value column="1">The recoil of a musket or other firearm, when discharged.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kickable</value>
            <value column="1">Capable or deserving of being kicked.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kickapoos</value>
            <value column="1">A tribe of Indians which formerly occupied the region of Northern Illinois, allied in language to the Sacs and Foxes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kicker</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, kicks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kicking</value>
            <value column="1">of Kick</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kickshaw</value>
            <value column="1">See Kickshaws, the correct singular.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kickshaws</value>
            <value column="1">Something fantastical; any trifling, trumpery thing; a toy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kickshaws</value>
            <value column="1">A fancy dish; a titbit; a delicacy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kickshawses</value>
            <value column="1">of Kickshaws</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kickshoe</value>
            <value column="1">A kickshaws.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kicksy-wicksy</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kicky-wisky</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kicksy-wicksy</value>
            <value column="1">Fantastic; restless; as, kicksy-wicksy flames.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kickup</value>
            <value column="1">The water thrush or accentor.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kicky-wisky</value>
            <value column="1">That which is restless and uneasy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kicred</value>
            <value column="1">of Kick</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kid</value>
            <value column="1">A young goat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kid</value>
            <value column="1">A young child or infant; hence, a simple person, easily imposed on.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kid</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of leather made of the skin of the young goat, or of the skin of rats, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kid</value>
            <value column="1">Gloves made of kid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kid</value>
            <value column="1">A small wooden mess tub; -- a name given by sailors to one in which they receive their food.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kid</value>
            <value column="1">To bring forth a young goat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kid</value>
            <value column="1">A fagot; a bundle of heath and furze.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kid</value>
            <value column="1">of Kythe.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kid</value>
            <value column="1">See Kiddy, v. t.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidde</value>
            <value column="1">of Kythe.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidde</value>
            <value column="1">of Kithe</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidded</value>
            <value column="1">of Kid</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidderminster</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of ingrain carpeting, named from the English town where formerly most of it was manufactured.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiddier</value>
            <value column="1">A huckster; a cadger.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidding</value>
            <value column="1">of Kid</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiddle</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of basketwork wear in a river, for catching fish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiddow</value>
            <value column="1">The guillemot.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiddy</value>
            <value column="1">To deceive; to outwit; to hoax.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiddy</value>
            <value column="1">A young fellow; formerly, a low thief.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiddyish</value>
            <value column="1">Frolicsome; sportive.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidfox</value>
            <value column="1">A young fox.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidling</value>
            <value column="1">A young kid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidnap</value>
            <value column="1">To take (any one) by force or fear, and against one's will, with intent to carry to another place.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidnaped</value>
            <value column="1">of Kidnap</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidnaper</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kidnapper</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidnaping</value>
            <value column="1">of Kidnap</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidnapped</value>
            <value column="1">of Kidnap</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidnapper</value>
            <value column="1">One who steals or forcibly carries away a human being; a manstealer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidnapping</value>
            <value column="1">of Kidnap</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidney</value>
            <value column="1">A glandular organ which excretes urea and other waste products from the animal body; a urinary gland.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidney</value>
            <value column="1">Habit; disposition; sort; kind.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidney</value>
            <value column="1">A waiter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidney-form</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kidney-shaped</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidney-shaped</value>
            <value column="1">Having the form or shape of a kidney; reniform; as, a kidney-shaped leaf.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidneys</value>
            <value column="1">of Kidney</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidneywort</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of saxifrage (Saxifrage stellaris).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kidneywort</value>
            <value column="1">The navelwort.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kie</value>
            <value column="1">Kine; cows.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiefekil</value>
            <value column="1">A species of clay; meerschaum.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kier</value>
            <value column="1">A large tub or vat in which goods are subjected to the action of hot lye or bleaching liquor; -- also called keeve.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kieselguhr</value>
            <value column="1">Siliceous earth; specifically, porous infusorial earth, used as an absorbent of nitroglycerin in the manufacture of dynamite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kieserite</value>
            <value column="1">Hydrous sulphate of magnesia found at the salt mines of Stassfurt, Prussian Saxony.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kieve</value>
            <value column="1">See Keeve, n.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kike</value>
            <value column="1">To gaze; to stare.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kike</value>
            <value column="1">To kick.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilderkin</value>
            <value column="1">A small barrel; an old liquid measure containing eighteen English beer gallons, or nearly twenty-two gallons, United States measure.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kill</value>
            <value column="1">A kiln.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kill</value>
            <value column="1">A channel or arm of the sea; a river; a stream; as, the channel between Staten Island and Bergen Neck is the Kill van Kull, or the Kills; -- used also in composition; as, Schuylkill, Catskill, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kill</value>
            <value column="1">To deprive of life, animal or vegetable, in any manner or by any means; to render inanimate; to put to death; to slay.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kill</value>
            <value column="1">To destroy; to ruin; as, to kill one's chances; to kill the sale of a book.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kill</value>
            <value column="1">To cause to cease; to quell; to calm; to still; as, in seamen's language, a shower of rain kills the wind.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kill</value>
            <value column="1">To destroy the effect of; to counteract; to neutralize; as, alkali kills acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kill-joy</value>
            <value column="1">One who causes gloom or grief; a dispiriting person.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killdee</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Killdeer</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killdeer</value>
            <value column="1">A small American plover (Aegialitis vocifera).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killed</value>
            <value column="1">of Kill</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killer</value>
            <value column="1">One who deprives of life; one who, or that which, kills.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killer</value>
            <value column="1">A voracious, toothed whale of the genus Orca, of which several species are known.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killesse</value>
            <value column="1">A gutter, groove, or channel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killesse</value>
            <value column="1">A hipped roof.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killifish</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several small American cyprinodont fishes of the genus Fundulus and allied genera. They live equally well in fresh and brackish water, or even in the sea. They are usually striped or barred with black. Called also minnow, and brook fish. See Minnow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killigrew</value>
            <value column="1">The Cornish chough. See under Chough.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killikinick</value>
            <value column="1">See Kinnikinic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killing</value>
            <value column="1">of Kill</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killing</value>
            <value column="1">Literally, that kills; having power to kill; fatal; in a colloquial sense, conquering; captivating; irresistible.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killock</value>
            <value column="1">A small anchor; also, a kind of anchor formed by a stone inclosed by pieces of wood fastened together.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Killow</value>
            <value column="1">An earth of a blackish or deep blue color.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiln</value>
            <value column="1">A large stove or oven; a furnace of brick or stone, or a heated chamber, for the purpose of hardening, burning, or drying anything; as, a kiln for baking or hardening earthen vessels; a kiln for drying grain, meal, lumber, etc.; a kiln for calcining limestone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiln</value>
            <value column="1">A furnace for burning bricks; a brickkiln.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiln-dry</value>
            <value column="1">To dry in a kiln; as, to kiln-dry meal or grain.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilnhole</value>
            <value column="1">The mouth or opening of an oven or kiln.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilo</value>
            <value column="1">An abbreviation of Kilogram.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilogram</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kilogramme</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilogramme</value>
            <value column="1">A measure of weight, being a thousand grams, equal to 2.2046 pounds avoirdupois (15,432.34 grains). It is equal to the weight of a cubic decimeter of distilled water at the temperature of maximum density, or 39 Fahrenheit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilogrammeter</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kilogrammetre</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilogrammetre</value>
            <value column="1">A measure of energy or work done, being the amount expended in raising one kilogram through the height of one meter, in the latitude of Paris.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiloliter</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kilolitre</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilolitre</value>
            <value column="1">A measure of capacity equal to a cubic meter, or a thousand liters. It is equivalent to 35.315 cubic feet, and to 220.04 imperial gallons, or 264.18 American gallons of 321 cubic inches.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilometer</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kilometre</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilometre</value>
            <value column="1">A measure of length, being a thousand meters. It is equal to 3,280.8 feet, or 62137 of a mile.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilos</value>
            <value column="1">of Kilo</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilostere</value>
            <value column="1">A cubic measure containing 1000 cubic meters, and equivalent to 35,315 cubic feet.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilowatt</value>
            <value column="1">One thousand watts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilt</value>
            <value column="1">p. p. from Kill.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilt</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of short petticoat, reaching from the waist to the knees, worn in the Highlands of Scotland by men, and in the Lowlands by young boys; a filibeg.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilt</value>
            <value column="1">To tuck up; to truss up, as the clothes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilted</value>
            <value column="1">of Kilt</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilted</value>
            <value column="1">Having on a kilt.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilted</value>
            <value column="1">Plaited after the manner of kilting.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilted</value>
            <value column="1">Tucked or fastened up; -- said of petticoats, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilter</value>
            <value column="1">See Kelter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilting</value>
            <value column="1">of Kilt</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kilting</value>
            <value column="1">A perpendicular arrangement of flat, single plaits, each plait being folded so as to cover half the breadth of the preceding one.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kimbo</value>
            <value column="1">Crooked; arched; bent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kimmerian</value>
            <value column="1">See Cimmerian.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kimnel</value>
            <value column="1">A tub. See Kemelin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kimry</value>
            <value column="1">See Cymry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kin</value>
            <value column="1">A primitive Chinese instrument of the cittern kind, with from five to twenty-five silken strings.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kin</value>
            <value column="1">Relationship, consanguinity, or affinity; connection by birth or marriage; kindred; near connection or alliance, as of those having common descent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kin</value>
            <value column="1">Relatives; persons of the same family or race.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kin</value>
            <value column="1">Of the same nature or kind; kinder.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinaesodic</value>
            <value column="1">Kinesodic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinaesthesis</value>
            <value column="1">The perception attendant upon the movements of the muscles.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinate</value>
            <value column="1">See Quinate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kincob</value>
            <value column="1">India silk brocaded with flowers in silver or gold.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kincob</value>
            <value column="1">Of the nature of kincob; brocaded.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kind</value>
            <value column="1">Characteristic of the species; belonging to one's nature; natural; native.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kind</value>
            <value column="1">Having feelings befitting our common nature; congenial; sympathetic; as, a kind man; a kind heart.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kind</value>
            <value column="1">Showing tenderness or goodness; disposed to do good and confer happiness; averse to hurting or paining; benevolent; benignant; gracious.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kind</value>
            <value column="1">Proceeding from, or characterized by, goodness, gentleness, or benevolence; as, a kind act.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kind</value>
            <value column="1">Gentle; tractable; easily governed; as, a horse kind in harness.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kind</value>
            <value column="1">Nature; natural instinct or disposition.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kind</value>
            <value column="1">Race; genus; species; generic class; as, in mankind or humankind.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kind</value>
            <value column="1">Nature; style; character; sort; fashion; manner; variety; description; class; as, there are several kinds of eloquence, of style, and of music; many kinds of government; various kinds of soil, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kind</value>
            <value column="1">To beget.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kind-hearted</value>
            <value column="1">Having kindness of nature; sympathetic; characterized by a humane disposition; as, a kind-hearted landlord.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kind-heartedness</value>
            <value column="1">The state or quality of being kind-hearted; benevolence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindergarten</value>
            <value column="1">A school for young children, conducted on the theory that education should be begun by gratifying and cultivating the normal aptitude for exercise, play, observation, imitation, and construction; -- a name given by Friedrich Froebel, a German educator, who introduced this method of training, in rooms opening on a garden.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindergartner</value>
            <value column="1">One who teaches in a kindergarten.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinding</value>
            <value column="1">The of causing to burn, or of exciting or inflaming the passions.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinding</value>
            <value column="1">Materials, easily lighted, for starting a fire.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindle</value>
            <value column="1">To bring forth young.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindle</value>
            <value column="1">To set on fire; to cause to burn with flame; to ignite; to cause to begin burning; to start; to light; as, to kindle a match, or shavings.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindle</value>
            <value column="1">Fig.: To inflame, as the passions; to rouse; to provoke; to excite to action; to heat; to fire; to animate; to incite; as, to kindle anger or wrath; to kindle the flame of love, or love into a flame.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindle</value>
            <value column="1">To take fire; to begin to burn with flame; to start as a flame.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindle</value>
            <value column="1">Fig.: To begin to be excited; to grow warm or animated; to be roused or exasperated.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindled</value>
            <value column="1">of Kindle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindler</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, kindles, stirs up, or sets on fire.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindless</value>
            <value column="1">Destitute of kindness; unnatural.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindliness</value>
            <value column="1">Natural inclination; natural course.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindliness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being kindly; benignity; benevolence; gentleness; tenderness; as, kindliness of disposition, of treatment, or of words.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindliness</value>
            <value column="1">Softness; mildness; propitiousness; as, kindliness of weather, or of a season.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindling</value>
            <value column="1">of Kindle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindly</value>
            <value column="1">According to the kind or nature; natural.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindly</value>
            <value column="1">Humane; congenial; sympathetic; hence, disposed to do good to; benevolent; gracious; kind; helpful; as, kindly affections, words, acts, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindly</value>
            <value column="1">Favorable; mild; gentle; auspicious; beneficent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindly</value>
            <value column="1">Naturally; fitly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindly</value>
            <value column="1">In a kind manner; congenially; with good will; with a disposition to make others happy, or to oblige.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindness</value>
            <value column="1">The state or quality of being kind, in any of its various senses; manifestation of kind feeling or disposition beneficence.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindness</value>
            <value column="1">A kind act; an act of good will; as, to do a great kindness.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindred</value>
            <value column="1">Relationship by birth or marriage; consanguinity; affinity; kin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindred</value>
            <value column="1">Relatives by blood or marriage, more properly the former; relations; persons related to each other.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kindred</value>
            <value column="1">Related; congenial; of the like nature or properties; as, kindred souls; kindred skies; kindred propositions.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kine</value>
            <value column="1">of Cow</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kine</value>
            <value column="1">Cows.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinematic</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kinematical</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinematical</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to kinematics.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinematics</value>
            <value column="1">The science which treats of motions considered in themselves, or apart from their causes; the comparison and relation of motions.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinepox</value>
            <value column="1">See Cowpox.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinepox</value>
            <value column="1">See Kinetoscope.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinesiatrics</value>
            <value column="1">A mode of treating disease by appropriate muscular movements; -- also termed kinesitherapy, kinesipathy, lingism, and the movement cure.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinesipathy</value>
            <value column="1">See Kinesiatrics.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinesipathy</value>
            <value column="1">See Kinesiatrics.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinesitherapy</value>
            <value column="1">See Kinesiatrics.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinesodic</value>
            <value column="1">Conveying motion; as; kinesodic substance; -- applied esp. to the spinal cord, because it is capable of conveying doth voluntary and reflex motor impulses, without itself being affected by motor impulses applied to it directly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinetic</value>
            <value column="1">Moving or causing motion; motory; active, as opposed to latent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinetics</value>
            <value column="1">See Dynamics.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinetogenesis</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument for producing curves by the combination of circular movements; -- called also kinescope.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">King</value>
            <value column="1">A Chinese musical instrument, consisting of resonant stones or metal plates, arranged according to their tones in a frame of wood, and struck with a hammer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">King</value>
            <value column="1">A chief ruler; a sovereign; one invested with supreme authority over a nation, country, or tribe, usually by hereditary succession; a monarch; a prince.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">King</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, holds a supreme position or rank; a chief among competitors; as, a railroad king; a money king; the king of the lobby; the king of beasts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">King</value>
            <value column="1">A playing card having the picture of a king; as, the king of diamonds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">King</value>
            <value column="1">The chief piece in the game of chess.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">King</value>
            <value column="1">A crowned man in the game of draughts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">King</value>
            <value column="1">The title of two historical books in the Old Testament.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">King</value>
            <value column="1">To supply with a king; to make a king of; to raise to royalty.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">King Charles spaniel</value>
            <value column="1">A variety of small pet dogs, having, drooping ears, a high, dome-shaped forehead, pug nose, large, prominent eyes, and long, wavy hair. The color is usually black and tan.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">King's Bench</value>
            <value column="1">Formerly, the highest court of common law in England; -- so called because the king used to sit there in person. It consisted of a chief justice and four puisne, or junior, justices. During the reign of a queen it was called the Queen's Bench. Its jurisdiction was transferred by the judicature acts of 1873 and 1875 to the high court of justice created by that legislation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">King-post</value>
            <value column="1">A member of a common form of truss, as a roof truss. It is strictly a tie, intended to prevent the sagging of the tiebeam in the middle. If there are struts, supporting the main rafters, they often bear upon the foot of the king-post. Called also crown-post.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingbird</value>
            <value column="1">A small American bird (Tyrannus tyrannus, or T. Carolinensis), noted for its courage in attacking larger birds, even hawks and eagles, especially when they approach its nest in the breeding season. It is a typical tyrant flycatcher, taking various insects upon the wing. It is dark ash above, and blackish on the head and tail. The quills and wing coverts are whitish at the edges. It is white beneath, with a white terminal band on the tail. The feathers on the head of the adults show a bright orange basal spot when erected. Called also bee bird, and bee martin. Several Southern and Western species of Tyrannus are also called king birds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingbird</value>
            <value column="1">The king tody. See under King.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingbolt</value>
            <value column="1">A vertical iron bolt, by which the forward axle and wheels of a vehicle or the trucks of a railroad car are connected with the other parts.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingcraft</value>
            <value column="1">The craft of kings; the art of governing as a sovereign; royal policy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingcup</value>
            <value column="1">The common buttercup.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingdom</value>
            <value column="1">The rank, quality, state, or attributes of a king; royal authority; sovereign power; rule; dominion; monarchy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingdom</value>
            <value column="1">The territory or country subject to a king or queen; the dominion of a monarch; the sphere in which one is king or has control.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingdom</value>
            <value column="1">An extensive scientific division distinguished by leading or ruling characteristics; a principal division; a department; as, the mineral kingdom.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingdomed</value>
            <value column="1">Having a kingdom or the dignity of a king; like a kingdom.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinged</value>
            <value column="1">of King</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingfish</value>
            <value column="1">An American marine food fish of the genus Menticirrus, especially M. saxatilis, or M. nebulosos, of the Atlantic coast; -- called also whiting, surf whiting, and barb.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingfish</value>
            <value column="1">The opah.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingfish</value>
            <value column="1">The common cero; also, the spotted cero. See Cero.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingfish</value>
            <value column="1">The queenfish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingfisher</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of numerous species of birds constituting the family Alcedinidae. Most of them feed upon fishes which they capture by diving and seizing then with the beak; others feed only upon reptiles, insects, etc. About one hundred and fifty species are known. They are found in nearly all parts of the world, but are particularly abundant in the East Indies.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinghood</value>
            <value column="1">The state of being a king; the attributes of a king; kingship.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinging</value>
            <value column="1">of King</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingless</value>
            <value column="1">Having no king.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinglet</value>
            <value column="1">A little king; a weak or insignificant king.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinglet</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several species of small singing birds of the genus Regulus and family Sylviidae.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinglihood</value>
            <value column="1">King-liness.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingliness</value>
            <value column="1">The state or quality of being kingly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingling</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Kinglet, 1.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingly</value>
            <value column="1">Belonging to, suitable to, or becoming, a king; characteristic of, resembling, a king; directed or administered by a king; monarchical; royal; sovereign; regal; august; noble; grand.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingly</value>
            <value column="1">In a kingly or kinglike manner.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingship</value>
            <value column="1">The state, office, or dignity of a king; royalty.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingston</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kingstone</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingston metal</value>
            <value column="1">An alloy of tin, copper, and mercury, sometimes used for the bearings and packings of machinery.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingston valve</value>
            <value column="1">A conical valve, opening outward, to close the mouth of a pipe which passes through the side of a vessel below the water line.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingstone</value>
            <value column="1">The black angel fish. See Angel fish, under Angel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kingtruss</value>
            <value column="1">A truss, framed with a king-post; -- used in roofs, bridges, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinic</value>
            <value column="1">See Quinic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kink</value>
            <value column="1">A twist or loop in a rope or thread, caused by a spontaneous doubling or winding upon itself; a close loop or curl; a doubling in a cord.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kink</value>
            <value column="1">An unreasonable notion; a crotchet; a whim; a caprice.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kink</value>
            <value column="1">To wind into a kink; to knot or twist spontaneously upon itself, as a rope or thread.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kink</value>
            <value column="1">A fit of coughing; also, a convulsive fit of laughter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinkajou</value>
            <value column="1">A nocturnal carnivorous mammal (Cercoleptes caudivolvulus) of South America, about as large as a full-grown cat. It has a prehensile tail and lives in trees. It is the only representative of a distinct family (Cercoleptidae) allied to the raccoons. Called also potto, and honey bear.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinked</value>
            <value column="1">of Kink</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinkhaust</value>
            <value column="1">Whooping cough.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinking</value>
            <value column="1">of Kink</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinkle</value>
            <value column="1">Same as 3d Kink.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinky</value>
            <value column="1">Full of kinks; liable to kink or curl; as, kinky hair.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinky</value>
            <value column="1">Queer; eccentric; crotchety.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinnikinic</value>
            <value column="1">Prepared leaves or bark of certain plants; -- used by the Indians of the Northwest for smoking, either mixed with tobacco or as a substitute for it. Also, a plant so used, as the osier cornel (Cornus stolonijra), and the bearberry (Arctostaphylus Uva-ursi).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kino</value>
            <value column="1">The dark red dried juice of certain plants, used variously in tanning, in dyeing, and as an astringent in medicine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinology</value>
            <value column="1">That branch of physics which treats of the laws of motion, or of moving bodies.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinone</value>
            <value column="1">See Quinone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinoyl</value>
            <value column="1">See Quinoyl.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinrede</value>
            <value column="1">Kindred.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinsfolk</value>
            <value column="1">Relatives; kindred; kin; persons of the same family or closely or closely related families.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinship</value>
            <value column="1">Family relationship.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinsman</value>
            <value column="1">A man of the same race or family; one related by blood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinsmanship</value>
            <value column="1">Kinship.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinsmen</value>
            <value column="1">of Kinsman</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinswoman</value>
            <value column="1">A female relative.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kinswomen</value>
            <value column="1">of Kinswoman</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kintlidge</value>
            <value column="1">See Kentledge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiosk</value>
            <value column="1">A Turkish open summer house or pavilion, supported by pillars.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kioways</value>
            <value column="1">A tribe of Indians distantly related to the Shoshones. They formerly inhabited the region about the head waters of the North Platte.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kip</value>
            <value column="1">The hide of a young or small beef creature, or leather made from it; kipskin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kipe</value>
            <value column="1">An osier basket used for catching fish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kipper</value>
            <value column="1">A salmon after spawning.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kipper</value>
            <value column="1">A salmon split open, salted, and dried or smoked; -- so called because salmon after spawning were usually so cured, not being good when fresh.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kipper</value>
            <value column="1">To cure, by splitting, salting, and smoking.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kipper</value>
            <value column="1">Amorous; also, lively; light-footed; nimble; gay; sprightly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kippered</value>
            <value column="1">of Kipper</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kippering</value>
            <value column="1">of Kipper</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kippernut</value>
            <value column="1">A name given to earthnuts of several kinds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kipskin</value>
            <value column="1">Leather prepared from the skin of young or small cattle, intermediate in grade between calfskin and cowhide.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirk</value>
            <value column="1">A church or the church, in the various senses of the word; esp., the Church of Scotland as distinguished from other reformed churches, or from the Roman Catholic Church.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirked</value>
            <value column="1">Turned upward; bent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirkman</value>
            <value column="1">A clergyman or officer in a kirk.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirkman</value>
            <value column="1">A member of the Church of Scotland, as distinguished from a member of another communion.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirkmen</value>
            <value column="1">of Kirkman</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirkyard</value>
            <value column="1">A churchyard.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirmess</value>
            <value column="1">In Europe, particularly in Belgium and Holland, and outdoor festival and fair; in the United States, generally an indoor entertainment and fair combined.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirschwasser</value>
            <value column="1">An alcoholic liquor, obtained by distilling the fermented juice of the small black cherry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirsome</value>
            <value column="1">Christian; christened.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirtle</value>
            <value column="1">A garment varying in form and use at different times, and worn doth by men and women.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirtled</value>
            <value column="1">Wearing a kirtle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kirumbo</value>
            <value column="1">A bird of Madagascar (Leptosomus discolor), the only living type of a family allied to the rollers. It has a pair of loral plumes. The male is glossy green above, with metallic reflections; the female is spotted with brown and black.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kish</value>
            <value column="1">A workman's name for the graphite which forms incidentally in iron smelting.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kismet</value>
            <value column="1">Destiny; fate.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiss</value>
            <value column="1">To salute with the lips, as a mark of affection, reverence, submission, forgiveness, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiss</value>
            <value column="1">To touch gently, as if fondly or caressingly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiss</value>
            <value column="1">To make or give salutation with the lips in token of love, respect, etc.; as, kiss and make friends.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiss</value>
            <value column="1">To meet; to come in contact; to touch fondly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiss</value>
            <value column="1">A salutation with the lips, as a token of affection, respect, etc.; as, a parting kiss; a kiss of reconciliation.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiss</value>
            <value column="1">A small piece of confectionery.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kissed</value>
            <value column="1">of Kiss</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kisser</value>
            <value column="1">One who kisses.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kissing</value>
            <value column="1">of Kiss</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kissingcrust</value>
            <value column="1">The portion of the upper crust of a loaf which has touched another loaf in baking.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kist</value>
            <value column="1">A chest; hence, a coffin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kist</value>
            <value column="1">A stated payment, especially a payment of rent for land; hence, the time for such payment.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kistvaen</value>
            <value column="1">A Celtic monument, commonly known as a dolmen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kit</value>
            <value column="1">To cut.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kit</value>
            <value column="1">A kitten.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kit</value>
            <value column="1">A small violin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kit</value>
            <value column="1">A large bottle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kit</value>
            <value column="1">A wooden tub or pail, smaller at the top than at the bottom; as, a kit of butter, or of mackerel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kit</value>
            <value column="1">straw or rush basket for fish; also, any kind of basket.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kit</value>
            <value column="1">A box for working implements; hence, a working outfit, as of a workman, a soldier, and the like.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kit</value>
            <value column="1">A group of separate parts, things, or individuals; -- used with whole, and generally contemptuously; as, the whole kit of them.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitcat</value>
            <value column="1">Designating a club in London, to which Addison and Steele belonged; -- so called from Christopher Cat, a pastry cook, who served the club with mutton pies.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitcat</value>
            <value column="1">Designating a canvas used for portraits of a peculiar size, viz., twenty-right or twenty-nine inches by thirty-six; -- so called because that size was adopted by Sir Godfrey Kneller for the portraits he painted of the members of the Kitcat Club.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitcat</value>
            <value column="1">A game played by striking with a stick small piece of wood, called a cat, shaped like two cones united at their bases; tipcat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitchen</value>
            <value column="1">A cookroom; the room of a house appropriated to cookery.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitchen</value>
            <value column="1">A utensil for roasting meat; as, a tin kitchen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitchen</value>
            <value column="1">To furnish food to; to entertain with the fare of the kitchen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitchen middens</value>
            <value column="1">Relics of neolithic man found on the coast of Denmark, consisting of shell mounds, some of which are ten feet high, one thousand feet long, and two hundred feet wide. The name is applied also to similar mounds found on the American coast from Canada to Florida, made by the North American Indians.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitchen-ry</value>
            <value column="1">The body of servants employed in the kitchen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitchener</value>
            <value column="1">A kitchen servant; a cook.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitchenmaid</value>
            <value column="1">A woman employed in the kitchen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kite</value>
            <value column="1">Any raptorial bird of the subfamily Milvinae, of which many species are known. They have long wings, adapted for soaring, and usually a forked tail.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kite</value>
            <value column="1">Fig. : One who is rapacious.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kite</value>
            <value column="1">A light frame of wood or other material covered with paper or cloth, for flying in the air at the end of a string.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kite</value>
            <value column="1">A lofty sail, carried only when the wind is light.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kite</value>
            <value column="1">A quadrilateral, one of whose diagonals is an axis of symmetry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kite</value>
            <value column="1">Fictitious commercial paper used for raising money or to sustain credit, as a check which represents no deposit in bank, or a bill of exchange not sanctioned by sale of goods; an accommodation check or bill.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kite</value>
            <value column="1">The brill.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kite</value>
            <value column="1">To raise money by &quot;kites;&quot; as, kiting transactions. See Kite, 6.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kite</value>
            <value column="1">The belly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiteflier</value>
            <value column="1">See Kite, n., 6.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiteflying</value>
            <value column="1">A mode of raising money, or sustaining one's credit, by the use of paper which is merely nominal; -- called also kiting.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kith</value>
            <value column="1">Acquaintance; kindred.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kithara</value>
            <value column="1">See Cithara.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kithe</value>
            <value column="1">See Kythe.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kithe</value>
            <value column="1">To make known; to manifest; to show; to declare.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitish</value>
            <value column="1">Like or relating to a kite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitling</value>
            <value column="1">A young kitten; a whelp.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitte</value>
            <value column="1">of Kit</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitte</value>
            <value column="1">of Kit to cut.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kittel</value>
            <value column="1">See Kittle, v. t.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitten</value>
            <value column="1">A young cat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kitten</value>
            <value column="1">To bring forth young, as a cat; to bring forth, as kittens.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kittened</value>
            <value column="1">of Kitten</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kittening</value>
            <value column="1">of Kitten</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kittenish</value>
            <value column="1">Resembling a kitten; playful; as, a kittenish disposition.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kittiwake</value>
            <value column="1">A northern gull (Rissa tridactyla), inhabiting the coasts of Europe and America. It is white, with black tips to the wings, and has but three toes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kittle</value>
            <value column="1">To bring forth young, as a cat; to kitten; to litter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kittle</value>
            <value column="1">To tickle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kittle</value>
            <value column="1">Ticklish; not easily managed; troublesome; difficult; variable.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kittlish</value>
            <value column="1">Ticklish; kittle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kittysol</value>
            <value column="1">The Chinese paper parasol.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kive</value>
            <value column="1">A mash vat. See Keeve.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiver</value>
            <value column="1">To cover.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiver</value>
            <value column="1">A cover.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kivikivi</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kiwikiwi</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kivikivies</value>
            <value column="1">of Kiwikiwi</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiwikiwi</value>
            <value column="1">Any species of Apteryx, esp. A. australis; -- so called in imitation of its notes. Called also kiwi. See Apteryx.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kiwikiwies</value>
            <value column="1">of Kiwikiwi</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kjoekken moeddings</value>
            <value column="1">See Kitchen middens.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Klamaths</value>
            <value column="1">A collective name for the Indians of several tribes formerly living along the Klamath river, in California and Oregon, but now restricted to a reservation at Klamath Lake; -- called also Clamets and Hamati.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kleeneboc</value>
            <value column="1">(Zool.) An antelope (Cerphalopus pygmaeus), found in South Africa. It is of very small size, being but one foot high at shoulder. It is remarkable for its activity, and for its mild and timid disposition. Called also guevi, and pygmy antelope.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kleptomania</value>
            <value column="1">A propensity to steal, claimed to be irresistible. This does not constitute legal irresponsibility.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kleptomaniac</value>
            <value column="1">A person affected with kleptomania.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Klick</value>
            <value column="1">See Click.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Klicket</value>
            <value column="1">A small postern or gate in a palisade, for the passage of sallying parties.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Klinkstone</value>
            <value column="1">See Clinkstone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Klinometer</value>
            <value column="1">See Clinometer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Klipdachs</value>
            <value column="1">A small mammal (Hyrax Capensis), found in South Africa. It is of about the size of a rabbit, and closely resembles the daman. Called also rock rabbit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Klipdas</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Klipdachs</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Klipfish</value>
            <value column="1">Dried cod, exported from Norway.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Klipspringer</value>
            <value column="1">A small, graceful South African antelope (Nanotragus oreotragus), which, like the chamois, springs from one crag to another with great agility; -- called also kainsi.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kloof</value>
            <value column="1">A glen; a ravine closed at its upper end.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Klopemania</value>
            <value column="1">See Kleptomania.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knab</value>
            <value column="1">To seize with the teeth; to gnaw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knab</value>
            <value column="1">To nab. See Nab, v. t.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knabbed</value>
            <value column="1">of Knab</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knabbing</value>
            <value column="1">of Knab</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knabble</value>
            <value column="1">To bite or nibble.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knack</value>
            <value column="1">To crack; to make a sharp, abrupt noise to chink.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knack</value>
            <value column="1">To speak affectedly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knack</value>
            <value column="1">A petty contrivance; a toy; a plaything; a knickknack.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knack</value>
            <value column="1">A readiness in performance; aptness at doing something; skill; facility; dexterity.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knack</value>
            <value column="1">Something performed, or to be done, requiring aptness and dexterity; a trick; a device.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knack-kneed</value>
            <value column="1">See Knock-kneed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knacker</value>
            <value column="1">One who makes knickknacks, toys, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knacker</value>
            <value column="1">One of two or more pieces of bone or wood held loosely between the fingers, and struck together by moving the hand; -- called also clapper.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knacker</value>
            <value column="1">a harness maker.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knacker</value>
            <value column="1">One who slaughters worn-out horses and sells their flesh for dog's meat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knackish</value>
            <value column="1">Trickish; artful.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knacky</value>
            <value column="1">Having a knack; cunning; crafty; trickish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knag</value>
            <value column="1">A knot in wood; a protuberance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knag</value>
            <value column="1">A wooden peg for hanging things on.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knag</value>
            <value column="1">The prong of an antler.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knag</value>
            <value column="1">The rugged top of a hill.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knagged</value>
            <value column="1">Full of knots; knaggy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knaggy</value>
            <value column="1">Knotty; rough; figuratively, rough in temper.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knap</value>
            <value column="1">A protuberance; a swelling; a knob; a button; hence, rising ground; a summit. See Knob, and Knop.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knap</value>
            <value column="1">To bite; to bite off; to break short.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knap</value>
            <value column="1">To strike smartly; to rap; to snap.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knap</value>
            <value column="1">To make a sound of snapping.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knap</value>
            <value column="1">A sharp blow or slap.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knapbottle</value>
            <value column="1">The bladder campion (Silene inflata).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knapped</value>
            <value column="1">of Knap</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knapping</value>
            <value column="1">of Knap</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knappish</value>
            <value column="1">Snappish; peevish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knapple</value>
            <value column="1">To break off with an abrupt, sharp noise; to bite; to nibble.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knappy</value>
            <value column="1">Having knaps; full of protuberances or humps; knobby.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knapsack</value>
            <value column="1">A case of canvas or leather, for carrying on the back a soldier's necessaries, or the clothing, etc., of a traveler.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knapweed</value>
            <value column="1">The black centaury (Centaurea nigra); -- so called from the knoblike heads of flowers. Called also bullweed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knar</value>
            <value column="1">See Gnar.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knarl</value>
            <value column="1">A knot in wood. See Gnarl.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knarled</value>
            <value column="1">Knotted. See Gnarled.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knarred</value>
            <value column="1">Knotty; gnarled.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knarry</value>
            <value column="1">Knotty; gnarled.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knave</value>
            <value column="1">A boy; especially, a boy servant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knave</value>
            <value column="1">Any male servant; a menial.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knave</value>
            <value column="1">A tricky, deceitful fellow; a dishonest person; a rogue; a villain.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knave</value>
            <value column="1">A playing card marked with the figure of a servant or soldier; a jack.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knaveries</value>
            <value column="1">of Knavery</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knavery</value>
            <value column="1">The practices of a knave; petty villainy; fraud; trickery; a knavish action.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knavery</value>
            <value column="1">Roguish or mischievous tricks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knaveship</value>
            <value column="1">A small due, in meal, established by usage, which is paid to the under miller.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knavess</value>
            <value column="1">A knavish woman.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knavish</value>
            <value column="1">Like or characteristic of a knave; given to knavery; trickish; fraudulent; dishonest; villainous; as, a knavish fellow, or a knavish trick.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knavish</value>
            <value column="1">Mischievous; roguish; waggish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knavishly</value>
            <value column="1">In a knavish manner; dishonestly; fraudulently.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knavishly</value>
            <value column="1">Mischievously; waggishly; roguishly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knaw</value>
            <value column="1">See Gnaw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knawel</value>
            <value column="1">A low, spreading weed (Scleranthus annuus), common in sandy soil.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knead</value>
            <value column="1">To work and press into a mass, usually with the hands; esp., to work, as by repeated pressure with the knuckles, into a well mixed mass, as the materials of bread, cake, etc.; as, to knead dough.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knead</value>
            <value column="1">Fig.: To treat or form as by kneading; to beat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneadable</value>
            <value column="1">That may be kneaded; capable of being worked into a mass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneaded</value>
            <value column="1">of Knead</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneader</value>
            <value column="1">One who kneads.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneading</value>
            <value column="1">of Knead</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneadingly</value>
            <value column="1">In the manner of one kneading.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knebelite</value>
            <value column="1">A mineral of a gray, red, brown, or green color, and glistening luster. It is a silicate of iron and manganese.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneck</value>
            <value column="1">The twisting of a rope or cable, as it is running out.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knee</value>
            <value column="1">In man, the joint in the middle part of the leg.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knee</value>
            <value column="1">The joint, or region of the joint, between the thigh and leg.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knee</value>
            <value column="1">In the horse and allied animals, the carpal joint, corresponding to the wrist in man.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knee</value>
            <value column="1">A piece of timber or metal formed with an angle somewhat in the shape of the human knee when bent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knee</value>
            <value column="1">A bending of the knee, as in respect or courtesy.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knee</value>
            <value column="1">To supplicate by kneeling.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knee-crooking</value>
            <value column="1">Obsequious; fawning; cringing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knee-deep</value>
            <value column="1">Rising to the knees; knee-high; as, water or snow knee-deep.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knee-deep</value>
            <value column="1">Sunk to the knees; as, men knee-deep in water.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knee-high</value>
            <value column="1">Rising or reaching upward to the knees; as, the water is knee-high.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneebrush</value>
            <value column="1">A tuft or brush of hair on the knees of some species of antelopes and other animals; -- chiefly used in the plural.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneebrush</value>
            <value column="1">A thick mass or collection of hairs on the legs of bees, by aid of which they carry the collected pollen to the hive or nest; -- usually in the plural.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneecap</value>
            <value column="1">The kneepan.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneecap</value>
            <value column="1">A cap or protection for the knee.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneed</value>
            <value column="1">Having knees;- used chiefly in composition; as, in-kneed; out-kneed; weak-kneed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneed</value>
            <value column="1">Geniculated; forming an obtuse angle at the joints, like the knee when a little bent; as, kneed grass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneejoint</value>
            <value column="1">The joint of the knee.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneejoint</value>
            <value column="1">A toggle joint; -- so called because consisting of two pieces jointed to each other end to end, making an angle like the knee when bent.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneejointed</value>
            <value column="1">Geniculate; kneed. See Kneed, a., 2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneel</value>
            <value column="1">To bend the knee; to fall or rest on the knees; -- sometimes with down.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneeled</value>
            <value column="1">of Kneel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneeler</value>
            <value column="1">One who kneels or who worships by or while kneeling.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneeler</value>
            <value column="1">A cushion or stool to kneel on.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneeler</value>
            <value column="1">A name given to certain catechumens and penitents who were permitted to join only in parts of church worship.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneeling</value>
            <value column="1">of Kneel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneelingly</value>
            <value column="1">In a kneeling position.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneepan</value>
            <value column="1">A roundish, flattened, sesamoid bone in the tendon in front of the knee joint; the patella; the kneecap.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kneepiece</value>
            <value column="1">A piece shaped like a knee; as, the kneepieces or ears of a boat.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knell</value>
            <value column="1">The stoke of a bell tolled at a funeral or at the death of a person; a death signal; a passing bell; hence, figuratively, a warning of, or a sound indicating, the passing away of anything.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knell</value>
            <value column="1">To sound as a knell; especially, to toll at a death or funeral; hence, to sound as a warning or evil omen.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knell</value>
            <value column="1">To summon, as by a knell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knelled</value>
            <value column="1">of Knell</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knelling</value>
            <value column="1">of Knell</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knelt</value>
            <value column="1">of Kneel</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knelt</value>
            <value column="1">of Kneel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knew</value>
            <value column="1">of Know.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knew</value>
            <value column="1">of Know</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knicker</value>
            <value column="1">A small ball of clay, baked hard and oiled, used as a marble by boys in playing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knickerbockers</value>
            <value column="1">The name for a style of short breeches; smallclothes.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knickknack</value>
            <value column="1">A trifle or toy; a bawble; a gewgaw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knickknackatory</value>
            <value column="1">A collection of knickknacks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knickknackery</value>
            <value column="1">Knickknacks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knife</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument consisting of a thin blade, usually of steel and having a sharp edge for cutting, fastened to a handle, but of many different forms and names for different uses; as, table knife, drawing knife, putty knife, pallet knife, pocketknife, penknife, chopping knife, etc..</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knife</value>
            <value column="1">A sword or dagger.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knife</value>
            <value column="1">To prune with the knife.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knife</value>
            <value column="1">To cut or stab with a knife.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knife-edge</value>
            <value column="1">A piece of steel sharpened to an acute edge or angle, and resting on a smooth surface, serving as the axis of motion of a pendulum, scale beam, or other piece required to oscillate with the least possible friction.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knifeboard</value>
            <value column="1">A board on which knives are cleaned or polished.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knifed</value>
            <value column="1">of Knife</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knifing</value>
            <value column="1">of Knife</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight</value>
            <value column="1">A young servant or follower; a military attendant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight</value>
            <value column="1">In feudal times, a man-at-arms serving on horseback and admitted to a certain military rank with special ceremonies, including an oath to protect the distressed, maintain the right, and live a stainless life.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight</value>
            <value column="1">One on whom knighthood, a dignity next below that of baronet, is conferred by the sovereign, entitling him to be addressed as Sir; as, Sir John.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight</value>
            <value column="1">A champion; a partisan; a lover.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight</value>
            <value column="1">A piece used in the game of chess, usually bearing a horse's head.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight</value>
            <value column="1">A playing card bearing the figure of a knight; the knave or jack.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight</value>
            <value column="1">To dub or create (one) a knight; -- done in England by the sovereign only, who taps the kneeling candidate with a sword, saying: Rise, Sir ---.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight Templar</value>
            <value column="1">See Commandery, n., 3, and also Templar, n., 1 and 3.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight bachelor</value>
            <value column="1">A knight of the most ancient, but lowest, order of English knights, and not a member of any order of chivalry. See Bachelor, 4.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight banneret</value>
            <value column="1">A knight who carried a banner, who possessed fiefs to a greater amount than the knight bachelor, and who was obliged to serve in war with a greater number of attendants. The dignity was sometimes conferred by the sovereign in person on the field of battle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight baro-net</value>
            <value column="1">See Baronet.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight marshal</value>
            <value column="1">An officer in the household of the British sovereign, who has cognizance of transgressions within the royal household and verge, and of contracts made there, a member of the household being one of the parties.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight service</value>
            <value column="1">A tenure of lands held by knights on condition of performing military service. See Chivalry, n., 4.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight-er-ratic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to a knight-errant or to knight-errantry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight-errant</value>
            <value column="1">A wandering knight; a knight who traveled in search of adventures, for the purpose of exhibiting military skill, prowess, and generosity.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight-errantries</value>
            <value column="1">of Knight-errantry</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight-errantry</value>
            <value column="1">The character or actions of wandering knights; the practice of wandering in quest of adventures; chivalry; a quixotic or romantic adventure or scheme.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knight-errants</value>
            <value column="1">of Knight-errant</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knightage</value>
            <value column="1">To body of knights, taken collectively.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knighted</value>
            <value column="1">of Knight</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knighthead</value>
            <value column="1">A bollard timber. See under Bollard.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knighthood</value>
            <value column="1">The character, dignity, or condition of a knight, or of knights as a class; hence, chivalry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knighthood</value>
            <value column="1">The whole body of knights.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knighting</value>
            <value column="1">of Knight</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knightless</value>
            <value column="1">Unbecoming a knight.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knightliness</value>
            <value column="1">The character or bearing suitable for a knight; chivalry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knightly</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to a knight; becoming a knight; chivalrous; as, a knightly combat; a knightly spirit.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knightly</value>
            <value column="1">In a manner becoming a knight.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knights Templars</value>
            <value column="1">of Knight Templar</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knights bachelors</value>
            <value column="1">of Knight bachelor</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knights bannerets</value>
            <value column="1">of Knight banneret</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knights-errant</value>
            <value column="1">of Knight-errant</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knit</value>
            <value column="1">of Knit</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knit</value>
            <value column="1">To form into a knot, or into knots; to tie together, as cord; to fasten by tying.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knit</value>
            <value column="1">To form, as a textile fabric, by the interlacing of yarn or thread in a series of connected loops, by means of needles, either by hand or by machinery; as, to knit stockings.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knit</value>
            <value column="1">To join; to cause to grow together.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knit</value>
            <value column="1">To unite closely; to connect; to engage; as, hearts knit together in love.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knit</value>
            <value column="1">To draw together; to contract into wrinkles.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knit</value>
            <value column="1">To form a fabric by interlacing yarn or thread; to weave by making knots or loops.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knit</value>
            <value column="1">To be united closely; to grow together; as, broken bones will in time knit and become sound.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knit</value>
            <value column="1">Union knitting; texture.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knitback</value>
            <value column="1">The plant comfrey; -- so called from its use as a restorative.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knitch</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Knitchet</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knitchet</value>
            <value column="1">A number of things tied or knit together; a bundle; a fagot.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knits</value>
            <value column="1">Small particles of ore.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knitster</value>
            <value column="1">A woman who knits.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knitted</value>
            <value column="1">of Knit</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knitter</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, knits, joins, or unites; a knitting machine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knitting</value>
            <value column="1">of Knit</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knitting</value>
            <value column="1">The work of a knitter; the network formed by knitting.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knitting</value>
            <value column="1">Union formed by knitting, as of bones.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knittle</value>
            <value column="1">A string that draws together a purse or bag.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knittle</value>
            <value column="1">See Nettles.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knives</value>
            <value column="1">of Knife</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knives</value>
            <value column="1">of Knife. See Knife.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knob</value>
            <value column="1">A hard protuberance; a hard swelling or rising; a bunch; a lump; as, a knob in the flesh, or on a bone.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knob</value>
            <value column="1">A knoblike ornament or handle; as, the knob of a lock, door, or drawer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knob</value>
            <value column="1">A rounded hill or mountain; as, the Pilot Knob.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knob</value>
            <value column="1">See Knop.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knob</value>
            <value column="1">To grow into knobs or bunches; to become knobbed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knobbed</value>
            <value column="1">Containing knobs; full of knobs; ending in a nob. See Illust of Antenna.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knobber</value>
            <value column="1">See Knobbler.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knobbing</value>
            <value column="1">Rough dressing by knocking off knobs or projections.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knobbler</value>
            <value column="1">The hart in its second year; a young deer.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knobbling fire</value>
            <value column="1">A bloomery fire. See Bloomery.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knobby</value>
            <value column="1">Full of, or covered with, knobs or hard protuberances.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knobby</value>
            <value column="1">Irregular; stubborn in particulars.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knobby</value>
            <value column="1">Abounding in rounded hills or mountains; hilly.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knobstick</value>
            <value column="1">One who refuses to join, or withdraws from, a trades union.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knock</value>
            <value column="1">To drive or be driven against something; to strike against something; to clash; as, one heavy body knocks against another.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knock</value>
            <value column="1">To strike or beat with something hard or heavy; to rap; as, to knock with a club; to knock on the door.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knock</value>
            <value column="1">To strike with something hard or heavy; to move by striking; to drive (a thing) against something; as, to knock a ball with a bat; to knock the head against a post; to knock a lamp off the table.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knock</value>
            <value column="1">To strike for admittance; to rap upon, as a door.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knock</value>
            <value column="1">A blow; a stroke with something hard or heavy; a jar.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knock</value>
            <value column="1">A stroke, as on a door for admittance; a rap.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knock-knee</value>
            <value column="1">A condition in which the knees are bent in so as to touch each other in walking; inknee.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knock-kneed</value>
            <value column="1">Having the legs bent inward so that the knees touch in walking.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knockdown</value>
            <value column="1">A felling by a knock, as of a combatant, or of an animal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knockdown</value>
            <value column="1">Of force sufficient to fell or completely overthrow; as, a knockdown blow; a knockdown argument.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knocked</value>
            <value column="1">of Knock</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knocker</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, knocks; specifically, an instrument, or kind of hammer, fastened to a door, to be used in seeking for admittance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knocking</value>
            <value column="1">of Knock</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knocking</value>
            <value column="1">A beating; a rap; a series of raps.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knockings</value>
            <value column="1">Large lumps picked out of the sieve, in dressing ore.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knockstone</value>
            <value column="1">A block upon which ore is broken up.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knoll</value>
            <value column="1">A little round hill; a mound; a small elevation of earth; the top or crown of a hill.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knoll</value>
            <value column="1">To ring, as a bell; to strike a knell upon; to toll; to proclaim, or summon, by ringing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knoll</value>
            <value column="1">To sound, as a bell; to knell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knoll</value>
            <value column="1">The tolling of a bell; a knell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knolled</value>
            <value column="1">of Knoll</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knoller</value>
            <value column="1">One who tolls a bell.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knolling</value>
            <value column="1">of Knoll</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knop</value>
            <value column="1">A knob; a bud; a bunch; a button.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knop</value>
            <value column="1">Any boldly projecting sculptured ornament; esp., the ornamental termination of a pinnacle, and then synonymous with finial; -- called also knob, and knosp.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knopped</value>
            <value column="1">Having knops or knobs; fastened as with buttons.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knoppern</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of gall produced by a gallfly on the cup of an acorn, -- used in tanning and dyeing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knopweed</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Knapweed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knor</value>
            <value column="1">See Knur.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knosp</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Knop,2.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A fastening together of the pars or ends of one or more threads, cords, ropes, etc., by any one of various ways of tying or entangling.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A lump or loop formed in a thread, cord, rope. etc., as at the end, by tying or interweaving it upon itself.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">An ornamental tie, as of a ribbon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A bond of union; a connection; a tie.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">Something not easily solved; an intricacy; a difficulty; a perplexity; a problem.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A figure the lines of which are interlaced or intricately interwoven, as in embroidery, gardening, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A cluster of persons or things; a collection; a group; a hand; a clique; as, a knot of politicians.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A portion of a branch of a tree that forms a mass of woody fiber running at an angle with the grain of the main stock and making a hard place in the timber. A loose knot is generally the remains of a dead branch of a tree covered by later woody growth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A knob, lump, swelling, or protuberance.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A protuberant joint in a plant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">The point on which the action of a story depends; the gist of a matter.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">See Node.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A division of the log line, serving to measure the rate of the vessel's motion. Each knot on the line bears the same proportion to a mile that thirty seconds do to an hour. The number of knots which run off from the reel in half a minute, therefore, shows the number of miles the vessel sails in an hour.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A nautical mile, or 6080.27 feet; as, when a ship goes eight miles an hour, her speed is said to be eight knots.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of epaulet. See Shoulder knot.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">A sandpiper (Tringa canutus), found in the northern parts of all the continents, in summer. It is grayish or ashy above, with the rump and upper tail coverts white, barred with dusky. The lower parts are pale brown, with the flanks and under tail coverts white. When fat it is prized by epicures. Called also dunne.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">To tie in or with, or form into, a knot or knots; to form a knot on, as a rope; to entangle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">To unite closely; to knit together.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">To entangle or perplex; to puzzle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">To form knots or joints, as in a cord, a plant, etc.; to become entangled.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">To knit knots for fringe or trimming.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knot</value>
            <value column="1">To copulate; -- said of toads.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotberry</value>
            <value column="1">The cloudberry (Rudus Chamaemorus); -- so called from its knotted stems.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotgrass</value>
            <value column="1">a common weed with jointed stems (Polygonum aviculare); knotweed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotgrass</value>
            <value column="1">The dog grass. See under Dog.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotless</value>
            <value column="1">Free from knots; without knots.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotted</value>
            <value column="1">of Knot</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotted</value>
            <value column="1">Full of knots; having knots knurled; as, a knotted cord; the knotted oak.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotted</value>
            <value column="1">Interwoven; matted; entangled.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotted</value>
            <value column="1">Having intersecting lines or figures.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotted</value>
            <value column="1">Characterized by small, detached points, chiefly composed of mica, less decomposable than the mass of the rock, and forming knots in relief on the weathered surface; as, knotted rocks.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotted</value>
            <value column="1">Entangled; puzzling; knotty.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knottiness</value>
            <value column="1">The quality or state of being knotty or full of knots.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knottiness</value>
            <value column="1">Difficulty of solution; intricacy; complication.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotting</value>
            <value column="1">of Knot</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotty</value>
            <value column="1">Full of knots; knotted; having many knots; as, knotty timber; a knotty rope.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotty</value>
            <value column="1">Hard; rugged; as, a knotty head.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotty</value>
            <value column="1">Difficult; intricate; perplexed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotweed</value>
            <value column="1">See Knot/rass.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knotwort</value>
            <value column="1">A small, herbaceous, trailing plant, of the genus Illecebrum (I. verticillatum).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knout</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of whip for flogging criminals, formerly much used in Russia. The last is a tapering bundle of leather thongs twisted with wire and hardened, so that it mangles the flesh.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knout</value>
            <value column="1">To punish with the knout.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Know</value>
            <value column="1">Knee.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Know</value>
            <value column="1">To perceive or apprehend clearly and certainly; to understand; to have full information of; as, to know one's duty.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Know</value>
            <value column="1">To be convinced of the truth of; to be fully assured of; as, to know things from information.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Know</value>
            <value column="1">To be acquainted with; to be no stranger to; to be more or less familiar with the person, character, etc., of; to possess experience of; as, to know an author; to know the rules of an organization.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Know</value>
            <value column="1">To recognize; to distinguish; to discern the character of; as, to know a person's face or figure.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Know</value>
            <value column="1">To have sexual commerce with.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Know</value>
            <value column="1">To have knowledge; to have a clear and certain perception; to possess wisdom, instruction, or information; -- often with of.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Know</value>
            <value column="1">To be assured; to feel confident.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Know-all</value>
            <value column="1">One who knows everything; hence, one who makes pretension to great knowledge; a wiseacre; -- usually ironical.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Know-nothing</value>
            <value column="1">A member of a secret political organization in the United States, the chief objects of which were the proscription of foreigners by the repeal of the naturalization laws, and the exclusive choice of native Americans for office.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Know-nothingism</value>
            <value column="1">The doctrines, principles, or practices, of the Know-nothings.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowa bleness</value>
            <value column="1">The state or quality of being knowable.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowable</value>
            <value column="1">That may be known; capable of being discovered, understood, or ascertained.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knower</value>
            <value column="1">One who knows.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowing</value>
            <value column="1">of Know</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowing</value>
            <value column="1">Skilful; well informed; intelligent; as, a knowing man; a knowing dog.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowing</value>
            <value column="1">Artful; cunning; as, a knowing rascal.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowing</value>
            <value column="1">Knowledge; hence, experience.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowingly</value>
            <value column="1">With knowledge; in a knowing manner; intelligently; consciously; deliberately; as, he would not knowingly offend.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowingly</value>
            <value column="1">By experience.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowingness</value>
            <value column="1">The state or quality of being knowing or intelligent; shrewdness; skillfulness.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowleche</value>
            <value column="1">See Knowl, edge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowleching</value>
            <value column="1">Knowledge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowledge</value>
            <value column="1">The act or state of knowing; clear perception of fact, truth, or duty; certain apprehension; familiar cognizance; cognition.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowledge</value>
            <value column="1">That which is or may be known; the object of an act of knowing; a cognition; -- chiefly used in the plural.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowledge</value>
            <value column="1">That which is gained and preserved by knowing; instruction; acquaintance; enlightenment; learning; scholarship; erudition.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowledge</value>
            <value column="1">That familiarity which is gained by actual experience; practical skill; as, a knowledge of life.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowledge</value>
            <value column="1">Scope of information; cognizance; notice; as, it has not come to my knowledge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowledge</value>
            <value column="1">Sexual intercourse; -- usually preceded by carnal; as, carnal knowledge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knowledge</value>
            <value column="1">To acknowledge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Known</value>
            <value column="1">of Know</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Known</value>
            <value column="1">of Know.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knubs</value>
            <value column="1">Waste silk formed in winding off the threads from a cocoon.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuckle</value>
            <value column="1">The joint of a finger, particularly when made prominent by the closing of the fingers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuckle</value>
            <value column="1">The kneejoint, or middle joint, of either leg of a quadruped, especially of a calf; -- formerly used of the kneejoint of a human being.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuckle</value>
            <value column="1">The joint of a plant.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuckle</value>
            <value column="1">The joining pars of a hinge through which the pin or rivet passes; a knuckle joint.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuckle</value>
            <value column="1">A convex portion of a vessel's figure where a sudden change of shape occurs, as in a canal boat, where a nearly vertical side joins a nearly flat bottom.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuckle</value>
            <value column="1">A contrivance, usually of brass or iron, and furnished with points, worn to protect the hand, to add force to a blow, and to disfigure the person struck; as, brass knuckles; -- called also knuckle duster.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuckle</value>
            <value column="1">To yield; to submit; -- used with down, to, or under.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuckle</value>
            <value column="1">To beat with the knuckles; to pommel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuckled</value>
            <value column="1">of Knuckle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuckled</value>
            <value column="1">Jointed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuckling</value>
            <value column="1">of Knuckle</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knuff</value>
            <value column="1">A lout; a clown.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knur</value>
            <value column="1">A knurl.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knurl</value>
            <value column="1">A contorted knot in wood; a crossgrained protuberance; a nodule; a boss or projection.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knurl</value>
            <value column="1">One who, or that which, is crossgrained.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knurl</value>
            <value column="1">To provide with ridges, to assist the grasp, as in the edge of a flat knob, or coin; to mill.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knurled</value>
            <value column="1">Full of knots; gnarled.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knurled</value>
            <value column="1">Milled, as the head of a screw, or the edge of a coin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knurly</value>
            <value column="1">Full of knots; hard; tough; hence, capable of enduring or resisting much.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Knurry</value>
            <value column="1">Full of knots.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koaita</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Coaita.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koala</value>
            <value column="1">A tailless marsupial (Phascolarctos cinereus), found in Australia. The female carries her young on the back of her neck. Called also Australian bear, native bear, and native sloth.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kob</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Koba</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koba</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several species of African antelopes of the genus Kobus, esp. the species Kobus sing-sing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kobalt</value>
            <value column="1">See Cobalt.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kobellite</value>
            <value column="1">A blackish gray mineral, a sulphide of antimony, bismuth, and lead.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kobold</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of domestic spirit in German mythology, corresponding to the Scottish brownie and the English Robin Goodfellow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kodak</value>
            <value column="1">A kind of portable camera.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koel</value>
            <value column="1">Any one of several species of cuckoos of the genus Eudynamys, found in India, the East Indies, and Australia. They deposit their eggs in the nests of other birds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koff</value>
            <value column="1">A two-masted Dutch vessel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kohinoor</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kohnur</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kohl</value>
            <value column="1">A mixture of soot and other ingredients, used by Egyptian and other Eastern women to darken the edges of the eyelids.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kohl-rabi</value>
            <value column="1">A variety of cabbage, in which the edible part is a large, turnip-shaped swelling of the stem, above the surface of the ground.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kohl-rabies</value>
            <value column="1">of Kohl-rabi</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kohnur</value>
            <value column="1">A famous diamond, surrendered to the British crown on the annexation of the Punjab. According to Hindoo legends, it was found in a Golconda mine, and has been the property of various Hindoo and Persian rulers.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kokama</value>
            <value column="1">The gemsbok.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koklass</value>
            <value column="1">Any pheasant of the genus Pucrasia. The birds of this genus inhabit India and China, and are distinguished by having a long central and two lateral crests on the head. Called also pucras.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kokoon</value>
            <value column="1">The gnu.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kolarian</value>
            <value column="1">An individual of one of the races of aboriginal inhabitants which survive in Hindostan.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kolarian</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the Kolarians.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Komenic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to, or designating, an acid derived from meconic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Komtok</value>
            <value column="1">An African freshwater fish (Protopterus annectens), belonging to the Dipnoi. It can breathe air by means of its lungs, and when waters dry up, it encases itself in a nest of hard mud, where it remains till the rainy season. It is used as food.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kon</value>
            <value column="1">To know. See Can, and Con.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Konite</value>
            <value column="1">See Conite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Konze</value>
            <value column="1">A large African antelope (Alcelaphus Lichtensteini), allied to the hartbeest, but having shorter and flatter horns, and lacking a black patch on the face.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koodoo</value>
            <value column="1">A large South African antelope (Strepsiceros kudu). The males have graceful spiral horns, sometimes four feet long. The general color is reddish or grayish brown, with eight or nine white bands on each side, and a pale dorsal stripe. The old males become dark bluish gray, due to the skin showing through the hair. The females are hornless. Called also nellut.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kookoom</value>
            <value column="1">The oryx or gemsbok.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koolokamba</value>
            <value column="1">A west African anthropoid ape (Troglodytes koolokamba, or T. Aubryi), allied to the chimpanzee and gorilla, and, in some respects, intermediate between them.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koolslaa</value>
            <value column="1">See Coleslaw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koord</value>
            <value column="1">See Kurd.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koordish</value>
            <value column="1">See Kurdish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koorilian</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Kurilian.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kopeck</value>
            <value column="1">A small Russian coin. One hundred kopecks make a rouble, worth about sixty cents.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koran</value>
            <value column="1">The Scriptures of the Mohammedans, containing the professed revelations to Mohammed; -- called also Alcoran.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Korin</value>
            <value column="1">The gazelle.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Korrigum</value>
            <value column="1">A West African antelope (Damalis Senegalensis), allied to the sassaby. It is reddish gray, with a black face, and a black stripe on the outside of the legs above the knees.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kosmos</value>
            <value column="1">See Cosmos.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kotow</value>
            <value column="1">The prostration made by mandarins and others to their superiors, either as homage or worship, by knocking the forehead on the ground. There are degrees in the rite, the highest being expressed by three knockings.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kotow</value>
            <value column="1">To perform the kotow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kotowed</value>
            <value column="1">of Kotow</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kotowing</value>
            <value column="1">of Kotow</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koulan</value>
            <value column="1">A wild horse (Equus, / Asinus, onager) inhabiting the plants of Central Asia; -- called also gour, khur, and onager.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Koumiss</value>
            <value column="1">An intoxicating fermented or distilled liquor originally made by the Tartars from mare's or camel's milk. It can be obtained from any kind of milk, and is now largely made in Europe.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kousso</value>
            <value column="1">An Abyssinian rosaceous tree (Brayera anthelmintica), the flowers of which are used as a vermifuge.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kowtow</value>
            <value column="1">The same as Kotow.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kra</value>
            <value column="1">A long-tailed ape (Macacus cynomolgus) of India and Sumatra. It is reddish olive, spotted with black, and has a black tail.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kraal</value>
            <value column="1">A collection of huts within a stockade; a village; sometimes, a single hut.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kraal</value>
            <value column="1">An inclosure into which are driven wild elephants which are to be tamed and educated.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krait</value>
            <value column="1">A very venomous snake of India (Bungarus coeruleus), allied to the cobra. Its upper parts are bluish or brownish black, often with narrow white streaks; the belly is whitish.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kraken</value>
            <value column="1">A fabulous Scandinavian sea monster, often represented as resembling an island, but sometimes as resembling an immense octopus.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krakowiak</value>
            <value column="1">A lively Polish dance. See Cracovienne.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krameria</value>
            <value column="1">A genus of spreading shrubs with many stems, from one species of which (K. triandra), found in Peru, rhatany root, used as a medicine, is obtained.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krameric</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or derived from, Krameria (rhatany); as, krameric acid, usually called ratanhia-tannic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krang</value>
            <value column="1">The carcass of a whale after the blubber has been removed.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kranging hook</value>
            <value column="1">A hook for holding the blubber while cutting it away.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kreatic</value>
            <value column="1">See Creatic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kreatin</value>
            <value column="1">See Creatin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kreatinin</value>
            <value column="1">See Creatinin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kreel</value>
            <value column="1">See Creel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kremlin</value>
            <value column="1">The citadel of a town or city; especially, the citadel of Moscow, a large inclosure which contains imperial palaces, cathedrals, churches, an arsenal, etc.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krems</value>
            <value column="1">A variety of white lead. See Krems lead, under Lead, n.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kreng</value>
            <value column="1">See Krang.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kreosote</value>
            <value column="1">See Creosote.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kreutzer</value>
            <value column="1">A small copper coin formerly used in South Germany; also, a small Austrian copper coin.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kriegsspiel</value>
            <value column="1">A game of war, played for practice, on maps.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kris</value>
            <value column="1">A Malay dagger. See Creese.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krishna</value>
            <value column="1">The most popular of the Hindoo divinities, usually held to be the eighth incarnation of the god Vishnu.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kritarchy</value>
            <value column="1">The rule of the judges over Israel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krokidolite</value>
            <value column="1">See Crocidolite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krone</value>
            <value column="1">A coin of Denmark, Norway, and Sweden, of the value of about twenty-eight cents. See Crown, n., 9.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krooman</value>
            <value column="1">One of a negro tribe of Liberia and the adjacent coast, whose members are much employed on shipboard.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kroomen</value>
            <value column="1">of Krooman</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kruller</value>
            <value column="1">See Cruller.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krumhorn</value>
            <value column="1">A reed instrument of music of the cornet kind, now obsolete (see Cornet, 1, a.).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krumhorn</value>
            <value column="1">A reed stop in the organ; -- sometimes called cremona.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krummhorn</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Krumhorn</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Krupp gun</value>
            <value column="1">A breech-loading steel cannon manufactured at the works of Friedrich Krupp, at Essen in Prussia. Guns of over eight-inch bore are made up of several concentric cylinders; those of a smaller size are forged solid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kryolite</value>
            <value column="1">See Cryolite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ksar</value>
            <value column="1">See Czar.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kshatriya</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kshatruya</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kshatruya</value>
            <value column="1">The military caste, the second of the four great Hindoo castes; also, a member of that caste. See Caste.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kuda</value>
            <value column="1">The East Indian tapir. See Tapir.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kudos</value>
            <value column="1">Glory; fame; renown; praise.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kudos</value>
            <value column="1">To praise; to extol; to glorify.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kudu</value>
            <value column="1">See Koodoo.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kufic</value>
            <value column="1">See Cufic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kukang</value>
            <value column="1">The slow lemur. See Lemur.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kuklux</value>
            <value column="1">The name adopted in the southern part of the United States by a secret political organization, active for several years after the close of the Civil War, and having for its aim the repression of the political power of the freedmen; -- called also Kuklux Klan.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kulan</value>
            <value column="1">See Koulan.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kumish</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kumiss</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kumiss</value>
            <value column="1">See Koumiss.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kummel</value>
            <value column="1">A Russian and German liqueur, consisting of a sweetened spirit flavored with caraway seeds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kumquat</value>
            <value column="1">A small tree of the genus Citrus (C. Japonica) growing in China and Japan; also, its small acid, orange-colored fruit used for preserves.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kupfernickel</value>
            <value column="1">Copper-nickel; niccolite. See Niccolite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kurd</value>
            <value column="1">A native or inhabitant of a mountainous region of Western Asia belonging to the Turkish and Persian monarchies.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kurdish</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the Kurds.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kurilian</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to the Kurile Islands, a chain of islands in the Pacific ocean, extending from the southern extremity of Kamschatka to Yesso.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kurilian</value>
            <value column="1">A native or an inhabitant of the Kurile Islands.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kursaal</value>
            <value column="1">A public hall or room, for the use of visitors at watering places and health resorts in Germany.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kusimanse</value>
            <value column="1">A carnivorous animal (Crossarchus obscurus) of tropical Africa. It its allied to the civets. Called also kusimansel, and mangue.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kuskus</value>
            <value column="1">See Vetiver.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kussier</value>
            <value column="1">(Mus.) A Turkish instrument of music, with a hollow body covered with skin, over which five strings are stretched.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kutauss</value>
            <value column="1">The India civet (Viverra zibetha).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kutch</value>
            <value column="1">The packet of vellum leaves in which the gold is first beaten into thin sheets.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kutch</value>
            <value column="1">See Catechu.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Ky</value>
            <value column="1">Kine.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyaboca wood</value>
            <value column="1">Amboyna wood.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyaboca wood</value>
            <value column="1">Sandalwood (Santalum album).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyanize</value>
            <value column="1">To render (wood) proof against decay by saturating with a solution of corrosive sublimate in open tanks, or under pressure.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyanized</value>
            <value column="1">of Kyanize</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyanizing</value>
            <value column="1">of Kyanize</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyannite</value>
            <value column="1">See Cyanite.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyanol</value>
            <value column="1">Aniline.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyanol</value>
            <value column="1">A base obtained from coal tar.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyanophyll</value>
            <value column="1">Same as Cyanophyll.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyar</value>
            <value column="1">Cocoanut fiber, or the cordage made from it. See Coir.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyaw</value>
            <value column="1">A daw.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyd</value>
            <value column="1">p. p. of Kythe.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kydde</value>
            <value column="1">imp. of Kythe, to show.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kydde</value>
            <value column="1">of Kithe</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyke</value>
            <value column="1">To look steadfastly; to gaze.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyley</value>
            <value column="1">A variety of the boomerang.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyloes</value>
            <value column="1">The cattle of the Hebrides, or of the Highlands.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kymnel</value>
            <value column="1">See Kimnel.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kymograph</value>
            <value column="1">An instrument for measuring, and recording graphically, the pressure of the blood in any of the blood vessels of a living animal; -- called also kymographion.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kymographic</value>
            <value column="1">Of or pertaining to a kymograph; as, a kymographic tracing.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kymric</value>
            <value column="1">See Cymric, a. &amp; n.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kymry</value>
            <value column="1">See Cymry.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kynrede</value>
            <value column="1">Kindred.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kynurenic</value>
            <value column="1">Pertaining to, or designating, an acid obtained from the urine of dogs. By decomposition the acid yields a nitrogenous base (called kynurin) and carbonic acid.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyrie</value>
            <value column="1">See Kyrie eleison.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyrie eleison</value>
            <value column="1"><![CDATA[Greek words, meaning "Lord, have mercy upon us," used in the Mass, the breviary offices, the litany of the saints, etc.]]></value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyrie eleison</value>
            <value column="1">The name given to the response to the Commandments, in the service of the Church of England and of the Protestant Episcopal Church.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyrielle</value>
            <value column="1">A litany beginning with the words.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyriolexy</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kyriology</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyriological</value>
            <value column="1">Serving to denote objects by conventional signs or alphabetical characters; as, the original Greek alphabet of sixteen letters was called kyriologic, because it represented the pure elementary sounds. See Curiologic.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kyriology</value>
            <value column="1">The use of literal or simple expressions, as distinguished from the use of figurative or obscure ones.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kythe</value>
            <value column="1">Alt. of Kithe</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kythe</value>
            <value column="1">To come into view; to appear.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kythed</value>
            <value column="1">of Kithe</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kything</value>
            <value column="1">of Kithe</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kytomiton</value>
            <value column="1">See Karyomiton.</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">Kytoplasma</value>
            <value column="1">See Karyoplasma. L () L is the twelfth letter of the English alphabet, and a vocal consonant. It is usually called a semivowel or liquid. Its form and value are from the Greek, through the Latin, the form of the Greek letter being from the Phoenician, and the ultimate origin prob. Egyptian. Etymologically, it is most closely related to r and u; as in pilgrim, peregrine, couch (fr. collocare), aubura (fr. LL. alburnus).</value>
         
         
            <value column="0">kin</value>
            <value column="1">A diminutive suffix; as, manikin; lambkin.</value>
         
</rows> 